<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bangalore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/bangalore/</link><description>Recent content in Bangalore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/bangalore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sharat</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</guid><description>2014 October
While month of September 2014 was supposed to a unique one, It started like just another month of the year.
Honestly it has 17th September which is most times ‘Bishwakarma Puja’ and Pamela’s B’day. From childhood Bishwakarma puja has a special one growing up in Tripura. After Saraswati puja in January/February there was no major festival till Bishwakarma Puja. And there used to pandals and people going out in the evening to visit those pandals.</description></item><item><title>Indian Babus(Govt Official)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-05-indian-babus-govt-official/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-05-indian-babus-govt-official/</guid><description>Today went to the local BBMP (Bruhat Bengaluru Mahanagara Palike) office
to get my property Tax receipt which I paid in June there. Was told to
go other one as this office is being closed. God only knows why
Government build office first and operate there for few years and move
to another one. On going to next office
 The guy told without looking at me &amp;ldquo;Come Monday&amp;rdquo;
Me - ** &amp;ldquo;Sir Monday is Off due to Ganesha Festival&amp;rdquo;**</description></item><item><title>South Trip</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-22-south-trip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 18:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-22-south-trip/</guid><description>Our trip to South was one for which we hardly planned meticulously.
Moreover, my son got fractured elbow but then also our spirit was on
high although bit dampened that whether we will enjoy or not; kind of
excitement mixed with anxiety, hope and happiness. I still remember the
moment we sat in the car and started for the trip which was going to be
one of the longest drive with Aarush.</description></item><item><title>Anandhadam</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-04-03-anandhadam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 04:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-04-03-anandhadam/</guid><description>Prologue, On 2ndof Feb received an open invitation from our
MD to be a part of her team to walk 100KM within 48hours. The walk
was organized by OXFAM to raise funds and awareness of their work among
poor section of society. I immediately hit reply as my earlier
discussion with another friend on the same walk did not materialized.
In the late afternoon I received confirmation that I am in and need to
walk on 10 &amp;amp; 11thFeb.</description></item><item><title>Father Day - Thank you Aarush</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 19:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</guid><description>During month of May there were some sudden turn of events happened that
changed the course of my life as father. Well I am quite positive on
this sudden turn of event that this happened for good. Pamela suddenly
jackpot a teaching Job with one of the premier institute of Bangalore.
And they asked her to join immediately. The first week was in training
in Kormangala was OK OK as Aarush had his summer camp in his old
school.</description></item><item><title>Chod Aaye Hum Woh Galiyan</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-01-17-chod-aaye-hum-woh-galiyan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-01-17-chod-aaye-hum-woh-galiyan/</guid><description>This is our 4th move in last eight years. It was a different protocol
each time. Today I am lost in a mysterious maze of chasing thoughts;
want to pin them down and seal them in jars before they disappear
leaving behind nothing but an empty spot. I came to Tata Sherwood when
my son was 5 months old and today he is almost 3 yrs old. In this time
span I met so many people.</description></item><item><title>Lalbagh Flower Show'10</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-08-14-lalbagh-flower-show10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 19:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-08-14-lalbagh-flower-show10/</guid><description>Finally went to Lalbagh flower show last weekend (8th Aug). Thanks to my
work; was awake from 3 AM and had no trouble of getting ready early on
Sunday. By 8:40 AM we reached; crowd just started to show-up there was
not much problem of parking and all. As soon after we entered the main
glass-house Aarush started to sneeze incessantly. Among many varieties
of flower main attraction was off course the huge structure of India
Gate made of roses; it was tribute to soldiers who lost their lives
during the Second World war.</description></item><item><title>Circle and Cycle</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-02-circle-and-cycle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 17:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-02-circle-and-cycle/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Progress @ New Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-06-30-progress-new-apartment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 20:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-06-30-progress-new-apartment/</guid><description>Some update from previous
post . Till far we
made numerous trip on weekdays and weekends. We are almost done as far
as carpenter work and civil work is concerned. There are still few
things pending but we can wait for now. The next major one and obvious
ones are hardware and shower enclosure fixing at bathrooms along
with painting and electrical fittings. We need to make all the
necessary holes for pictures and wall hanging before final painting
work.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-06-28-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 22:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-06-28-another-weekend/</guid><description>The past weekend was very low key just wanted to laze around to be
honest. It was great to watch to few late nights World Cup Football
matches live with Jishu. Saturday went to usual vegetable market at HAL.
After a quick and early lunch we went to southern part of Bangalore to
drop Jishu back home. It started to drizzle at first and very soon it
was pouring by the time we reached BTM layout.</description></item><item><title>Aarush's-Free ride</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-05-11-aarushs-free-ride/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 22:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-05-11-aarushs-free-ride/</guid><description>Well another small post with pictures. These pictures of Aarush are
months apart. One on left with motorcycle are just after his tonsuring
and on the right are just weeks old. He really likes to ride like any
other boy. And if we try to stop him it does not go well at public
place. When we were in Star Bazaar @ Kormangala few weeks back he
remembered where this toy car was kept and every time we tried to
refrain him he used to go back there.</description></item><item><title>Whats happening</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-05-09-whats-happening/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 16:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-05-09-whats-happening/</guid><description>If long hours in the office and the phone calls at 2AM does fail to keep
me busy this is another Work in Progress which is keeping me recharged.</description></item><item><title>A quick fix</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-01-06-a-quick-fix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-01-06-a-quick-fix/</guid><description>A quick post to start the year.</description></item><item><title>It came to an end</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-19-it-came-to-an-end/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-19-it-came-to-an-end/</guid><description>Officially it is over… ten month long journey came to an end. There were
two exams and one submission before pulling the final curtain by
November end.
Before writing further I must thank Pamela for persuading me in
enrolling in to this Executive MBA (EXMP) of IIM Bangalore.
The course in nutshell covers almost all the areas of management and
gives you enough foundation to build your own interest in specific area.</description></item><item><title>Tonsuring my baby’s head: Tirupati</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 13:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</guid><description>Ever since from childhood heard about Tirupati but never had a chance
till date or never understood why people use to grumble till they had
darshan. May be god wanted me to experience the same. Few days back
Santanu suddenly decided to visit before his upcoming hectic weeks at
office. So it was kind of planned-unplanned trip. Why unplanned
knowingly was&amp;hellip;.we didn&amp;rsquo;t had any ticket in hands before starting the
journey nor we had any references to make use of.</description></item><item><title>Vote for us The Great Driving Challenge !!</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 05:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</guid><description>We are inviting you to post your vote in support of travel. Visit our
application page by clicking on this link here.
Cast your vote and support
us.
This is our great grand escape plan
View GDC -
NH17
in a larger map</description></item><item><title>Happy Holi</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-11-happy-holi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 05:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-11-happy-holi/</guid><description>Have a safe holi; this picture was taken on night before celebrating
holi-ka-dahan</description></item><item><title>Drive to heritage site - Lepakshi</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</guid><description>My 1st term is coming to an end and we are given the upcoming test as
well project submission dates. On reaching home from class on Saturday I
was desperate to go out of Bangalore to get charged to combat the
upcoming gruelling weeks at work and personal front with study. I had no
clue where to go for a day and started to check my faithful websites and
zeroed on Lepakshi from Anita’s
site.</description></item><item><title>Lavazza in India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 18:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</guid><description>Just saw this advertisement on BBC website while checking my morning
dose of news. I was quite fascinated by this ad. Immediately started to
think “Oh this is great!!” now I can get a great coffee to start my
day at home by pressing a button.
If you are not familiar with this machine or not a coffee person this
machine uses special coffee capsules to dispense coffee. There are
varieties of flavor to choose from and trust me it really makes great
coffee.</description></item><item><title>Joyeux Anniversaire- mon petit</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</guid><description>As usual there is lots of gaps of posting. Last month was quite hectic
as we celebrated Aarush&amp;rsquo;s first birthday
We started planning from December onwards. As our schedule now revolves
around his nap-time and whims we hardly get time for each other or to
discuss any matter it’s just a lot more rare these days than it used to
be. So, gone are the days of last minute plan. Despite how he has
completely turned our lives upside down we wanted to celebrate his first
b&amp;rsquo;day which I know he hardly will acknowledge at this age.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 17:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</guid><description>Happy New Year everyone!!!. Wish
you all the best for next 361 days; already late by two days to post the
first one of &amp;lsquo;09.Only one resolution we take &amp;ndash; that is to update our blog often and
complete the list of posts we are supposed to for long time; there are
some of travelogue too to complete. Keep coming back and put your
comments that really makes us going.</description></item><item><title>2008 - mixed bag</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 17:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</guid><description>Thinking of 2008&amp;hellip; it was an eventful year. We started by adding a new
member to our family after going through lot of apprehension. Now our
new world started to revolve around baby with umpteen number of diaper
changes and sleepless nights, his cries, bowel movement and what
not&amp;hellip;..
Pamela&amp;rsquo;s parents were at Mumbai to help us in our happily tough times.
Even before completing two months Aarush left Mumbai for Pamela&amp;rsquo;s
hometown.</description></item><item><title>As time flies...</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 06:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</guid><description>We feel elated to celebrate our sixth year of togetherness @ IndiJoe. A
journey full of sweet, bitter, sour, spicy and many more&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; flavours.
After all soft items like paper, linen etc finally we reached
anniversary which is represented by metal -&amp;ldquo;Iron
Anniversary&amp;rdquo;.
This year&amp;rsquo;s anniversary is extra special because we were given a very
precious gift from God, our son Aarush, and now we&amp;rsquo;ve moved on from
&amp;ldquo;couple&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;small family&amp;rdquo;, and it feels amazing.</description></item><item><title>Extempo Performance</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-08-28-extempo-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 04:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-08-28-extempo-performance/</guid><description>Pamela&amp;rsquo;s maternal cousin
Jeet
was our guest in Bangalore for three nights from Calcutta. His purpose
of this trip to meet his school and college mates as most of them are
working in Bangalore IT sector. Jeet plays guitar and mouth organ as
hobbies. His musical talent is in his gene , he got it from his
mother
who is a trained singer and used to perform in All India Radio in her
young days.</description></item><item><title>Whatz FRESH about Reliance Fresh ?</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</guid><description>As we are new to Bangalore trying to explore all nearby hypermarket,
supermarket and open markets as we settle in. This is also giving us as
chance to explore places around. The first one we tried and explored was
BIG-BAZAR on Old Madras road. As it is just near to one of our
office address in Bangalore I knew how to reach there without being
lost. Then weekend after we tried SPAR at Kormongala followed by
Nilgiris.</description></item><item><title>We are @ Bangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-06-20-we-are-bangalore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 16:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-06-20-we-are-bangalore/</guid><description>This post is going to be a quick one, need to write and publish in next
8 minutes time I have from my grueling schedule. Just to let you know we
(this time Aarush &amp;amp; Pamela accompanied me) reached safely after
traveling from west to central-part to east and then to south of India .
The details of long travel will require several small posts but with
Aarush, new apartment and work do not think we will be left with ample
time to write those.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye – Mumbai – a quick update</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</guid><description>I
did not want to use a title like “Welcome to Bangalore” or “Here I
come to Bangaloru” on purpose as need some time before I can call this
my new home. From long time we were knowing that we have to move to
Banglore but on personal grounds I had to postpone it which was readily
accepted by my company. In recent months, I was waiting for that green
signal from my company that I have to move in any case.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Parking</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</guid><description>Encountered this perfect parking on a small by-lane in Bangalore. For
sure I will not be able to park like this; normally have enough
difficulties in parallel parking on the street between cars. I was
failed (fatal) as rear tire touched the ramp in my first attempt to
secure Californian driving License. Looks like the owner will not be
change car as this is customized parking only which can accommodate
small car.</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Hebbal Lake</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid><description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress on
construction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as at
work things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is a
nice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes a
happy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in next
month this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that is
going to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item></channel></rss>