<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>street on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/street/</link><description>Recent content in street on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/street/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Perfect Parking</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</guid><description>Encountered this perfect parking on a small by-lane in Bangalore. For
sure I will not be able to park like this; normally have enough
difficulties in parallel parking on the street between cars. I was
failed (fatal) as rear tire touched the ramp in my first attempt to
secure Californian driving License. Looks like the owner will not be
change car as this is customized parking only which can accommodate
small car.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>Last Week</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-11-last-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 14:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-11-last-week/</guid><description>Watched lots of movies, uploaded some photos to
Running and
walked around Paris last week.
New in gallery - bibs from running . Well you must be wondering what is
that ? For a person like me from whom the activity of sport was taken
away by various pressures at young age it means a lot. The good side of
it is that I am the very few fortunate one to run at this age at various
places but rest remains as silent voice in vast population of India.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Cordoba – Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid><description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought of
Cordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggested
visiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reach
the train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. The
fair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costs
almost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item><item><title>St. Michel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2004 22:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</guid><description>Perched on a rocky islet in the midst of vast sandbanks exposed to
powerful tides between Normandy and Brittany (on the north coast of
France) stand the &amp;lsquo;Wonder of the West&amp;rsquo;, a Gothic-style abbey dedicated
to the Archangel St Michael
It was built in 8thcentury, the buildings of Mont St. Michel
were constructed of granite which were carried from near-by island but
some limestone were also used in the cloister.</description></item><item><title>Stockholm (Aug 14th - 17th)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2003 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</guid><description>While browsing through web sites for summer travel deals I found there
was a very attractive deal by Ryan Air to Stockholm.We went there middle
of August when Paris was burning with summer heat. It was a great escape
to Scandinavia. Stockholm was very clean and very beautiful. Although,
the weather was not at its best as it rained for first two days.
We stayed in the centre of Stockholm (Drottninggatan) one side of this
pedestrian street with full of shops.</description></item><item><title>Trip to Amsterdam (June 7th-9th)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</guid><description>Our first trip in Europe, I decided about Amsterdam because of two
reason Van Gogh and people of Amsterdam. To our delight it was really
great and was a great escape from noise and crowd of Paris.The city is
not so big compared to Paris but very clean and friendly. As most
tourist books suggest Dutch people has unique and very efficient
solution to their day-to-day problem. The streets are not crowded with
car.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Paris an unofficial guide by Malc</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2003 20:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</guid><description>Here is a set of stuff about flat hunting, contributed from many
sources. One note. Most of this is for finding a flat on your own.Don&amp;rsquo;t
go near
Hestia.fr (many a tale of woe has originated
from here) Get your &amp;lsquo;dossier&amp;rsquo; together straight away. Needs
photocopy of
Present employment contract
Last 3 pay slips
Last 3 rent receipts (or in my case my 1 year mortgage statement from
the UK)</description></item></channel></rss>