<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>people on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/people/</link><description>Recent content in people on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:50:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A quick post</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</guid><description>Reading old newspaper clipping fascinate me; an article which earns a
good amount space on that day and most likely people read and forgot.
and here I am reading it after days with a fresh eye. And most times it
turns out to be a great story to read with eagerness.
This one was bit special which caught my eyes today was &amp;ldquo;Chaturanan
Mishra
passed away&amp;rdquo;; now there are few things which made me to write this quick
post.</description></item><item><title>Whatz FRESH about Reliance Fresh ?</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</guid><description>As we are new to Bangalore trying to explore all nearby hypermarket,
supermarket and open markets as we settle in. This is also giving us as
chance to explore places around. The first one we tried and explored was
BIG-BAZAR on Old Madras road. As it is just near to one of our
office address in Bangalore I knew how to reach there without being
lost. Then weekend after we tried SPAR at Kormongala followed by
Nilgiris.</description></item><item><title>Shiv Jayanti</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid><description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night of
lord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindu
mythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birth
anniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17th
century fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He was
named Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabai
had prayed for a son.</description></item><item><title>Bhat Suar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid><description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”
(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my college
days. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of same
state 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similar
to an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”
and second part “suar which means pig”.</description></item><item><title>Geography - mismatch</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 05:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</guid><description>For any fifth grader Mumbai is located in Western part of India if asked
north or south answer will be south. So how can there be a church of
North India which is located in posh south Mumbai in a stone throw
distance from famous Flora Fountain? You may wonder - in the world of
bharat-todo (Break India by new politicians) how all bhaia&amp;rsquo;s(people from
North India Bihar and Uttarpradesh - speaking Hindi) suddenly built a
church for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Indian Inglish</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</guid><description>The biggest asset of 21st century modern India is its big chunk of young
educated Indian who can speak decent English. There is lot of buzz and
business happening in India as there are numerous outsourcing
operations.
But on the ground we speak very different English with borrowed words
from Indian regional languages that do find their way into our writing,
advertisements and newspapers, TV spots and shows from north to south or
east to west.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>An afteroon at Pisa</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</guid><description>Being exhausted from last evening we got up bit late and had very good
breakfast before hitting the road. According to our itinerary, distance
to be covered was long one as our hotel was booked at Florence.
We took train to La Spezia, it was a crowded, got packed with each
passing stations of Cinque Terre but became empty as soon as we
crossed Riomaggiore. We had to wait a bit at La Spezia as train was
coming from north was late.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Belgium</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</guid><description>While categorizing our old travelogs I found there was no post on
Belgium
which values a lot for me. As I go down the memory lane&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;year 2003,
within 2 ½ months of marriage we have to move to Paris from US which was
a big change for me. Apart from the cultural shock, language was immense
barrier for day today life as well to mingle up with people around. Not
only that, in Indian arrange marriage, it takes time to understand each
other with each one&amp;rsquo;s weaknesses and failings.</description></item><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>Thread of love</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</guid><description>It is a celebration of unconditional love between brother and sister in
Hindu culture. This age old celebration tries to remind us of the
beautiful and unique relationship between brother and sister celebrated
since time immemorial. Sisters tie sacred threads on brothers wrist
asking for longer &amp;amp; healthy life of brother and brothers in-turn vow to
protect (to save her- Raksha) their sisters from any unpleasant
situations of life on this day.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item><item><title>W questions of Indian life</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</guid><description>In India, life of middle class is different compared to occidental
culture. There is a vast population of middle class in India and within
middle class there are three distinct sub-divisions - “lower
middleclass”, “middle middleclass” and “higher middleclass”.
Comprehending the complexities of Indian society is not that easy.
Though there are variations in socio-economic life within these three
but one thing is common between all of them - everyone is curious to
know whatz happening in others life despite of their own busy life.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid><description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arranged
for two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. We
opted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in a
non-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary included
Dona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilica
and se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurga
dedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit to
Ancestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description></item><item><title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid><description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I got
opportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, I
couldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarried
Indian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as an
escort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered like
friend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description></item><item><title>Mumbaiya Lingo</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 03:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</guid><description>While boarding a train I heard one co-passenger saying to another
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” which astonished me for a fraction of
second as its not at all palatable to an untrained ears. It seems this
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” is considered far more effective while getting
into locals then long winded formal request to the people ahead to make
way.
I was trying hard to relate as it sounds hindi but actually its not.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Micro$oft Launch @ Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</guid><description>Micro$oft is doing a round of business and technical launch show around
India. The products are Exchange 2007, Office 2007 and Vista. I attended
only a brief session @ Hyatt.
Well, somehow my name was not there even though I registered 10 days
before the event.
And my business card with orange and blue dots did not help much to get
attention from those desk people. Anyway, it was solid 40 minutes of
work for me – replied emails, chat with business contact got updates
from their team – thanks to CDMA mobile card.</description></item><item><title>Travel Under Terror</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 00:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</guid><description>There were massive bomb blasts last summer in Mumbai local trains. After
that now there are constant reminders for the commuters to be on alert
and check their surroundings. It is logistical nightmare to manage the
massive number of commuters who takes train every day in Mumbai. In
simple words, “impossible” will be closest word I can pick.
Few months back after lots of planning and public announcement Mumbai
Police conducted a security drill where every passenger was supposed to
pass via metal detector in two Main Terminus in the evening but after
few moments it was clear that police can not handle the stream of
passengers in lakhs and crores as they were heading home and it was
abandoned.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Linen anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid><description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the naming
convention it is Linen
Anniversary we have still
have a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek
(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. After
our wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description></item><item><title>Local trains of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</guid><description>After moving to Mumbai (India) commuting from one place to another was a
big problem (as we didn’t have our own vehicle). It seems Mumbai local
trains are the most efficient one carrying millions of people everyday.
Getting in and out of local trains is one of the hardest tasks
particularly during rush hours which every mumbains has to undergo at
least ones in their life. So, lot of advice was given from Santanu’s
maternal family who are staying here for more than 15 years.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Aids Awareness - Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2006 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</guid><description>Can any one guess what this publicity is about? Well, this is 2006 anti
Aids campaign by city hall of Paris (Paris protège l&amp;rsquo;amour means
Paris protects love)
In the photo what we see is sunset on some historical building with moon
at backdrop, but when you take a close look moon is&amp;hellip; a condom. It aims
at promoting the use of condoms among the population i.e., to have safe
sex.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Le vol</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-04-le-vol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 09:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-04-le-vol/</guid><description>I am not a person who hates flying to start with as my major air-travel
in recent years was visiting India on holiday from Europe. Like all
other events in life this can be looked at like a coin; on one side the
travel time has reduced significantly while on other side only 20 to 30
kilos of baggage allowed compared to California (65 Kilo).
As we were moving out of Paris we had lot of important things to bring
along with us that we will need till our shipment arrives in next 5
weeks time.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>Last Week</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-11-last-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 14:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-11-last-week/</guid><description>Watched lots of movies, uploaded some photos to
Running and
walked around Paris last week.
New in gallery - bibs from running . Well you must be wondering what is
that ? For a person like me from whom the activity of sport was taken
away by various pressures at young age it means a lot. The good side of
it is that I am the very few fortunate one to run at this age at various
places but rest remains as silent voice in vast population of India.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Hiking Mt.Rigi - 22nd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 14:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</guid><description>Queen of Swiss Mountains From Zurich we went to Mt. Rigi via Arth-Goldau a very short train ride.
From there we took the cogwheel train to the summit at Rigi-Kulm
(1,800m). Incredible vistas, typical Swiss farmhouses, and hundreds of
cows with bells will surprise one throughout the trip. Reward on going
to top is magnificent panorama of Alpine peaks crowding around the
convoluted contours of Lake Lucerne. While going up it was a nice
weather but slowly &amp;amp; slowly it started getting dark.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Rescued - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</guid><description>By now, seeing the time I was
discussing about hitch hiking to the next big town which was ruled out
by Santanu as it seems not safe. Even I was suggesting him how about
getting into a car of people who does not look that young and suddenly
one car stopped and they asked if we need any lift… looking at their
face we did not take a second to decide and say “YES” in unison (which
came out as if instinct) with big smiling face.</description></item><item><title>C’est fou !</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</guid><description>Football - the definition for the same may be quite simple but it
certainly does have lots of colors. It is a mutli-billion dollar
business from sporting to TV companies. For some it is as close to their
religion. People can fight or hug with a complete stranger while
ignoring his family or close one when there is a match.
As we live in Europe it is very hard to escape it.</description></item><item><title>Uddan - Flight</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid><description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing its
publicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in the
world. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouraged
us to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar covering
around 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooth
though they were very strict about luggage weight.
In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough leg
room; quality of the food was better than what we had before and was
good with choice of films and music on demand.</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item><item><title>Metro in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</guid><description>Living in Paris and not travelling in Metro has lots of demerits. Like
usual I am going to start with the traffic jams, one way roads,
unavailability of parking, high parking tickets and very unusual sense
of Parisian driving skills.
These only list if you have a car and travelling of your own. But what
about those who are taking other mode of smart transports like Bus,
Tram, Bicycle, Rollerblade or just walk to work or work from home?</description></item><item><title>Tibx Shoe Laces</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</guid><description>Yes these are my dirty shoes. Not very sure about the origin of those
shoe laces, I got them when my old office was getting closed. Missing
the TIBX bus and shares I got those laces :( (People got nice race cars
and big houses in Bay Area a dream come true in this materialistic world
and what I got for boarding the train late. Well I have another pair of
these laces….</description></item><item><title>Hotel Train Lisbon to Madrid</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</guid><description>We
were at the very last phase of our vacation. We took train back to
Madrid tonight as from there we had our flight back to Paris.
We booked the train ticket long back; I went in-person to get the same
from Spanish Railway ticket office based in Paris. The office is kind of
hidden by all the stores near to Boulevard Haussmann; ever busy shopping
place.
Being Indian it was a really something new although we had experienced
few other different night trains in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Cordoba – Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid><description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought of
Cordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggested
visiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reach
the train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. The
fair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costs
almost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item><item><title>LA HOLLANDE, ALLEZ-Y MAINTENANT!</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-08-la-hollande-allez-y-maintenant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2004 22:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-08-la-hollande-allez-y-maintenant/</guid><description>Seeing one of friend&amp;rsquo;s photographs we were so excited to visit that
place. That, in our last trip to Amsterdam (May 2003) we tried to visit
that - but alas! Local people told us that Tulip season is already over.
But deep down in our heart we wanted to visit that place particularly
Keukenhof thinking -maybe next year.
Then we were in touch with Holland tourism in-order to know more about
Keukenhof.</description></item><item><title>Got an IPOD</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2004 21:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</guid><description>Requested my brother to send me one I-pod from USA with Hitesh as he was
coming to Paris on a business trip. It was very nice to catch up with
Hitesh, Neetu and Simran after moving out of CA. We met them at their
hotel in Latin quarter and had dinner with them. It was almost 2 in the
morning when we returned home in the cold night of February.</description></item><item><title>A year in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2004 04:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved to Paris almost a year back from US. We try to travel around at
least once a month outside of Paris. This year so far we have been to
Zurich, Mt. Saint Michel and Barcelona.
I like Paris but some time French system and people makes me mad. I am
going to run Paris Half marathon in March first week. Now a days I am
trying to run more regularly.</description></item><item><title>London 5days (July 29th - Aug 3rd)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2003 23:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</guid><description>We went to London the proper Bilayet (Foreign land -as mentioned by
S.Rushdie ) for five days. We stayed as guest of Sampath, at his home
bit outside of London. The trip would not have been so pleasant and
memorable without his help and warm hospitality.
We reached around noon at Waterloo station by Eurostar. After keeping
our luggage at cloak room we went straight to London Eye. It was a
nice start to see all the monuments of London from birds view.</description></item><item><title>Trip to Amsterdam (June 7th-9th)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</guid><description>Our first trip in Europe, I decided about Amsterdam because of two
reason Van Gogh and people of Amsterdam. To our delight it was really
great and was a great escape from noise and crowd of Paris.The city is
not so big compared to Paris but very clean and friendly. As most
tourist books suggest Dutch people has unique and very efficient
solution to their day-to-day problem. The streets are not crowded with
car.</description></item><item><title>Second Titre De Sejour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</guid><description>On the 9th of April we were supposed to collect our new Titre De
Sejour (Long term VISA) from Cite Prefecture de Police. The interview
was fixed almost 3 months ago and we reached there before our scheduled
time to be make sure this time there is no big problem. But our turn
came around 4o&amp;rsquo;clock which is almost one hour behind our scheduled time.
And after checking all our paper she says oh!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Paris an unofficial guide by Malc</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2003 20:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</guid><description>Here is a set of stuff about flat hunting, contributed from many
sources. One note. Most of this is for finding a flat on your own.Don&amp;rsquo;t
go near
Hestia.fr (many a tale of woe has originated
from here) Get your &amp;lsquo;dossier&amp;rsquo; together straight away. Needs
photocopy of
Present employment contract
Last 3 pay slips
Last 3 rent receipts (or in my case my 1 year mortgage statement from
the UK)</description></item><item><title>Louvre</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-02-louvre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-02-louvre/</guid><description>After figuring out, lots of museum have free entry on first Sunday of
every month we started with our museum tour with Louvre. Oh!! It is
a museum in itself. I am sure all of you know some thing or other about
it. We started our tour with Egyptian section last month. We are still
visiting &amp;amp; we think we only covered 1/3rd so far after two Sundays. God
knows how many sundays it will take to complete this whole museum.</description></item><item><title>Visit to Ram Krishna Mission</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</guid><description>Ramkrishana Mission or center of Vendantic Society as we know it,
commonly is situated out side of Paris. A great place just to go and
spend some time in peace. It was birth anniversary of Ramkrishana when
we went there first time. We were very unsure how to reach the Center.
But it was a miracle we found some one speaking English at the station
to guide us. This center is quite big area-wise compared to San
Francisco and Berkeley one that we visited.</description></item><item><title>Moving to Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</guid><description>OK, we moved to our own apartment after all. This whole week was very
busy and hectic.Monday: It started with getting informed that my
checkout from hotel was the very same day. But I was not informed about
this before. And hotel people informed Pamela and disconnected
telephone; a real mess. We could not connect each other and convey what
was happening at two ends. I must have to admit the HR practice is worse
here.</description></item><item><title>Tour Effiel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</guid><description>It was a bright and bleak winter day, we headed straight to the number
one attraction of Paris or Europe as you might say. A great view; this
picture was taken by a Japanese tourist. There were lots of people from
Indian sub-continent selling momento of Eiffel Tower for cheap. But we
left after a while, as it was too cold and windy that day to go at the
top of tower.</description></item><item><title>OMI and Prefecture</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-07-omi-and-prefecture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-07-omi-and-prefecture/</guid><description>After getting over with jetlag went to OMI for my medical visit next
morning. It was OK. Tried Metro for the first time (Parlez vous Anglais)
worked. BTW this medical vist is must before any one starts working in
French. But all that good time was so short lived as we reached Cite
Police Prefecture. A very big old building in front of Notre Dame in
center Paris. This is the H.</description></item><item><title>Moved to Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</guid><description>After basking last 4 years in Bay Area we moved to Paris. The weather
was bleak cold which almost blew me off as we were getting in to the
TAXI at the airport. Reached hotel without problem, had a Chinese female
driver speaking English. Exhausted and tired to reach work which looked
like a 5 minutes walk from hotel on map. But, got lost in concrete
jungle of La Defense which is one of the unique place with
concentrated modern high-rise buildings in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>