<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wayanad on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/wayanad/</link><description>Recent content in wayanad on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 18:16:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/wayanad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Madras Filter Coffee</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 18:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is old an old one. My morning does not start
without coffee on weekdays. I am not quite human still have my
morning coffee will probably describe it best. In India coffee is very
different from West. I came to know recently that Indian Coffee Board
is head quartered in Bangalore. The main coffee producing region of
India(hills of Coorg, Niligiris and Wayanad&amp;gt;) are not very far off
Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Wayanad-III</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-14-wayanad-iii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-14-wayanad-iii/</guid><description>On second day we went to see Lakidi view point, Phookot lake and
Vythiri resort. Lakidi is about 2 km south of Chain Tree and is the
gateway of Wayanad which is on highway to Calicut. It is a ghat pass at
an elevation of 700m above sea level.We crossed Kalpetta and drove
mostly on NH 212.
Overwhelmed with scenery as this highway is heaven on this earth , a
beautiful place with lot of tea gardens on the way.</description></item><item><title>Wayanad-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-13-wayanad-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 12:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-13-wayanad-ii/</guid><description>After a deep slumber the next morning we woke-up fresh and energetic.
Aarush wanted to play seeing an open space- courtyard. They have toys,
cycles, carom board, badminton court, balls to play with. He was really
happy to get all these stuffs. What more parent wants if kid is happy
you are happy otherwise nothing on earth can make you happy.
Morning, we were shown all rooms available there. It was a nice room
with a central common area and one room each on either side.</description></item><item><title>Visit to North kerala- Wayanad</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 06:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</guid><description>From the time Santanu having classes and top of it exams this month; its
really a grueling month for both of us. For this I too was not getting
some time off from “Our little one”. There was absolute need of one
break. Santanu suddenly said two days before last exam that he is having
leave and if interested then we can go somewhere near by. Then he only
started reading on net and ended up saying we would go to
WAYANAD- Northern region of Kerala.</description></item></channel></rss>