<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>modern india on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/modern-india/</link><description>Recent content in modern india on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/modern-india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Indian Inglish</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</guid><description>The biggest asset of 21st century modern India is its big chunk of young
educated Indian who can speak decent English. There is lot of buzz and
business happening in India as there are numerous outsourcing
operations.
But on the ground we speak very different English with borrowed words
from Indian regional languages that do find their way into our writing,
advertisements and newspapers, TV spots and shows from north to south or
east to west.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item></channel></rss>