<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>piazza on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/piazza/</link><description>Recent content in piazza on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/piazza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Venice at leisure</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid><description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after two
days of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s
Square. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was too
crowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out of
time and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.
Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear end
which is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>Rome (Sep 5th-7th)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 09:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</guid><description>We wanted to visit all the top attractions of Italy in one trip but due
to vacation time (for Parisians) and taking off from work and with
Pamela&amp;rsquo;s school we could not do. So, we planned for only Rome. We
flew with Alitalia from CDG this time in early morning. It was much
better than Ryan Airlines in terms of access to the airport. But the
initial fun started when just before checking-in we have to run 3
terminals to collect our tickets from Air Traffic office.</description></item></channel></rss>