<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rajasthan on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/rajasthan/</link><description>Recent content in rajasthan on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:18:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/rajasthan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chokhi Dhani- Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</guid><description>Last day at Jaipur, today we have kept ourselves more or less free for
shopping. Had breakfast at hotel lawn for the first time. The buffet
breakfast at Hotel Madhuvan worth only when you have time to enjoy
it. We met one Indian family who were travelling from Gujrat for the
Diwali weekend to Jaipur and wanted to join us at Chokhi Dhani later in
the evening. Around 10 we left for shopping with Mr.</description></item><item><title>Maro des “Rajasthan”</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-18-maro-des-rajasthan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 17:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-18-maro-des-rajasthan/</guid><description>The first thing that struck me about Rajasthan was its roads when I last
went in 2000 with my parents. Rajasthan roads are amazing; and they are
very well connected interms of bus, train, private cars, even one can
hire cars to drive around between different places with in state. This
makes travelling in Rajasthan quite safe and less tiring. With good road
conditions you can also explore the interiors of Rajasthan.</description></item><item><title>Ajmer-Pushkar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-14-ajmer-pushkar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 23:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-14-ajmer-pushkar/</guid><description>Early morning reached Jaipur from Jaisalmer by train. This time our
cab driver from hotel (Madhuban) was waiting and on reaching hotel
relaxed for while. Before leaving for Jodhpur, we have fixed
with Mr. Singh (our reliable cab driver) for this trip to
Ajmer-Pushkar. As usual, he was there on time; left hotel room
around 8.00am. Had our breakfast on way at small neat and clean dhaba.
Road being 6 lane; had very comfort drive and was hardly crowded.</description></item><item><title>Jaisalmer</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-11-jaisalmer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-11-jaisalmer/</guid><description>We reached Jaisalmer early morning around 4.00am.Going from station
to hotel is another headache if you don’t have pick-up service
particularly at wee hours. We didn&amp;rsquo;t had that service from hotel as it
was extra 100INR so on reaching station we found, 10 people surrounded
us even they don’t allow couples to talk among themselves. Finally
hired one for 40 INR to go to Deoki Niwas hotel. When we reached, we
literally had to wake them up.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-09-jodhpur-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 22:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-09-jodhpur-ii/</guid><description>We started early morning after breakfast around 8 .00am. But luck is
always not in favour we got one nasty cab driver unlike Jaipur. Although
hired cab through hotel and asked to take us to Osyian but he insisted
on going to majestic sandstone palace of Umaid Bhawan. Before going
there he took us to shops for early morning shopping but we
didn’t.(they get commission when they take clients to their choice of
place).</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur 1st Nov 2010</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-22-jodhpur-1st-nov-2010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-22-jodhpur-1st-nov-2010/</guid><description>31stmidnight boarded train to Jodhpur from Jaipur after a
long day we were very tired . The train was late as it arrived from
Delhi. On the train meet Subhojit who was also in Rajasthan for one
long week break just like us from Bangalore. Their itinerary was bit
different compared to us and they were going to Jaiselmer. On the wee
hours of 1st November reached the platform of Jodhpur and thankgod for
ensuring that hotel provided a cab for pickup.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-01-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 02:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-01-jaipur/</guid><description>We woke around 7ish and left by the same Cab with Mr. Singh (who took us
to Shekhawati) around 8:30 from hotel. As Mr. Singh said jokingly lets
start the day in auspicious way – which mean Birla Temple was first
on the list and we reached the parking lot at dot 9. The journey took us
trough the posh residential area of Jaipur with huge bungalows which
have similarities with the Lutyens’ Delhi but a rarity in modern India.</description></item><item><title>Shekhawati - Open Air Art Gallery</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 17:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</guid><description>29th Oct - We took SpiceJet flight to Jaipur but unfortunately could
not make it within time due to technical problems and traffic congestion
we were made to wait for 3 hrs inside flight. We reached around 22:00 to
our pre-booked Hotel Madhuban by prepaid taxi.
On reaching hotel driver says &amp;ldquo;kya bekar hotel liya hain sir&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;.ughh.
Lump in my throat as all booking was done by me. It was a laborious,
monotonous job going through website after website, jotting down details
regarding price.</description></item><item><title>Des vacances</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-29-des-vacances/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 02:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-29-des-vacances/</guid><description>We are off to Rajasthan starting tomorrow. Here is the plan lets see
what we achieve in next one week-
29th Oct Fly to Jaipur on SpiceJet 30th Oct shekhawati day trip from Jaipur 31st Jaipur ; in the night catch train for Jodhpur 1st Nov in Jodhpur 2nd November in Jodhpur catch night train to Jaisalmer 3rd November in Jaisalmer and sunset in desert 4th Nov in the evening catch train back to Jaipur 5th Nov relax in Jaipur celebrate Deepavali 6th Nov if possible make a trip to Ajmer and Pushkar 7th Nov fly back to Bangalore All the bookings are done and big thanks to Pamela.</description></item></channel></rss>