<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>post bus on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/post-bus/</link><description>Recent content in post bus on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:09:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/post-bus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rescued - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</guid><description>By now, seeing the time I was
discussing about hitch hiking to the next big town which was ruled out
by Santanu as it seems not safe. Even I was suggesting him how about
getting into a car of people who does not look that young and suddenly
one car stopped and they asked if we need any lift… looking at their
face we did not take a second to decide and say “YES” in unison (which
came out as if instinct) with big smiling face.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item></channel></rss>