<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bon Appetite on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/bon-appetite/</link><description>Recent content in Bon Appetite on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/bon-appetite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coffee – makes me happy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is not new and there are few
posts on the same subject
in past. The culture of having a good time with a cup of coffee is
catching up in India. Café Coffee Day aka CCD is expanding its
footprints in rapid speed from past few years; people close to the
business speculate they are just spending money and expanding in hope
for a bought over by some FDI like Starbucks if the later enter
Indian market.</description></item><item><title>Sondesh</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-05-21-sondesh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 12:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-05-21-sondesh/</guid><description>Bengalis are considered as food-lovers (khadya-rashik).For them any
sumptuous bengali meal is always incomplete without a sweet dish. Just
like any french meal which would remain incomplete without a bottle of
exquisite french wine.
I was not a big fan of sweet earlier but when you live with someone for
a long period of time, you quickly start to adapt some of your partner’s
habits be it deliberately or inadvertently.</description></item><item><title>chocolate Banana Muffins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</guid><description>First weekend of December past with lots of activities - a trip to
commercial street, malls and office. On Saturday Aarush forced me to
leave bed early - deprived me of extended sleeping on the weekend. After
that I was busy with him mostly for breakfast. Nowadays he has developed
a nasty habit of prolonged (around an hour or more) eating times be it
breakfast, lunch or dinner. After that he played for while but soon he
was sleepy for nap.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Tomato Soup</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 20:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</guid><description>Till far only soup ever tried to make was carrot soup in Paris that too
in bleak winter. Big thanks to my French Teacher for sharing the
recipe en Français. Recently, went to local vegetable market; seeing
tomato got so tempted that without thinking bought two kilos. Then I
brainstormed a bit to think and idea of soup came as an escape. Here is
my 2 cents recipe. If craving for something sweet and sour at the
same time just have a bowl of creamy tomato soup to satisfy your desire
as an appetizer.</description></item><item><title>Sweet potato dessert</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</guid><description>Sweet potato dessert (Ranga Alur Puli) is an age old Bengali dessert - a
sweet lover&amp;rsquo;s delight for sure. Its crispy outer layer mesmerizes
gastronomic senses. As for its availability, it is more of a
traditional sweet, prepared in households. These days some sweet shops
are starting to include this in their repertoire to cater to the
time-constrained generation.
My hubby being born with a sweet tooth, do enjoy sweet of any kind.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine -II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 19:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</guid><description>As I said lots of thoughts were coming
across in spite of
my busy-ness. So first was to ask Pamela to come over at Fort area for
lunch which was denied by her saying that lots of household chores left
to be done. Then again I modified my plan and asked her to join at
evening for dinner when she told me she won’t as without any prior
booking no food will be available at any good restaurant because of that
day- which is in fact quite true.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Making of Chocolate Charlotte</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</guid><description>Today we have a dinner invitation; spent whole yesterday morning in
thinking what would be good to prepare as I did not want to buy anything
from supermarket. Since we are moving, wanted to clean the fridge
without overstuffing it. So after lot of thought came to conclusion that
charlotte might be best. Learnt this recipe from a friend.
A charlotte is any dessert that&amp;rsquo;s moulded into a container lined
with sponge fingers or boudoir biscuits (purchased at a bakery or
supermarket).</description></item><item><title>Italian aroma…</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Daney Daney Pey likha hain khaney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo;- which
colloquially means each grain has the name of the person who will eat it
(it is the fortune of the person to have certain meal or not). Well the
same with more of spice in Hindi movies &amp;ldquo;goli goli pey likha hain
marney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo; which means in each bullets it is written the
name of the person who will die.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Green plate</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</guid><description>In
my salad days I used to hate many green veggies and I remember when maa
used to scold me for the same. Somehow I didn’t had taste for them at
that point of time but gradually I developed the taste so much so that I
can now survive happily on those green things (cow-food).
From long time Santanu wanted to make a change on our meal as it seems
we both are putting on weight.</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>Joy of baking</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-01-17-joy-of-baking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2006 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-01-17-joy-of-baking/</guid><description>With the cold weather and shorter day lights lots of baking is going on
and enjoying the butter and sugar lately. Feeling guilty as cann&amp;rsquo;t
resist and moreover did not do any exercise after my Paris - Versailles
marathon :(
We were invited to one of my colleague’s place for the first time after
almost 3 years in France for ‘Galette des rois’. It was very
memorable and an enjoyable evening.</description></item></channel></rss>