<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>south mumbai on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/south-mumbai/</link><description>Recent content in south mumbai on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 05:50:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/south-mumbai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Geography - mismatch</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 05:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</guid><description>For any fifth grader Mumbai is located in Western part of India if asked
north or south answer will be south. So how can there be a church of
North India which is located in posh south Mumbai in a stone throw
distance from famous Flora Fountain? You may wonder - in the world of
bharat-todo (Break India by new politicians) how all bhaia&amp;rsquo;s(people from
North India Bihar and Uttarpradesh - speaking Hindi) suddenly built a
church for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item></channel></rss>