<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>baby on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/baby/</link><description>Recent content in baby on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 13:06:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/baby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fifth Month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-15-fifth-month/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 05:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-15-fifth-month/</guid><description>May 17- June 16
By 5th month slowly started introducing solid food like banana and
apple puree to Aarush. According to our custom till
&amp;ldquo;Annaprasanna&amp;rdquo;
we are not suppose to introduce solid food like rice or wheat to baby.
And his didu was also against using common baby food item like &amp;ldquo;Cerelac&amp;rdquo;
as they contain rice or wheat. This resulted in his first solid bite
being fruit &amp;ndash; mashed banana. The first spoon he swallowed as my mom
fed him, but little man has a frown of disapproval, like &amp;ldquo;what the heck
they are feeding me?</description></item><item><title>playing with bubbles</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-28-playing-with-bubbles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 04:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-28-playing-with-bubbles/</guid><description>Aarush and Pamela playing with soap bubbles ; this video is bit old when
he did not started walking at that point of time. He was bit amused with
bubbles trying to catch them but could not.</description></item><item><title>Fourth month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</guid><description>(17th April - 16th May)
Normally A is taken to doctor for monthly check-up once other then that
no outing for him. As he is considered too small for all these by my
parents. So they neither allow him nor me to go anywhere. After birth it
was third time when Aarush was taken out of the house to meet people
other then his doc&amp;rsquo;s clinic. Moreover because of weather it was
difficult for us to go anywhere.</description></item><item><title>Third month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-15-third-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 11:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-15-third-month/</guid><description>(17th March-16th April)
Now, Aarush started to twitch, smile, frown and stretch a lot after
waking from sleep. Amazingly ( I never knew this) and apparently babies
between three to four months are at the stage where they get very
playful and drinking milk is not a priority anymore, I believe. They
prefer to talk and coo to adults, and being very observant at this stage
and they are attracted to moving objects, colours and everything new
around them.</description></item><item><title>Second month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-04-second-month/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 01:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-04-second-month/</guid><description>(17th February- 17th March)
Parenthood is a lifelong journey. No amount of training and
preparation can ever prepare fully for it. We are learning about our
little helpless bundle and same probably on his side. After returning
from official trip santanu was agog to spent more time with Aarush as if
it was ages he has spent not seeing him.
Aarush now learnt to squeal in delight as his arms flail about in the
air above him.</description></item><item><title>First month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-07-first-month/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-07-first-month/</guid><description>Tiredness was still there after delivery and by now I realized what
people were talking about… shamelessly take advantage of this period to
rest yourself. On other hand I was desperate to take a step outside
house of my own after 9 months bed rest to feel the breeze brushing
against my skin. But it never happened because of customs.
Ooof&amp;hellip;. On 10th day took a complete shower from head to toe as on
same day my stitch was removed which took hardly few minutes.</description></item><item><title>Birth of a Mother-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-25-birth-of-a-mother-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 05:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-25-birth-of-a-mother-ii/</guid><description>Truly said-
The moment a child is born,the mother is also born.She never existed
before.The woman existed, but the mother, never.A mother is something
absolutely new.
~Rajneesh
As soon as I was moved out of O.T. Aarush was brought to his crib next
to me. His didu was first to hold him in her arms then was given
forcefully to his thamma. She didn&amp;rsquo;t wanted to take him as it seems he
would become &amp;ldquo;Kol-lengra&amp;rdquo; (will get use to be in arms).</description></item><item><title>Birth of a Mother-I</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-22-birth-of-a-mother-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 03:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-22-birth-of-a-mother-i/</guid><description>It was 11th Jan when I went to my gynecologist in emergency as
couldn&amp;rsquo;t feel the movements. After check-up she mentioned that if my
baby didn&amp;rsquo;t arrive anytime sooner than 15 she would have to perform an
induction. She didn&amp;rsquo;t wanted to take any risk at this stage because of
cervical incompetence and heart problem. So at last, we opted for
planned c-section on 17th Jan.
Night before took admission at MGM Belapur, Navi Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Feeling the Kicks</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-19-feeling-the-kicks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 04:48:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-19-feeling-the-kicks/</guid><description>Friends and near ones use to ask me quite often then - Do you feel the
movement?
No (use to be my reply).
Somewhere, I use to wonder how it feels like the movement of the baby
inside. It was tough to answer as first timer. On routine check -up my
doctor asked the same whether I feel the movement and I nodded in
negative. Immediately asked her how it actually feels.</description></item></channel></rss>