<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>letter on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/letter/</link><description>Recent content in letter on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 23:14:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/letter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Letter to my son</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 23:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</guid><description>Hello Aarush,
Today you are four months old&amp;hellip;though nothing remarkable but for me it
has been days now since we met last. Hope you to be fit as fiddle.
I came to know from your mom that now your vision is focused more or
less, you are trying to grasp objects; can bat and swipe at dangling
toys. It seems now you are ready to rock and roll as you have started
taking side turns with squirms, giggles and wails&amp;hellip; You respond to your
nani (granny) and aunt with big toothless smiles as well with coos and
making happy noises.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Second Titre De Sejour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</guid><description>On the 9th of April we were supposed to collect our new Titre De
Sejour (Long term VISA) from Cite Prefecture de Police. The interview
was fixed almost 3 months ago and we reached there before our scheduled
time to be make sure this time there is no big problem. But our turn
came around 4o&amp;rsquo;clock which is almost one hour behind our scheduled time.
And after checking all our paper she says oh!</description></item></channel></rss>