<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>north east on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/north-east/</link><description>Recent content in north east on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/north-east/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Majuli Part-I, Day-10 Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</guid><description>Somewhere on the internet once read the need for a vacation within a vacation. I know it sounds oxymoron but trust me when you are on the road for some time you need a day or two just doing nothing. Majuli was supposed to a magical place for us.
As we drove back west from Sivsagar we took the diversion to Nematighat, the boat embarkation point (ferry ghat) to go to Majuli.</description></item><item><title>Sivasagar, Day-9 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</guid><description>When I was planning this long trip to Assam I always wanted to drive all the way up to Dibrugarh where I studied till class 5. Later, in the final planning stage realized it was too long of a drive. Covering Guwahati, Shillong &amp;amp; Dibrugarh was getting too much in one trip so saved it for a later day. Sivasagar remained in the itinerary for a night stay with a condition if we finish Gibbon-Hollongapar and still have time to explore the ancient capital of the Ahom kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Hoollongapar Gibbon, Day-8 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</guid><description>Our trip to Hollong was one of the most challenging and memorable ones. Still, after so many months, it remains clear like yesterday. We slept early knowing we have to leave early. So when the alarm went off at 4 AM the whole place was quiet and dark. We hauled all our luggage from the room to the rented car. It was a bit of a task given that we were staying backside of the property.</description></item><item><title>Gibbon Hollongapar Wildlife - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</guid><description>Hollongapar GIBBON WILDLIFE SANCTUARY Hollong - the state tree of Aaasm. The story goes back like this when the British came and saw these long trees, they asked How Long? And it became Hollong Tree.
Just like &amp;ldquo;there is a brown crow&amp;rdquo; was a way to say Darwazabandh Karo (close the door in Hindi &amp;ndash; from Satyajit Ray&amp;rsquo;s Feludaa
It is only 20 sq KM of Sanctuary. Actually, it is the oldest miscellaneous plantation having Dipterocarpus and Mesua as dominant species It was declared a Reserve by the British way back in 1881, (53years after the advent of British rule) The original forests used to extend to the foothills of the Patkai mountain range.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga Part-II, Day-7 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>Our hotel Wild Grass was next to Central Zone. For the second day in Kaziranga, we supposed to have Elephants Safari in the morning. Now there are 2 places where you can have elephant safari. The central zone is very popular, is difficult to get, The counter opens at 7 PM in the evening prior and people line up for long, there is a priority to foreign tourist. Our hotel arranged for the Western Zone.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</guid><description>Kaziranga is one of the bigger National Park of India. It has three prominent zones - Central, Western and Eastern.
Central Range This drive covers the central region of the park. It is an ideal introduction to the park and its ecology as the route passes through the entire spectrum of habitat types prevalent in the Kaziranga area. (though Brahmaputra view is not available, a stretch of the route goes by the tributary river Difloo) There is a possibility of sighting elephants as well as the other big animals especially the swamp buffalo and of course the rhino.</description></item><item><title>North East 2018 planning</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</guid><description>Long prologue … someone once said&amp;hellip;
Happiness is to plan a trip to somewhere new with your loved one.
One best friend from Santanu’s engineering college got transferred from Bangalore to Shillong last year. In his send-off party, everyone committed that they would like to visit that part of the country. The friend in question is serving our country and he promised to be our host there while we visit Shillong, the Scotland of East and British summer capital of North East.</description></item></channel></rss>