<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spinach on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/spinach/</link><description>Recent content in Spinach on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/spinach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>Italian aroma…</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Daney Daney Pey likha hain khaney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo;- which
colloquially means each grain has the name of the person who will eat it
(it is the fortune of the person to have certain meal or not). Well the
same with more of spice in Hindi movies &amp;ldquo;goli goli pey likha hain
marney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo; which means in each bullets it is written the
name of the person who will die.</description></item></channel></rss>