<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>parking on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/parking/</link><description>Recent content in parking on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/parking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Perfect Parking</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</guid><description>Encountered this perfect parking on a small by-lane in Bangalore. For
sure I will not be able to park like this; normally have enough
difficulties in parallel parking on the street between cars. I was
failed (fatal) as rear tire touched the ramp in my first attempt to
secure Californian driving License. Looks like the owner will not be
change car as this is customized parking only which can accommodate
small car.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>Metro in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</guid><description>Living in Paris and not travelling in Metro has lots of demerits. Like
usual I am going to start with the traffic jams, one way roads,
unavailability of parking, high parking tickets and very unusual sense
of Parisian driving skills.
These only list if you have a car and travelling of your own. But what
about those who are taking other mode of smart transports like Bus,
Tram, Bicycle, Rollerblade or just walk to work or work from home?</description></item></channel></rss>