<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>drive on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/drive/</link><description>Recent content in drive on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/drive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Day - 2 Dehradun &amp; Haridwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</guid><description>We
work up fresh after a good sleep. But soon we realized we are in a place
which we are very not fond off. May be the Mussoorie did not blink with
us. After taking shower and getting ready for the day we went up to the
restaurant for breakfast. But looked like we were an early riser as
there were no one else and the place was not cleaned up for the day.</description></item><item><title>Day 1 - Drive to Mussoorie</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-06-20-day-1-drive-to-mussoorie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-06-20-day-1-drive-to-mussoorie/</guid><description>It
was a crazyweek,
as usual, it always happens that the week is very bad forwork, commute and
others just before we go onvacation and come back. So somehow we finished our packing on Thursday
night and set our alarms for early Friday.We
woke up on time and got ready and then call for Uber, the app shows the
taxi is just next to our apartment where normally few Uber/Ola always
are found.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>Linen anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid><description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the naming
convention it is Linen
Anniversary we have still
have a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek
(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. After
our wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>Deja Vu</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 21:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</guid><description>I am not sure if you happened to experience a very low probability
situation or event in life which you can compare with winnnig a
lottery or
getting struck by thunder. Statistically the second one has more chance.
To explain the same I take to you to recent past&amp;hellip;
I had that bizarre experience in the month on December while returning
from work took a
bus.
There was one gentleman very well groomed of dark complexion And I met
the same person next day (Saturday) in a different
bus
while going out.</description></item><item><title>add new administrator and management post for smartdashboard firewall-1</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-add-new-administrator-and-management-post-for-smartdashboard-firewall-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 22:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-add-new-administrator-and-management-post-for-smartdashboard-firewall-1/</guid><description>1.Add the user in the system password file for *nix it will be in
/etc/passwd and /etc/shadow 2. Add his host(PC) to /etc/hosts 3. Use cpconfig ( /opt/CPshrd-53/bin/) in case of Solaris Rest is menu driven</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Moved to Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</guid><description>After basking last 4 years in Bay Area we moved to Paris. The weather
was bleak cold which almost blew me off as we were getting in to the
TAXI at the airport. Reached hotel without problem, had a Chinese female
driver speaking English. Exhausted and tired to reach work which looked
like a 5 minutes walk from hotel on map. But, got lost in concrete
jungle of La Defense which is one of the unique place with
concentrated modern high-rise buildings in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>