<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>picture on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/picture/</link><description>Recent content in picture on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/picture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Our sleeping beauty</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</guid><description>Aarush never likes to sleep when ever we tried to tuck his hands&amp;hellip;.I
mean with buritto wrap. If wrapped he keeps on moving his hands in
discomfort until he is unwrapped. He always loves to have his hands
free, outstretched in upward direction. This series of pictures which
were taken during half an hour cat&amp;rsquo;s nap. So many positions for two
little hands :D</description></item><item><title>Letter to my son</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 23:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</guid><description>Hello Aarush,
Today you are four months old&amp;hellip;though nothing remarkable but for me it
has been days now since we met last. Hope you to be fit as fiddle.
I came to know from your mom that now your vision is focused more or
less, you are trying to grasp objects; can bat and swipe at dangling
toys. It seems now you are ready to rock and roll as you have started
taking side turns with squirms, giggles and wails&amp;hellip; You respond to your
nani (granny) and aunt with big toothless smiles as well with coos and
making happy noises.</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>An announcement</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 01:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</guid><description>This announcement was long due on our blog. Though this breaking news
was shared on d-day instantly with friends and families from Hospital
via SMS and emails. I specifically carried my camera, laptop and
wireless data card for the same.
I created two announcement cards one in pink and other in blue with two
names (for girl and boy) and kept them ready. We never disclosed this
big-news in last few months in our blog in-fact it was kept secret to
many except close family members and few friends.</description></item><item><title>An afteroon at Pisa</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</guid><description>Being exhausted from last evening we got up bit late and had very good
breakfast before hitting the road. According to our itinerary, distance
to be covered was long one as our hotel was booked at Florence.
We took train to La Spezia, it was a crowded, got packed with each
passing stations of Cinque Terre but became empty as soon as we
crossed Riomaggiore. We had to wait a bit at La Spezia as train was
coming from north was late.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Playing with shutter speed</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 18:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</guid><description>Love taking pictures with long shutter speed at night - technique is
very simple. All I needed was a tripod to secure camera from shaking
while leaving the camera shutter open. I know this is not a great
picture but that is what I got from my balcony. A better one with
Kharghar landmark Utsav Chowk is posted
here.</description></item><item><title>Sunsets in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 21:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Sunset with blue sky of late October seems “magnifique” along with open
space of Navi Mumbai as viewed from local train (picture taken through
window)
This one I clicked last Saturday when I was stuck in middle of JJ
Flyover - the longest flyover in Mumbai (2.3 KM). It is constructed like
a snake, which makes its way through labyrinth of old buildings on
either side; basically you bypass the busy, crowded market underneath.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Bombay International Airport</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid><description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far as
my International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is getting
better and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the pictures
for the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictures
looks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may be
not …quality wise.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-20-celebrations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-20-celebrations/</guid><description>Looking at those plastic chairs brought back my memories of
Anandamela (a Bengali
children magazine - published fortnight. They used to have picture of
common objects in obscure way and you have to identify the same. I know
this picture is a far cry from those -any way some sweet memories to
reflect upon from fourth floor while taking this picture.
In India celebration is part of life whether big or small ones.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</guid><description>This picture was taken from my phone camera when I went to do our weekly
vegetable shopping in APMC [Agro Product Market] close to Vashi.
Prices for every vegetables went up. Due to lack of infrastructure it
was a shame to see so much wastage due to heavy rain. From the posture
of the seller it was quite clear he was not looking for lot of customers
as he stretches his back.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>China rose</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid><description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soul
into. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit if
they fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,
the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No one
wants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Adios</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 05:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</guid><description>Last day, woke up very early in the morning to visit Candolim, Sinquerim
beach- Just to avoid scorching heat of sun. The shimmering sea stretches
to the horizon. Spent some time to savour the view then headed to Fort
Aguada. Fort Agauda crowns the rocky flattened headland at the end of
the beach. Constructed in 1612 to protect the northern shores of Mandovi
estuary from Dutch and Maratha raiders. It was a reference point for the
vessels coming from Europe at that time.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid><description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arranged
for two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. We
opted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in a
non-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary included
Dona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilica
and se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurga
dedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit to
Ancestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description></item><item><title>Little Visitor at Office Window</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 22:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</guid><description>Friday again, I am already at work for last nine hours(reached around
8ish). Wow! that&amp;rsquo;s lot and time to head towards home soon.
Today, after lots of failure attempt I some how succeeded to capture a
very cute visitor at my window. I have no idea what kind of bird is
this, going to ask one expert for the same. Well, Pamela is working very
hard to upload pictures from Goa and writing trip details – hope this
weekend we upload them.</description></item><item><title>Mera Bharat Jawaan</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 22:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</guid><description>Another funny advertisement which caught my attention Budda Hoga Tera
Baap. This is a soft or hard slang depending on your view - &amp;ldquo;May be
your father is old&amp;rdquo; This new TV series name is &amp;ldquo;Mera Bharat
Jaawan&amp;rdquo; which translates into &amp;ldquo;My India is Young&amp;rdquo;. With one fourth
population under the age of 25 India definitely has young demography.
P.S - In last two months, I have changed theme for wordpress (blog) at
least four times.</description></item><item><title>Micro$oft Launch @ Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</guid><description>Micro$oft is doing a round of business and technical launch show around
India. The products are Exchange 2007, Office 2007 and Vista. I attended
only a brief session @ Hyatt.
Well, somehow my name was not there even though I registered 10 days
before the event.
And my business card with orange and blue dots did not help much to get
attention from those desk people. Anyway, it was solid 40 minutes of
work for me – replied emails, chat with business contact got updates
from their team – thanks to CDMA mobile card.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>New Gadget K790i</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</guid><description>Well I got
it. After
lots of deliberation I upgraded my choice to K790 from K750. The big
difference is price and features to say in simple words. I heard in
recent time James Bond used this same phone in his last
movie. Not sure what all other
accessories Mr.Q
added for him on the film.
I wanted to buy a camera phone as that will be handy to capture events.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>Pardey key Pichey</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</guid><description>From a good friend of mine I got an offer to help at backstage of Ritu
Beri’s fashion show to be held at Paris on 5th July at Lido. At
first I wanted to deny this proposal but with second thought that it
might be a fun with friends to be there; I nodded my head giving my
approval. Ace fashion designer Ritu Beri is the first Asian to have
joined a French fashion house making a slow transition from Indian Haute
Couture to Prêt-a-porter (ready to wear).</description></item><item><title>Swiss-Itenary, TGV and Gizmo</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 09:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</guid><description>Another
Friday, thinking to write something for my blog ;) I think I should have
kept a track of my Friday bloging or changes I made on Friday :D. Well,
this post is not going to be about Friday but it is about our
Switzerland itinerary, experience with TGV etc.
Might have noticed there are lots of posts by Pamela in recent time –
wish she would have done before from our other trips also.</description></item><item><title>Italian aroma…</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Daney Daney Pey likha hain khaney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo;- which
colloquially means each grain has the name of the person who will eat it
(it is the fortune of the person to have certain meal or not). Well the
same with more of spice in Hindi movies &amp;ldquo;goli goli pey likha hain
marney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo; which means in each bullets it is written the
name of the person who will die.</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>Shhh …. Silence Please</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</guid><description>Normally, I and Santanu don&amp;rsquo;t talk to each other on bus, train, flight
or whatsoever as we are normally lost in our own world and both try to
respect each others silence. We have books, newspaper, ipod for that
time but this particular evening we happened to talk so much while
returning to Zurich from Luzern. One of the reason maybe that by now we
are kind of used to watching beautiful sceneries from train as it runs
along lakes, rivers and creaking sometimes as it passes by the running
hills unfolding before us.</description></item><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;quot; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item><item><title>Bike Route</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-23-bike-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 17:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-23-bike-route/</guid><description>Just uploaded few
pictures from my
bike route as promised in earlier
post. There is a
movie which I tried to shoot while riding with my digital camera (which
is quite old now). Last weekend was very rainy and stormy so being at
home tried MPG4 and QuickTime. MOV version is around 7 MB but the
quality is so so while QuickTime version of the same is big around 26MB
with better quality.</description></item><item><title>Deja Vu</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 21:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</guid><description>I am not sure if you happened to experience a very low probability
situation or event in life which you can compare with winnnig a
lottery or
getting struck by thunder. Statistically the second one has more chance.
To explain the same I take to you to recent past&amp;hellip;
I had that bizarre experience in the month on December while returning
from work took a
bus.
There was one gentleman very well groomed of dark complexion And I met
the same person next day (Saturday) in a different
bus
while going out.</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item><item><title>Home Network ADSL-Network-Phone</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</guid><description>I just wanted to share my home network. It is not a state of
technologies with the latest &amp;amp; greatest wireless or wired network with
complex router and switches. I did it in old school way with a single
long CAT5 Ethernet Cable. I have a FreeBox which is an ADSL2 router
connecting to the main phone jack. The output from the
FreeBox connects my PC, Television and
Phone. Now all these components are connected with the single wire as
I mentioned before.</description></item><item><title>Place de la Concorde</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-30-place-de-la-concorde/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2005 21:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-30-place-de-la-concorde/</guid><description>After a long time I was able to
capture the fountain of Place de la Concordein a very beautiful sunny morning. It is
so amazing that we still take pictures of Paris like tourist on their
first day. When we left home it was cloudy and we were questioning
ourselves why we are carrying the camera with us. But luckily it was
worth to do so. Then from there we took a small promenade at the garden
of Elysee.</description></item><item><title>Gallery2</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-29-gallery2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2005 20:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-29-gallery2/</guid><description>Well I am having lots of trouble with a simple gallery2 installation
with 15 pictures for my wife&amp;rsquo;s hobby pictures. While I am running a 1600
picture gallery on the same server with out any problem touch wood. The
back on the main one not there.
And i am having wonderful tech support from dot5 hosting to say the
least. The guy does not even know what is Unix he replies it is
FreeBSD.</description></item><item><title>New look to web site</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2005 03:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</guid><description>Migrated to Wordpress along with
Gallery2, the choice for the same was not
easy. As for a long time Mambo and custom
home grown Photo Album was doing the job fine. In fact the template I
used for the same was appreciated by friends. But as days passed and
numbers of pictures are growing it was getting difficult to manage the
same with custom gallery. But the idea to grab Wordpress and dropping
Mambo is a personal one.</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 18:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</guid><description>When I was on my vacation last week in Spain and Portugal, was thinking
about to write down all that we had experienced there - the places we
visted and food we tasted and others. But back to work it is such a
Dilbert place that I can not explain with my logic.
Also I need to find a cheap solution to restore pictures from Smart
Media. It looks like there is a well suited option commercial for 40
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Lost Pictures Recovered</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 18:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</guid><description>After discovering that one of the SmartMedia Card from my Camera not
working at Seville we were really very heart broken and anxious. It had
pictures from our first three days of our trip. And in those first three
days we traveled from Madrid to Granada. We had captured lots of evening
pictures in Madrid and sunset view of Alhambra at Granada.
But we kept our nerve cool and continued with other media cards and
tried our best not to remember about the same.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Bonjour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-17-bonjour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-17-bonjour/</guid><description>After a long time I changed the theme of my web site; hope the color
combination looks good. The two templates are &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;zen&amp;rsquo;.
There are now more than 1300 pictures to checkout in the Photo Album
section. Most of them come from last 3 years as that is how old my
digital camera is. And a big section comes from Europe. After moving to
Paris, we used this opportunity to visit maximum countries possible
which are part of Schengen visa.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2004 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</guid><description>Happy Holidays!!! Well year 2004 is almost over; wish you all the best for the year 2005
and next. This year we did not traveled like last year. But we did
traveled to Italy and Greece for one week each, other than some of few
short trips. You will find them in pictures for 2004.
In the month of November we framed few pictures and cross-stitch work of
Pamela. Here are the pictures of the same.</description></item><item><title>Chateau de Versailles</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-11-12-chateau-de-versailles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2004 10:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-11-12-chateau-de-versailles/</guid><description>I have a fascination for the colour of autumn, mat be the reason is I
never experienced them before while in India and California. You can
enjoy the same in Paris where trees along the big boulevards changes it
colour. Around Paris particularly the Bois de Boulogne is very nice that
time. We went to Versailles just to take pictures. It was not a very
sunny day that Sunday, sun was playing around clouds.</description></item><item><title>Paris in night mode</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 20:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</guid><description>I wanted to take pictures of Paris famous landmarks in the twilight with
a tripod. We started with Sacre-coeur Basilica. And the picture we got
from there was really great as we were there on the right time. The sky
color was perfect for the camera and it was just lighted.
From there we went to Moulin-Rouge; the famous cabaret of Paris then to
Assembly National the French Parliament. We crossed Seine and came to
Concord.</description></item><item><title>Musee Guimet</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-12-musee-guimet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 09:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-12-musee-guimet/</guid><description>This Museum is an extension of Louvre Museum-collection of objects from
Asia. Mostly the objects are from south Asia and far east Asia, if you
been to London British Museum and visited Asian sections you will feel
deja vu. It is located in 16th arrondissement of Paris next to Metro
Station of Iena.
We visited the same with Francois; it was only Francois who told us
about this museum. He had been here before few times.</description></item><item><title>Itlay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 12:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</guid><description>We have been to Rome for 4 days in 2003 but we wanted to visit the other
parts of Italy but could not do that due to time constrain. We were
planning for trip to Florence, Venice etc old classic route for long
time.
Krovi and Vidya went to Italy on their paper honeymoon which was 3
weeks earlier than us and they did provided us with lots of good tips.</description></item><item><title>Back from vacation</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 04:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</guid><description>Back to Paris after a nice and quick vacation of 4 weeks from India. The
days passed by very quickly between meals and sleep. Our vacation got
split between my parents and in-law&amp;rsquo;s house. But it was great to spent
time with family. Will post some new pictures and others later. Paris is
very beautifully decorated for holidays, it is a great sight to see all
those big trees along the road being lighted up, as they don&amp;rsquo;t have any
leaf now.</description></item><item><title>Picnic with Ritu</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</guid><description>It has been a long time we were exchanging e-mails and phone calls with
Ritu, but could not meet her in-person. She is a friend of Akiko&amp;rsquo;s Paris
friend. A long chain; but a start to make social contacts in new place.
I am personally not that social to make friends at party or other social
gatherings that is one reason holding me to join local Expats club.Ritu
arranged a great picnic and was very nice to meet all other expaticians.</description></item><item><title>Tour Effiel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</guid><description>It was a bright and bleak winter day, we headed straight to the number
one attraction of Paris or Europe as you might say. A great view; this
picture was taken by a Japanese tourist. There were lots of people from
Indian sub-continent selling momento of Eiffel Tower for cheap. But we
left after a while, as it was too cold and windy that day to go at the
top of tower.</description></item><item><title>Cameras,Rolls,Photos and Albums</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2002-05-21-cameras-rolls-photos-and-albums/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2002 14:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2002-05-21-cameras-rolls-photos-and-albums/</guid><description>Most of my Web Site is dedicated to photography. In fact, the very
thought of sharing pictures has changed with internet. I like to see
pictures in-print myself. But when you have friends half way accross the
globe, internet is your best friend.The pictures in these albums are
taken by three different cameras. The first camera I had a Pentax. Now I
have a Nikon N-80 and recently bought a Digital camera from Olympus.</description></item></channel></rss>