<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>forest on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/forest/</link><description>Recent content in forest on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:27:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/forest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hoollongapar Gibbon, Day-8 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</guid><description>Our trip to Hollong was one of the most challenging and memorable ones. Still, after so many months, it remains clear like yesterday. We slept early knowing we have to leave early. So when the alarm went off at 4 AM the whole place was quiet and dark. We hauled all our luggage from the room to the rented car. It was a bit of a task given that we were staying backside of the property.</description></item><item><title>Gibbon Hollongapar Wildlife - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</guid><description>Hollongapar GIBBON WILDLIFE SANCTUARY Hollong - the state tree of Aaasm. The story goes back like this when the British came and saw these long trees, they asked How Long? And it became Hollong Tree.
Just like &amp;ldquo;there is a brown crow&amp;rdquo; was a way to say Darwazabandh Karo (close the door in Hindi &amp;ndash; from Satyajit Ray&amp;rsquo;s Feludaa
It is only 20 sq KM of Sanctuary. Actually, it is the oldest miscellaneous plantation having Dipterocarpus and Mesua as dominant species It was declared a Reserve by the British way back in 1881, (53years after the advent of British rule) The original forests used to extend to the foothills of the Patkai mountain range.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga Part-II, Day-7 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>Our hotel Wild Grass was next to Central Zone. For the second day in Kaziranga, we supposed to have Elephants Safari in the morning. Now there are 2 places where you can have elephant safari. The central zone is very popular, is difficult to get, The counter opens at 7 PM in the evening prior and people line up for long, there is a priority to foreign tourist. Our hotel arranged for the Western Zone.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</guid><description>Kaziranga is one of the bigger National Park of India. It has three prominent zones - Central, Western and Eastern.
Central Range This drive covers the central region of the park. It is an ideal introduction to the park and its ecology as the route passes through the entire spectrum of habitat types prevalent in the Kaziranga area. (though Brahmaputra view is not available, a stretch of the route goes by the tributary river Difloo) There is a possibility of sighting elephants as well as the other big animals especially the swamp buffalo and of course the rhino.</description></item><item><title>Visit to hungry tide- Sunderban</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 20:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</guid><description>For the first time in my life I spent more than 2 nights in a row at
Calcutta. The initial plan was to attend Papai’s wedding reception and
travel to some where around like Digha and back to Bangalore. We got our
Bangalore – Calcutta ticket booked. Going was by train to save money and
return was on flight so that we save time &amp;amp; energy before getting back
to our daily routine.</description></item></channel></rss>