<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ATM on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/atm/</link><description>Recent content in ATM on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 15:32:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/atm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Theme</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-13-free-theme/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 15:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-13-free-theme/</guid><description>I just found out d-atmosphere.com is holding a competition where they
are offering a free wordpress theme called WP
Remix. It’s a very nice theme with loads
of features.
The rule is simple - just write about the competition in your blog and
post your link back in the comments on the contest page.
The winner will be announced on March 1st.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item><item><title>Second Titre De Sejour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</guid><description>On the 9th of April we were supposed to collect our new Titre De
Sejour (Long term VISA) from Cite Prefecture de Police. The interview
was fixed almost 3 months ago and we reached there before our scheduled
time to be make sure this time there is no big problem. But our turn
came around 4o&amp;rsquo;clock which is almost one hour behind our scheduled time.
And after checking all our paper she says oh!</description></item></channel></rss>