<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mumbai on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/mumbai/</link><description>Recent content in mumbai on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/mumbai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goodbye – Mumbai – a quick update</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</guid><description>I
did not want to use a title like “Welcome to Bangalore” or “Here I
come to Bangaloru” on purpose as need some time before I can call this
my new home. From long time we were knowing that we have to move to
Banglore but on personal grounds I had to postpone it which was readily
accepted by my company. In recent months, I was waiting for that green
signal from my company that I have to move in any case.</description></item><item><title>Shiv Jayanti</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid><description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night of
lord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindu
mythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birth
anniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17th
century fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He was
named Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabai
had prayed for a son.</description></item><item><title>Geography - mismatch</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 05:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</guid><description>For any fifth grader Mumbai is located in Western part of India if asked
north or south answer will be south. So how can there be a church of
North India which is located in posh south Mumbai in a stone throw
distance from famous Flora Fountain? You may wonder - in the world of
bharat-todo (Break India by new politicians) how all bhaia&amp;rsquo;s(people from
North India Bihar and Uttarpradesh - speaking Hindi) suddenly built a
church for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Playing with shutter speed</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 18:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</guid><description>Love taking pictures with long shutter speed at night - technique is
very simple. All I needed was a tripod to secure camera from shaking
while leaving the camera shutter open. I know this is not a great
picture but that is what I got from my balcony. A better one with
Kharghar landmark Utsav Chowk is posted
here.</description></item><item><title>Sunsets in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 21:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Sunset with blue sky of late October seems “magnifique” along with open
space of Navi Mumbai as viewed from local train (picture taken through
window)
This one I clicked last Saturday when I was stuck in middle of JJ
Flyover - the longest flyover in Mumbai (2.3 KM). It is constructed like
a snake, which makes its way through labyrinth of old buildings on
either side; basically you bypass the busy, crowded market underneath.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Thread of love</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</guid><description>It is a celebration of unconditional love between brother and sister in
Hindu culture. This age old celebration tries to remind us of the
beautiful and unique relationship between brother and sister celebrated
since time immemorial. Sisters tie sacred threads on brothers wrist
asking for longer &amp;amp; healthy life of brother and brothers in-turn vow to
protect (to save her- Raksha) their sisters from any unpleasant
situations of life on this day.</description></item><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>Bombay International Airport</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid><description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far as
my International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is getting
better and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the pictures
for the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictures
looks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may be
not …quality wise.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</guid><description>Looking at those plastic chairs brought back my memories of
Anandamela (a Bengali
children magazine - published fortnight. They used to have picture of
common objects in obscure way and you have to identify the same. I know
this picture is a far cry from those -any way some sweet memories to
reflect upon from fourth floor while taking this picture.
In India celebration is part of life whether big or small ones.</description></item><item><title>Cart in city road</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 21:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</guid><description>While coming to work this morning oxen (castrated male) cart
carrying sugar canes caught my attention. It is not a common site to see
a bullock cart or hand pulled cart (pulled or pushed by a man) at the
heart of Mumbai city next to VT Station.
They are not allowed in the main roads of the city but can only move in
the peripheral roads of the city. These kinds of slow moving objects
cause most notorious traffic jam in India.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Courtesy still … in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-31-courtesy-still-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 04:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-31-courtesy-still-in-mumbai/</guid><description>With all its busy, speedy life I found courtesy still existing within in
Mumbai-local; an unexpected encounter with refined human behavior in
this Maximum city. I was retuning home in a local train and lucky to be
seated as I started from VT terminus. In the mid way a family of three
boarded the train; it is quite out of the way for a female passenger to
get into general or male compartment at the rush hour.</description></item><item><title>China rose</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid><description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soul
into. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit if
they fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,
the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No one
wants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description></item><item><title>Mumbaiya Lingo</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 03:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</guid><description>While boarding a train I heard one co-passenger saying to another
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” which astonished me for a fraction of
second as its not at all palatable to an untrained ears. It seems this
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” is considered far more effective while getting
into locals then long winded formal request to the people ahead to make
way.
I was trying hard to relate as it sounds hindi but actually its not.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 18:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</guid><description>Another view of Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s Ballard Pier from my desk. May be I am too busy
between meetings so no time to romance with my valentine. Well, heart
shape balloons floating around our office here and there reminding me of
the special day. Due to meetings and tight schedule I even missed the
chocolate distribution. C&amp;rsquo;est dommage!!! :( . Although enormous
work-pressure but many thoughts are coming across to make evening
better.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Micro$oft Launch @ Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</guid><description>Micro$oft is doing a round of business and technical launch show around
India. The products are Exchange 2007, Office 2007 and Vista. I attended
only a brief session @ Hyatt.
Well, somehow my name was not there even though I registered 10 days
before the event.
And my business card with orange and blue dots did not help much to get
attention from those desk people. Anyway, it was solid 40 minutes of
work for me – replied emails, chat with business contact got updates
from their team – thanks to CDMA mobile card.</description></item><item><title>Travel Under Terror</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 00:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</guid><description>There were massive bomb blasts last summer in Mumbai local trains. After
that now there are constant reminders for the commuters to be on alert
and check their surroundings. It is logistical nightmare to manage the
massive number of commuters who takes train every day in Mumbai. In
simple words, “impossible” will be closest word I can pick.
Few months back after lots of planning and public announcement Mumbai
Police conducted a security drill where every passenger was supposed to
pass via metal detector in two Main Terminus in the evening but after
few moments it was clear that police can not handle the stream of
passengers in lakhs and crores as they were heading home and it was
abandoned.</description></item><item><title>New Gadget K790i</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</guid><description>Well I got
it. After
lots of deliberation I upgraded my choice to K790 from K750. The big
difference is price and features to say in simple words. I heard in
recent time James Bond used this same phone in his last
movie. Not sure what all other
accessories Mr.Q
added for him on the film.
I wanted to buy a camera phone as that will be handy to capture events.</description></item><item><title>Linen anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid><description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the naming
convention it is Linen
Anniversary we have still
have a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek
(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. After
our wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description></item><item><title>Local trains of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</guid><description>After moving to Mumbai (India) commuting from one place to another was a
big problem (as we didn’t have our own vehicle). It seems Mumbai local
trains are the most efficient one carrying millions of people everyday.
Getting in and out of local trains is one of the hardest tasks
particularly during rush hours which every mumbains has to undergo at
least ones in their life. So, lot of advice was given from Santanu’s
maternal family who are staying here for more than 15 years.</description></item><item><title>Durga Puja</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-23-durga-puja/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2006 23:23:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-23-durga-puja/</guid><description>Durga Puja is the most important and biggest festival in Bengal for any
Bengali Hindu. Its five days of festivity where this Puja symbolizes
good winning over evil. Maa Durga is considered as daughter of Bengalis.
It is believed that every year she comes to visit her father’s home
(earth) for five days with her four children - Kartik, Ganesh, Saraswati
and Lakshmi- representing respectively the Protector, the Initiator of
the puja, Knowledge and the Provider - signifies the complete
manifestation of the goddess.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Shan &amp; Pam-The Perfect Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2002 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</guid><description>It was the 27thApril 02 &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:green;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;evening,
Every thing was geared up for the Mumbai &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;meeting,
Our “Rosy” flower, made “&amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#ff9900;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;Shan” like a bee &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993300;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;humming,
Not showing outside, Pam thought it was her prince &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993366;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;charming,
Santanu was convinced it was the end of his &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:fuchsia;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;findings,
Gandhiji was nervously smiling,
Shan’s mother in law thought it was perfectly &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;matching,
Pam’s mother and father in law were unable to hide the &amp;lt;span</description></item></channel></rss>