<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>curd on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/curd/</link><description>Recent content in curd on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/curd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item></channel></rss>