<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travel on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/travel/</link><description>Recent content in Travel on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 18:34:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Day 3 - Rishikesh</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</guid><description>The
weather looked gloomy with an overcast sky as we woke up. We had
breakfast at the hotel and decided to visit Rishikesh today. Again we
headed back the way we came yesterday and after crossing Rajaji National
Park the road divides and one goes towards to Dehradun and one to
Rishikesh. The drive was pleasant, as we opted Laxman Jhula as our
destination google map smartly took us via highway bypassing the main
city.</description></item><item><title>Uttarakhand - prelude</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</guid><description>*It
has been such a long time that we posted something we almost forgot how
to type long paragraphs. Maybe all due to Facebook and WhatsApp which is
instant but then in when you look back you have no way to figure out
what all the noise was about. Well enough of rant now let me
type….*Beginning
of 2017 we were very much looking for a vacation and Pamela was
interested in Uttarakhand.</description></item><item><title>Cochin Full Marathon 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 15:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</guid><description>Pre-Race Day
The day started early, we get out Cochin Club today and part our our
ways for some time. While Pamela &amp;amp; Aarush goes back to Bangalore on
Saturday itself I stay back for the big run on Sunday.
They had a train to catch around 9 from ERS. There was not a single auto
around so had to walk and get one from Ferry station and as usual the
price asked and agreed is way more than normal,</description></item><item><title>Gujarat 2011 - Map</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 14:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</guid><description>Need to write the 4 years old road trip before my memory fades away. The
pictures
are there to help but need lots of coffee to complete the writing.
Our itinerary to khushbu Gujarat ki
Day -1 By flight Bangalore- Bombay. We took a morning flight
for Mumbai and reached around afternoon. Same day boarded train to
Baroda from Mumbai Central. Reached Baroda by night around 9. It was
a chair car train.</description></item><item><title>Half early update</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 12:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</guid><description>So just before school reopens we had out of Bangalore for 2 nights. We
opted for something closer to home Coorg but on the southern side. We
opted for this side as we been to more popular side near Madikeri in
2008 when Aarush was around 9 month old. Time do really fly.
We started at 8:30 from home, very late compared to our slandered but
that day had Bangalore TCS 10K.</description></item><item><title>1st class sleeper</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-15-1st-class-sleeper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 21:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-15-1st-class-sleeper/</guid><description>It was a dream from a long time to travel in 1stclass in
Indian Railway. The last time I traveled in 1stclass was
early 1985 when we went to Puri ( a must stop for Bengali
).
So when the dates for summer vacation became clear started booking for
train tickets. It was month of December when we booked ticked for April.
Wanted to book 2ndAC ticket but to my surprise it was
already sold out so opted for AC 1stClass.</description></item><item><title>Vote for us The Great Driving Challenge !!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 05:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</guid><description>We are inviting you to post your vote in support of travel. Visit our
application page by clicking on this link here.
Cast your vote and support
us.
This is our great grand escape plan
View GDC -
NH17
in a larger map</description></item><item><title>Le vol</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 09:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</guid><description>I am not a person who hates flying to start with as my major air-travel
in recent years was visiting India on holiday from Europe. Like all
other events in life this can be looked at like a coin; on one side the
travel time has reduced significantly while on other side only 20 to 30
kilos of baggage allowed compared to California (65 Kilo).
As we were moving out of Paris we had lot of important things to bring
along with us that we will need till our shipment arrives in next 5
weeks time.</description></item><item><title>Uncertain Voyage</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 19:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</guid><description>After traveling to so many places in Europe in last three years now we
were thinking to travel to some other part of globe which can be easily
reached from Paris within few hours maybe somewhere in North African.
The very thought came was how about going to Morocco or Egypt but none
of them was perfect weather wise to visit. Then also after too much of
thinking we settled for Morocco and started to gather touristic
information.</description></item><item><title>Uddan - Flight</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid><description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing its
publicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in the
world. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouraged
us to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar covering
around 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooth
though they were very strict about luggage weight.
In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough leg
room; quality of the food was better than what we had before and was
good with choice of films and music on demand.</description></item><item><title>Vacation on the horizon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid><description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)
when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard of
travelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May be
it is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visit
some country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not at
all interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Paris
cold all the time.</description></item><item><title>Bonjour</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</guid><description>After a long time I changed the theme of my web site; hope the color
combination looks good. The two templates are &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;zen&amp;rsquo;.
There are now more than 1300 pictures to checkout in the Photo Album
section. Most of them come from last 3 years as that is how old my
digital camera is. And a big section comes from Europe. After moving to
Paris, we used this opportunity to visit maximum countries possible
which are part of Schengen visa.</description></item><item><title>Summer 2002</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-08-10-summer-2002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2002 13:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-08-10-summer-2002/</guid><description>Summer of 2002 was a great summer. I did lots of travelling. Thanks to
Tanujoy and Atul for the same. With Atul and I went to Utah for 4 day
trip in July, it was just great!. We visited four national parks and
travelled through very scenic highways.
I went to Yosemite few times for hiking and climbing with members of
PGVIP and with other friends as well.</description></item></channel></rss>