<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sale on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/sale/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sale on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 17:46:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/sale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sale</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</guid>
      <description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letterswords this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Dayweekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekendbrings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increaseswith advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you getconstant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you driveyour car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid>
      <description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperativeif you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedombut can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggledat least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activafor Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get goodprice). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim tovisit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metro in Paris</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</guid>
      <description>Living in Paris and not travelling in Metro has lots of demerits. Likeusual I am going to start with the traffic jams, one way roads,unavailability of parking, high parking tickets and very unusual senseof Parisian driving skills.
These only list if you have a car and travelling of your own. But whatabout those who are taking other mode of smart transports like Bus,Tram, Bicycle, Rollerblade or just walk to work or work from home?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>