<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airtel Hyderabad Marathon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/airtel-hyderabad-marathon/</link><description>Recent content in Airtel Hyderabad Marathon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 10:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/airtel-hyderabad-marathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>43 seconds and counting</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 10:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</guid><description>Third year in a row ran Airtel Hyderabad half
marathon yesterday. There was many
things which were different from 2013. Looking back 2013 was my second
outstation race with PaceMakers. We
traveled in train and return journey was not a great one as we had to
travel in sleeper class. The fun was most of us did not had bed linen as
we forgot how it was to travel in sleeper class.</description></item><item><title>Airtel Hyderabad Half Marathon 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</guid><description>After Chennai DRHM event the event I signed up for was Airtel Hyderabad
Half Marathon. This run is little special to me as received my first
ever finisher T-shirt last year as a proof of my improvement in running.
Also there is the big culinary charm of Dine-hill and Karachi biscuits
as post run celebration.
Booked myself a return flight as soon as the dates for AHM 2014 was out.</description></item><item><title>Blessed</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-28-blessed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 03:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-28-blessed/</guid><description>Blessing is a simple word, but yesterday night (Monday) just before
sleeping I was thinking about the same again and again. Wished for a
gadget to record my thought as I was too tired to use any keyboard or
voice recorder. At times we wonder and sometime make fun of those award
ceremonies where people on the stage keep on thanking people around him
or her and sometimes even their dogs.</description></item></channel></rss>