<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carrefour on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/carrefour/</link><description>Recent content in Carrefour on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 11:52:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/carrefour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sleepy Monday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 11:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</guid><description>Monday morning mother-son woke up pretty late. Santanu already left for
office while we were in sleep. Around noon we went out of hotel to
nearby mall. Today I was not much interested in exploring rather looking
for kids activities. Spent almost half day at Toys R Us play area in
Paragon mall where Aarush enjoyed to fullest. He did not want to
give-up the car and was seating there for hours.</description></item><item><title>Friday - Black Peper Crab</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</guid><description>On Friday we woke up early; had
breakfast- an elaborate one. Me and Aarush after shower around 11am left
our hotel room. Today again we walked on other side of Orchard
Streettill Dhoby Ghat Station. Now
a days; I too feel sick like my hubby when too much time spent at malls
… am I growing old ? :D It was good to be in mall when it is raining.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item></channel></rss>