<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weekend on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/weekend/</link><description>Recent content in weekend on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:52:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/weekend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Drive to heritage site - Lepakshi</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</guid><description>My 1st term is coming to an end and we are given the upcoming test as
well project submission dates. On reaching home from class on Saturday I
was desperate to go out of Bangalore to get charged to combat the
upcoming gruelling weeks at work and personal front with study. I had no
clue where to go for a day and started to check my faithful websites and
zeroed on Lepakshi from Anita’s
site.</description></item><item><title>chocolate Banana Muffins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</guid><description>First weekend of December past with lots of activities - a trip to
commercial street, malls and office. On Saturday Aarush forced me to
leave bed early - deprived me of extended sleeping on the weekend. After
that I was busy with him mostly for breakfast. Nowadays he has developed
a nasty habit of prolonged (around an hour or more) eating times be it
breakfast, lunch or dinner. After that he played for while but soon he
was sleepy for nap.</description></item><item><title>Whatz FRESH about Reliance Fresh ?</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</guid><description>As we are new to Bangalore trying to explore all nearby hypermarket,
supermarket and open markets as we settle in. This is also giving us as
chance to explore places around. The first one we tried and explored was
BIG-BAZAR on Old Madras road. As it is just near to one of our
office address in Bangalore I knew how to reach there without being
lost. Then weekend after we tried SPAR at Kormongala followed by
Nilgiris.</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Hebbal Lake</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid><description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress on
construction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as at
work things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is a
nice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes a
happy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in next
month this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that is
going to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid><description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I got
opportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, I
couldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarried
Indian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as an
escort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered like
friend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description></item><item><title>Little Visitor at Office Window</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 22:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</guid><description>Friday again, I am already at work for last nine hours(reached around
8ish). Wow! that&amp;rsquo;s lot and time to head towards home soon.
Today, after lots of failure attempt I some how succeeded to capture a
very cute visitor at my window. I have no idea what kind of bird is
this, going to ask one expert for the same. Well, Pamela is working very
hard to upload pictures from Goa and writing trip details – hope this
weekend we upload them.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Green plate</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</guid><description>In
my salad days I used to hate many green veggies and I remember when maa
used to scold me for the same. Somehow I didn’t had taste for them at
that point of time but gradually I developed the taste so much so that I
can now survive happily on those green things (cow-food).
From long time Santanu wanted to make a change on our meal as it seems
we both are putting on weight.</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>Bike Route</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-23-bike-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 17:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-23-bike-route/</guid><description>Just uploaded few
pictures from my
bike route as promised in earlier
post. There is a
movie which I tried to shoot while riding with my digital camera (which
is quite old now). Last weekend was very rainy and stormy so being at
home tried MPG4 and QuickTime. MOV version is around 7 MB but the
quality is so so while QuickTime version of the same is big around 26MB
with better quality.</description></item><item><title>Friday 12th May</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 15:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</guid><description>Just another weekend of May in Paris. I don&amp;rsquo;t know any other time when
the weather can be so beautiful with clear sky and warm temperature.
Right now, all the horse chestnut
trees along wide
boulevards are full of white flowers. This tree is also known as
Marronier d&amp;rsquo;Inde, thanks to Francois for introducing the same.
Truly, if one cheers up and forgets all the problems round him-it is a
romantic experience in itself.</description></item><item><title>Back to Mordor</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-20-back-to-mordor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 09:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-20-back-to-mordor/</guid><description>Well it has been a long time I bloged. I am back to Paris; Pamela will
join me in a month time. The title of the post could not be better as I
am missing the sun after returning from India. I like rain after very
hot summer or sunny days with cool breeze. I really can not take those
dark cloudy days which makes me feel gloomy. As looking out of my window
can&amp;rsquo;t even make out is it 11 AM or 3 PM.</description></item><item><title>Loire Valley</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-11-22-loire-valley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2004 20:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-11-22-loire-valley/</guid><description>River Loire is one of the four major rivers of France. It had always
major importance to France. In the Medieval time or the best time of
French civilization French Rules and noble men of that time had built
lot of Chateau (castles) along this river. It is very close to Paris,
which is one of the reasons to built their weekend home for hunting and
relaxation here.
We only visited three castles that Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Second Titre De Sejour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</guid><description>On the 9th of April we were supposed to collect our new Titre De
Sejour (Long term VISA) from Cite Prefecture de Police. The interview
was fixed almost 3 months ago and we reached there before our scheduled
time to be make sure this time there is no big problem. But our turn
came around 4o&amp;rsquo;clock which is almost one hour behind our scheduled time.
And after checking all our paper she says oh!</description></item><item><title>Moving to Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</guid><description>OK, we moved to our own apartment after all. This whole week was very
busy and hectic.Monday: It started with getting informed that my
checkout from hotel was the very same day. But I was not informed about
this before. And hotel people informed Pamela and disconnected
telephone; a real mess. We could not connect each other and convey what
was happening at two ends. I must have to admit the HR practice is worse
here.</description></item><item><title>Visting top sights</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-23-visting-top-sights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-23-visting-top-sights/</guid><description>Another nice weekend in the month of March and we are trying to see all
the top sights on our guidebook. We must admit this book is indeed a
very good and very nice gift from Akiko and others. A highly recommended
guidebook on Paris by Avant Guide.This time we started with St.
Chappell at Heart of Paris. Wonderful craftsmanship on glass windows,
which tells the story of Bible. Next to it is high court of France.</description></item></channel></rss>