<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>krishna on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/krishna/</link><description>Recent content in krishna on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/krishna/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Paper Anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid><description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventful
for both of us. On this day we went to Ramkrishna
Mission.The
hour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fall
color.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Pooja
and Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went to
Salon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description></item><item><title>Visit to Ram Krishna Mission</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</guid><description>Ramkrishana Mission or center of Vendantic Society as we know it,
commonly is situated out side of Paris. A great place just to go and
spend some time in peace. It was birth anniversary of Ramkrishana when
we went there first time. We were very unsure how to reach the Center.
But it was a miracle we found some one speaking English at the station
to guide us. This center is quite big area-wise compared to San
Francisco and Berkeley one that we visited.</description></item></channel></rss>