<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>starbucks on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/starbucks/</link><description>Recent content in starbucks on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/starbucks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coffee – makes me happy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is not new and there are few
posts on the same subject
in past. The culture of having a good time with a cup of coffee is
catching up in India. Café Coffee Day aka CCD is expanding its
footprints in rapid speed from past few years; people close to the
business speculate they are just spending money and expanding in hope
for a bought over by some FDI like Starbucks if the later enter
Indian market.</description></item><item><title>Cost cutting Travel and more</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 07:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</guid><description>My last week trip to Singapore was a hectic one. Too many meetings and
meetings at work; best part is now a new Starbucks at Science Park
Drive is opened close to work; was very lucky where every other day got
pampered by my host with a coffee.
The flight from Bangalore was a nightmare I never experienced such
horrible service from any airline in my travel history. For Airlines
each seats are perishable commodities, which is lost as soon as the
flight takes off and it is a dream come true for Airline Company when
they have one.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item></channel></rss>