<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>milan on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/milan/</link><description>Recent content in milan on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/milan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Itlay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 12:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</guid><description>We have been to Rome for 4 days in 2003 but we wanted to visit the other
parts of Italy but could not do that due to time constrain. We were
planning for trip to Florence, Venice etc old classic route for long
time.
Krovi and Vidya went to Italy on their paper honeymoon which was 3
weeks earlier than us and they did provided us with lots of good tips.</description></item></channel></rss>