<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>birthday on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/birthday/</link><description>Recent content in birthday on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/birthday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sharat - when rains give way to the early autumn with blue skies, mid-August to mid-October.</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</guid><description>Month of September 2014 was a unique one. It started like just another
month of the year.
Honestly it has 17th September which is most times ‘Bishwakarma Puja’
and Pamela’s B’day and that is how I remember it. From childhood
Bishwakarma puja has a special mention growing up in Tripura. After
Saraswati puja in January/February there was no major festival till
Bishwakarma Puja. And there used to pandals and people going out in the
evening to visit those pandals.</description></item><item><title>Another year passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 14:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</guid><description>Another year passed and more grey hairs to take care now. Well this time
I cut the cake at office with my team. Cake came off course from Cake
Walk. Well I never had any no birthday resolution there was no
difference this year as well. Big thanks to those who wished me on time
or belated. For others this post is few weeks old in itself.</description></item><item><title>Joyeux Anniversaire- mon petit</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</guid><description>As usual there is lots of gaps of posting. Last month was quite hectic
as we celebrated Aarush&amp;rsquo;s first birthday
We started planning from December onwards. As our schedule now revolves
around his nap-time and whims we hardly get time for each other or to
discuss any matter it’s just a lot more rare these days than it used to
be. So, gone are the days of last minute plan. Despite how he has
completely turned our lives upside down we wanted to celebrate his first
b&amp;rsquo;day which I know he hardly will acknowledge at this age.</description></item></channel></rss>