<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sea food on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/sea-food/</link><description>Recent content in sea food on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/sea-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item></channel></rss>