<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>road trip on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/road-trip/</link><description>Recent content in road trip on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/road-trip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Majuli Part-II, Day-11 Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-21-majuli-day-2-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-21-majuli-day-2-april-2018/</guid><description>Morning at Deka Cheng -
We went for a morning stroll along the stream that is just in front of Deka Cheng. After coming back about an hour, we had to wait patiently for breakfast as service was super BAD. As mentioned earlier while there was only other guest who is supposed to be a big Government Babu the whole attention of the whole staff was with him only. At the end we felt so frustrated that we gave our peace of mind to the so-called property manager.</description></item><item><title>Majuli Part-I, Day-10 Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</guid><description>Somewhere on the internet once read the need for a vacation within a vacation. I know it sounds oxymoron but trust me when you are on the road for some time you need a day or two just doing nothing. Majuli was supposed to a magical place for us.
As we drove back west from Sivsagar we took the diversion to Nematighat, the boat embarkation point (ferry ghat) to go to Majuli.</description></item><item><title>Sivasagar, Day-9 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</guid><description>When I was planning this long trip to Assam I always wanted to drive all the way up to Dibrugarh where I studied till class 5. Later, in the final planning stage realized it was too long of a drive. Covering Guwahati, Shillong &amp;amp; Dibrugarh was getting too much in one trip so saved it for a later day. Sivasagar remained in the itinerary for a night stay with a condition if we finish Gibbon-Hollongapar and still have time to explore the ancient capital of the Ahom kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga Part-I, Day-6 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 15:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>After a good night sleep with thunders and rain, the morning was clear of rain but the sky had overcast. Without much delay, we put all our stuff in the car and head out of the resort for Kaziranga. The best thing about the resort for us its proximity to the highway. We drive on the straight highway going east. The road was divided four lanes and there was not much traffic and was cruising around 100KM/Hr.</description></item><item><title>Sohra-Cherrapunjee, Day-5 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</guid><description>As usual, the sun went up early as we are the Eastern part of India, so after a good breakfast and settling our bills we left towards Cherrpunjee. The sky was cloudy but not raining. The 16KM drive is a long one from the resort we stayed and the road of first 8 KM closer to the resort was really bad.
We started with Thangkharang Park which looked farthest on the map.</description></item><item><title>Double Decker Bridge, Day-4 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</guid><description>Today we got up pretty late compared to other days. Had breakfast and left the hotel around 9 AM. There are some journeys in life which are hard to forget. Our trek to the much talked about Double Decker Root Bridge was one such journey for me. Staying at Cheerapunji Holiday resort has one advantage that it is hardly 7 km away from double-decker root bridge. We went 5 KM till Tyrna village where we parked our car and then 3KMs of hiking we were told by hotel people.</description></item><item><title>Driving Khasi Hills, Day-3 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</guid><description>Last night could not have proper sleep as in the middle of the night there was a sudden storm, followed by rain and finally power cut off. We got up around 6 AM and moved out of the place before 7 AM so as to avoid school traffic. We headed towards Elephant caves which come on the way to Cherrapunji, before that we saw the sign for Shillong Peak. And the sun was perfect to see the entire Shillong from the peak but as we approached near the turning and asked one passer-by whether it will be open.</description></item><item><title>Kerala 2018 Thekkady and Thattekad</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-10-16-kerala-2018-thekkady-and-thattekad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 14:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-10-16-kerala-2018-thekkady-and-thattekad/</guid><description>Just back from a week-long trip of Kerala. We left on a Monday quite unusual day to start a trip, always there is something new to do. We left home at 4:10 AM and b&amp;rsquo;cos of that we had almost zero traffic in crossing Bangalore city and every toll both we did had any queue and by 7:30 we reached Salem and stopped for Breakfast. Post breakfast we had to cross Salem and by 12ish we are in the border of Tamil Nadu &amp;amp; Kerala.</description></item><item><title>Shillong, Day-2 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</guid><description>We started early morning with a drive to pick-up point of our rented car. This place was in such an area where proper roads were not there….it was full of potholes and filled with rainwater from previous rains. One thing is there Guwahati inner roads are not great and even city is not that clean&amp;hellip;full of plastics. Anyways we zoomed out from that place without much wastage of time and hit the highway.</description></item><item><title>Guwahati, Day-1 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 19:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</guid><description>Guwahati Kamakhya The flight to Guwahati was too early in the morning from Bangalore and we decided upon that on landing we will go directly to Kamakhya temple before starting our trip. Kamakhya Temple is around 14KM from the airport and our relatives stay on the other side of the city. It makes sense to start the trip in an auspicious way and we tried to strike 2 birds with one.</description></item><item><title>North East 2018 planning</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</guid><description>Long prologue … someone once said&amp;hellip;
Happiness is to plan a trip to somewhere new with your loved one.
One best friend from Santanu’s engineering college got transferred from Bangalore to Shillong last year. In his send-off party, everyone committed that they would like to visit that part of the country. The friend in question is serving our country and he promised to be our host there while we visit Shillong, the Scotland of East and British summer capital of North East.</description></item><item><title>Day 3 - Rishikesh</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</guid><description>The
weather looked gloomy with an overcast sky as we woke up. We had
breakfast at the hotel and decided to visit Rishikesh today. Again we
headed back the way we came yesterday and after crossing Rajaji National
Park the road divides and one goes towards to Dehradun and one to
Rishikesh. The drive was pleasant, as we opted Laxman Jhula as our
destination google map smartly took us via highway bypassing the main
city.</description></item><item><title>Day - 2 Dehradun &amp; Haridwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</guid><description>We
work up fresh after a good sleep. But soon we realized we are in a place
which we are very not fond off. May be the Mussoorie did not blink with
us. After taking shower and getting ready for the day we went up to the
restaurant for breakfast. But looked like we were an early riser as
there were no one else and the place was not cleaned up for the day.</description></item><item><title>Driving October 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-10-24-driving-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 22:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-10-24-driving-october-2015/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Gujarat 2011 - Map</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 14:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</guid><description>Need to write the 4 years old road trip before my memory fades away. The
pictures
are there to help but need lots of coffee to complete the writing.
Our itinerary to khushbu Gujarat ki
Day -1 By flight Bangalore- Bombay. We took a morning flight
for Mumbai and reached around afternoon. Same day boarded train to
Baroda from Mumbai Central. Reached Baroda by night around 9. It was
a chair car train.</description></item><item><title>Half early update</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 12:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</guid><description>So just before school reopens we had out of Bangalore for 2 nights. We
opted for something closer to home Coorg but on the southern side. We
opted for this side as we been to more popular side near Madikeri in
2008 when Aarush was around 9 month old. Time do really fly.
We started at 8:30 from home, very late compared to our slandered but
that day had Bangalore TCS 10K.</description></item><item><title>Goa ... beach and x-mas</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 12:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</guid><description>In 2013 we had very little family vacation time. I personally travelled
here and there for single nights few times due to running and other
personal work. The worst was to spend a week in Calcutta just after
Durga Pooja and not able to accomplish anything there. So when December
vacation time was only few days away I booked for Goa for 4 nights
without much thinking. Personally felt quite happy with the booking as
got a decent price for Goa just before X-mas.</description></item><item><title>Visit to North kerala- Wayanad</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 06:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</guid><description>From the time Santanu having classes and top of it exams this month; its
really a grueling month for both of us. For this I too was not getting
some time off from “Our little one”. There was absolute need of one
break. Santanu suddenly said two days before last exam that he is having
leave and if interested then we can go somewhere near by. Then he only
started reading on net and ended up saying we would go to
WAYANAD- Northern region of Kerala.</description></item><item><title>Drive to heritage site - Lepakshi</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</guid><description>My 1st term is coming to an end and we are given the upcoming test as
well project submission dates. On reaching home from class on Saturday I
was desperate to go out of Bangalore to get charged to combat the
upcoming gruelling weeks at work and personal front with study. I had no
clue where to go for a day and started to check my faithful websites and
zeroed on Lepakshi from Anita’s
site.</description></item></channel></rss>