<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stories on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/stories/</link><description>Recent content in Stories on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Remembering Belgium</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</guid><description>While categorizing our old travelogs I found there was no post on
Belgium
which values a lot for me. As I go down the memory lane&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;year 2003,
within 2 ½ months of marriage we have to move to Paris from US which was
a big change for me. Apart from the cultural shock, language was immense
barrier for day today life as well to mingle up with people around. Not
only that, in Indian arrange marriage, it takes time to understand each
other with each one&amp;rsquo;s weaknesses and failings.</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item></channel></rss>