<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>West-Bengal on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/west-bengal/</link><description>Recent content in West-Bengal on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 03:09:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/west-bengal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kurseong</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 03:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</guid><description>The
first-daywe
got little suspicious with the transport rates being quoted by Kanchan
View Hotel Manager. We reported
that back to Calcutta the tour operator Mr. D. Ghosh. But once you are
away from home and you have limited option to negotiate a bargain. The
Hotel person by now have charged us 2500 for the first day covering only
Tagore Smritivan , monastery and forest bungalow. For the second day we
paid 2500 to cover 5/6 places but the distance was more.</description></item><item><title>Visit to hungry tide- Sunderban</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 20:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</guid><description>For the first time in my life I spent more than 2 nights in a row at
Calcutta. The initial plan was to attend Papai’s wedding reception and
travel to some where around like Digha and back to Bangalore. We got our
Bangalore – Calcutta ticket booked. Going was by train to save money and
return was on flight so that we save time &amp;amp; energy before getting back
to our daily routine.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>China rose</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid><description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soul
into. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit if
they fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,
the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No one
wants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description></item></channel></rss>