<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Majuli day 1 (April 2018)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</guid><description>Somewhere on the internet once read the need for a vacation within a
vacation. I know it sounds oxymoron but trust me when you are on the
road for some time you need a day or two just doing nothing. Majuli was
supposed to a magical place for us.
As we drove back west from Sivsagar we took the diversion to
Nematighat, the boat embarkation point (ferry ghat) to go to Majuli.</description></item><item><title>Sivasagar - Unexplored Ahom Kingdom's finest</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</guid><description>When I was planning this long trip to
Assam I
always wanted to drive all the way up to Dibrugarh where I studied till
class 5. Later, in the final planning stage realized it was too long of
a drive. Covering Guwahati, Shillong &amp;amp; Dibrugarh was getting too much in
one trip so saved it for a later day. Sivasagar remained in the
itinerary for a night stay with a condition if we finish
Gibbon-Hollongapar and still have time to explore the ancient capital of
the Ahom kingdom.</description></item><item><title>A morning at Hoollongapar Gibbon Sanctuary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</guid><description>Our trip to Hollong was one of the most challenging and memorable ones.
Still, after so many months, it remains clear like yesterday. We slept
early knowing we have to leave early. So when the alarm went off at 4 AM
the whole place was quiet and dark. We hauled all our luggage from the
room to the rented car. It was a bit of a task given that we were
staying backside of the property.</description></item><item><title>Gibbon Wildlife -- Things to know before vising.</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</guid><description>Hollongapar GIBBON WILDLIFE SANCTUARY Hollong - the state tree of Aaasm. The story goes back like this when
the British came and saw these long trees, they asked How Long? And
it became Hollong Tree. Just like &amp;ldquo;there is a brown crow&amp;rdquo; was a
way to say &amp;ldquo;Darwaza
bandh Karo**&amp;rdquo; (close the door in Hindi &amp;ndash; from Satyajit
Ray&amp;rsquo;s Feludaa).It is only 20 sq KM of Sanctuary. Actually, it is the oldest
miscellaneous plantation having Dipterocarpus and Mesua as dominant
species It was declared a Reserve by the British way back in 1881,(53
years after the advent of British rule) The original forests used to
extend to the foothills of the Patkai mountain range.</description></item><item><title>Second Day in Kaziranga (April 2018)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>Our hotel Wild Grass was next to Central Zone. For the second day in
Kaziranga, we supposed to have elephants Safari in the morning. Now
there are 2 places where you can have elephant safari. The central zone
is very popular, is difficult to get, The counter opens at 7 PM in the
evening prior and people line up for long, there is a priority to
foreign tourist. Our hotel arranged for the Western Zone.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga - information you need to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</guid><description>Kaziranga is one of the bigger National Park of India. It has three
prominent zones - Central, Western and Eastern.
Central Range &amp;ndash; This drive covers the central region of the park.
It is an ideal introduction to the park and its ecology as the route
passes through the entire spectrum of habitat types prevalent in the
Kaziranga area. (though Brahmaputra view is not available, a stretch of
the route goes by the tributary river Difloo) There is a possibility of
sighting elephants as well as the other big animals especially the swamp
buffalo and of course the rhino.</description></item><item><title>Day 1 in Kaziranga - April 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 15:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>After a good night sleep with thunders and rain, the morning was clear
of rain but the sky had overcast. Without much delay, we put all our
stuff in the car and head out of the resort for Kaziranga. The best
thing about the resort for us its proximity to the highway. We drive on
the straight highway going east. The road was divided four lanes and
there was not much traffic and was cruising around 100KM/Hr.</description></item><item><title>Sight Seeing Sohra (Cherrapunjee)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</guid><description>As usual, the sun went up early as we are the Eastern part of India, so
after a good breakfast and settling our bills we left towards
Cherrpunjee. The sky was cloudy but not raining. The 16KM drive is a
long one from the resort we stayed and the road of last 8 KM was really
bad. We started with Thangkharang Park which looked farthest on the map.
The road was good for the most part but again the last 4/5 KM was under
heavy construction.</description></item><item><title>Tiring yet happy day - Double Decker Root Bridge</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</guid><description>Today we got up pretty late compared to other days. Had breakfast and
left the hotel around 9 AM. There are some journeys in life which are
hard to forget. Our trek to the much talked about Double Decker Root
Bridge was one such journey for me. Staying at Cheerapunji holiday
resort has one advantage that it is hardly 7 km away from double-decker
root bridge. We went 5 KM till Tyrna village where we parked our car and
then 3KMs of hiking we were told by hotel people.</description></item><item><title>Day-3 Long day, Long drive- CRAZY ONE - Meghalaya</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</guid><description>Last night could not have proper sleep as in the middle of the night
there was a sudden storm, followed by rain and finally power cut off. We
got up around 6 AM and moved out of the place before 7 AM so as to avoid
school traffic. We headed towards Elephant caves which come on the way
to Cherrapunji, before that we saw the sign for Shillong Peak. And the
sun was perfect to see the entire Shillong from the peak but as we
approached near the turning and asked one passer-by whether it will be
open.</description></item><item><title>Birds of Coorg</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-11-12-birds-of-coorg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-11-12-birds-of-coorg/</guid><description>As we learn more about birds we try to accommodate a day or two within
our family trips for birding. These pictures were taken around Virajpet
(South Coorg) and few within Nagarhole National Park. from our recent
trip in 2108 October.
The birds found here are very common to birds of Kerala as they are very
close by.</description></item><item><title>Birds of Kerala</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-10-16-birds-of-kerala/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-10-16-birds-of-kerala/</guid><description>Some birds spotted in Kerala around Thekkady and Thattekad.</description></item><item><title>Kerala 2018 Thekkady and Thattekad</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-10-16-kerala-2018-thekkady-and-thattekad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 14:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-10-16-kerala-2018-thekkady-and-thattekad/</guid><description>Just back from a week-long trip of Kerala. We left on a Monday quite
unusual day to start a trip, always there is something new to do. We
left home at 4:10 AM and b&amp;rsquo;cos of that we had almost zero traffic in
crossing Bangalore city and every toll both we did had any queue and by
7:30 we reached Salem and stopped for Breakfast. Post breakfast we had
to cross Salem and by 12ish we are in the border of Tamil Nadu &amp;amp; Kerala.</description></item><item><title>Day 2 - Shillong</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</guid><description>We started early morning with a drive to pick-up point of our rented
car. This place was in such an area where proper roads were not
there….it was full of potholes and filled with rainwater from previous
rains. One thing is there Guwahati inner roads are not great and even
city is not that clean&amp;hellip;full of plastics. Anyways we zoomed out from
that place without much wastage of time and hit the highway.</description></item><item><title>Day - 1 Maa Kamakhya here we come !!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 19:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</guid><description>Guwahati Kamakhya
The flight to Guwahati was too early in the morning from Bangalore and
we decided upon that on landing we will go directly to Kamakhya temple
before starting our trip. Kamakhya Temple is around 14KM from the
airport and our relatives stay on the other side of the city. It makes
sense to start the trip in an auspicious way and we tried to strike 2
birds with one.</description></item><item><title>North East 2018 planning</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</guid><description>Long prologue … someone once said
***“Happiness is to plan a trip to somewhere new with your loved
ones”. ***
One best friend from Santanu’s engineering college got transferred from
Bangalore to Shillong last year. In his send-off party, everyone
committed that they would like to visit that part of the country. The
friend in question is serving our country and he promised to be our host
there while we visit Shillong, the Scotland of East and British summer
capital of North East.</description></item><item><title>Day 3 - Rishikesh</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-10-06-day-3-rishikesh/</guid><description>The
weather looked gloomy with an overcast sky as we woke up. We had
breakfast at the hotel and decided to visit Rishikesh today. Again we
headed back the way we came yesterday and after crossing Rajaji National
Park the road divides and one goes towards to Dehradun and one to
Rishikesh. The drive was pleasant, as we opted Laxman Jhula as our
destination google map smartly took us via highway bypassing the main
city.</description></item><item><title>Day - 2 Dehradun &amp; Haridwar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</guid><description>We
work up fresh after a good sleep. But soon we realized we are in a place
which we are very not fond off. May be the Mussoorie did not blink with
us. After taking shower and getting ready for the day we went up to the
restaurant for breakfast. But looked like we were an early riser as
there were no one else and the place was not cleaned up for the day.</description></item><item><title>Day 1 - Drive to Mussoorie</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-06-20-day-1-drive-to-mussoorie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-06-20-day-1-drive-to-mussoorie/</guid><description>It
was a crazyweek,
as usual, it always happens that the week is very bad forwork, commute and
others just before we go onvacation and come back. So somehow we finished our packing on Thursday
night and set our alarms for early Friday.We
woke up on time and got ready and then call for Uber, the app shows the
taxi is just next to our apartment where normally few Uber/Ola always
are found.</description></item><item><title>Uttarakhand - prelude</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</guid><description>*It
has been such a long time that we posted something we almost forgot how
to type long paragraphs. Maybe all due to Facebook and WhatsApp which is
instant but then in when you look back you have no way to figure out
what all the noise was about. Well enough of rant now let me
type….*Beginning
of 2017 we were very much looking for a vacation and Pamela was
interested in Uttarakhand.</description></item><item><title>Plan for 2017</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2017-02-14-plan-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 15:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2017-02-14-plan-for-2017/</guid><description>Wish list for year 2017/18.
27thAugust Airtel
Hyderabad HM 10thSeptember Chennai
Trail Marathon Full 15thOctober Bangalore
HM :) 29thOctober Gurgaon
Full  10thDecember Goa River
Marathon Full  4thFebruary 2018 IDBI
Calcutta Full  11thFebruary 2018
Auroville HM 25thFebruary 2018 Delhi
IDBI Full So far I have covered running a Full Marathon in these states of India.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can add Goa, West Bengal, and Tamilnadu to
the list.</description></item><item><title>2016 Planning</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2016-01-13-2016-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 19:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2016-01-13-2016-planning/</guid><description>Some Runs/Race I would like to do in 2016.
14-Feb-2016 Auroville Marathon 06-Mar-2016 IDBI Kolkata Marathon ( can not go but listing ) 19-Mar-2016 Nirbhaya Midnight Marathon (Bangalore) 12-Jun-2016 Run Your First Half or Full Marathon (Jaynagar Jaguar
date not confirmed) 17-Jul-2016 The Cherrapunjee Marathon 28-Aug-2016 Airtel Hyderabad Marathon 11-Sep-2016 Chennai Trail Marathon 16-Oct-2016 Bengaluru Marathon</description></item><item><title>Cochin Full Marathon 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 15:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</guid><description>Pre-Race Day
The day started early, we get out Cochin Club today and part our our
ways for some time. While Pamela &amp;amp; Aarush goes back to Bangalore on
Saturday itself I stay back for the big run on Sunday.
They had a train to catch around 9 from ERS. There was not a single auto
around so had to walk and get one from Ferry station and as usual the
price asked and agreed is way more than normal,</description></item><item><title>Driving October 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-10-24-driving-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 22:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-10-24-driving-october-2015/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Satara HM 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-09-23-satara-hm-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 11:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-09-23-satara-hm-2015/</guid><description>Satara is located in Maharashtra not very far from Pune,
Mahabaleshwar located
in western ghat. PaceMakers decided to run this HM instead of Hyderabad
beginning of the year and booked a complete hotel in February itself.
That caused a uproar in Indian armature running community. The
registration for Satara HM for out station also got closed as there is a
limited hotel accommodation in this town. Personally I was not very
keen to run to it given the remote location and no direct train and
flight.</description></item><item><title>43 seconds and counting</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 10:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</guid><description>Third year in a row ran Airtel Hyderabad half
marathon yesterday. There was many
things which were different from 2013. Looking back 2013 was my second
outstation race with PaceMakers. We
traveled in train and return journey was not a great one as we had to
travel in sleeper class. The fun was most of us did not had bed linen as
we forgot how it was to travel in sleeper class.</description></item><item><title>Gujarat 2011 - Map</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 14:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-08-26-gujarat-2011-map/</guid><description>Need to write the 4 years old road trip before my memory fades away. The
pictures
are there to help but need lots of coffee to complete the writing.
Our itinerary to khushbu Gujarat ki
Day -1 By flight Bangalore- Bombay. We took a morning flight
for Mumbai and reached around afternoon. Same day boarded train to
Baroda from Mumbai Central. Reached Baroda by night around 9. It was
a chair car train.</description></item><item><title>Half early update</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 12:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</guid><description>So just before school reopens we had out of Bangalore for 2 nights. We
opted for something closer to home Coorg but on the southern side. We
opted for this side as we been to more popular side near Madikeri in
2008 when Aarush was around 9 month old. Time do really fly.
We started at 8:30 from home, very late compared to our slandered but
that day had Bangalore TCS 10K.</description></item><item><title>Happy Baking Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-17-happy-baking-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 12:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-17-happy-baking-happy-holidays/</guid><description>Normal Sponge Cake Carrot walnut cake *Mocha pudding * Date Cake Honeyed Apple slice</description></item><item><title>What a Saturday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-07-what-a-saturday/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 12:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-07-what-a-saturday/</guid><description>Woke up at 4:25 AM ; it was supposed it be a a long day for me as I try
to run 39 KM practice run in a easy pace. Though I am not going to
participate in the upcoming SCMM (Standard Chartered Mumbai Marathon)
2015 I decided to stick with the full marathoner group to see how
grueling their preparation can be. Assembled at 4:45 in front of the NCBS gate and met an ultra marathoner
from our running group who already covered 23KM starting from 02:30 AM.</description></item><item><title>Sharat - when rains give way to the early autumn with blue skies, mid-August to mid-October.</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</guid><description>Month of September 2014 was a unique one. It started like just another
month of the year.
Honestly it has 17th September which is most times ‘Bishwakarma Puja’
and Pamela’s B’day and that is how I remember it. From childhood
Bishwakarma puja has a special mention growing up in Tripura. After
Saraswati puja in January/February there was no major festival till
Bishwakarma Puja. And there used to pandals and people going out in the
evening to visit those pandals.</description></item><item><title>Airtel Hyderabad Half Marathon 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</guid><description>After Chennai DRHM event the event I signed up for was Airtel Hyderabad
Half Marathon. This run is little special to me as received my first
ever finisher T-shirt last year as a proof of my improvement in running.
Also there is the big culinary charm of Dine-hill and Karachi biscuits
as post run celebration.
Booked myself a return flight as soon as the dates for AHM 2014 was out.</description></item><item><title>Instant Coffee Bundt Cake</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-21-instant-coffee-bundt-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-21-instant-coffee-bundt-cake/</guid><description>Was looking for a simple instant coffee cake recipe and after reading
few here and there, zeroed on this one from
Nestlé.
But as usual did not had many things at home and being a weekend decided
to go with what ever had and make a simple sponge cake with coffee
flavor. Very surprised how simple and tasty it came out being a coffee
lover would try it again :) Had a disastrous start when mixed baking powder and baking soda in the
wet mix of butter and sugar.</description></item><item><title>Indian Mobile scene and future ....</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-17-indian-mobile-scene-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 15:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-17-indian-mobile-scene-and-future/</guid><description>As you know the growth of mobile is one of BIG discussion point of any
technology seminar or talk show you attend today. Everybody already
predicting more and more people will use mobile to access
internet/information/e-commerce compared to traditional desktop or
laptop. And in a country like India there will be lots of users who will
be &amp;ldquo;on-line&amp;rdquo; for the first time and they will directly use a smart
phone bypassing key-board and mice altogether, in numbers they might be
larger than some European country.</description></item><item><title>DRHM Chennai 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-03-drhm-chennai-2014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 14:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-07-03-drhm-chennai-2014/</guid><description>Enough is enough I said to myself before I started to write down my
experience with 2014 Chennai Dream Runners Half marathon. After waiting
for weeks and getting constant update on social media that my friends
are being tagged in various albums I could not found a single picture of
myself what a pity when everyone was clicking with those super sharp
DSLRs and smart phones.
Like last year we travelled to Chennai in Shatabdi Express on Saturday
starting early morning from Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Facebook down - June 19th 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-06-19-facebook-down-june-19th-2014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 13:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-06-19-facebook-down-june-19th-2014/</guid><description>Wow that must generate more news later today when the social network
site of the world took a plunge. Lets see how much time it takes them to
fix the same. While some users are able to login they are not getting
any updates and people like me are not able to login at all :(</description></item><item><title>Wow what a coincidence!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-05-12-wow-what-a-coincidence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 10:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-05-12-wow-what-a-coincidence/</guid><description>For the
upcoming 2014 TCS Bangalore10K,
I am running for a cause. I will be supporting an NGO
called ILP (India Literacy Project) which
I became familiar with through my running group. I also volunteered to
raise funds for ILP
through BangaloreCare. This
is my humble effort to raise funds for a cause close to my heart. ILP
is working in 17 states and 850 villages of India to make this basic
right available.</description></item><item><title>PaceMakers</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-04-29-pacemakers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 12:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-04-29-pacemakers/</guid><description>Believe I shared it before many times, my likeness of an active
lifestyle. It was not new to me but last year found like minded group
and joined them and now i can say i do exercise few times a week. A
passion drives us to wake up at 4 AM twice on weekdays to reach stadium
and start workout by sharp 5AM. It is tough but once you reach there
and start your day the whole day I find myself with plenty of positive
energies.</description></item><item><title>Driving Himachal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-04-26-driving-himachal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 17:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-04-26-driving-himachal/</guid><description>View Larger
MapWe are back to Bangalore from our
first trip to Northern India. It was touching the dot of the
***&amp;ldquo;i&amp;rdquo;*** in the amazing
**Incredible India**. The
eco-friendlystate of
Himachal Pradesh and
Himalaya has so much to offer is just amazing. Feeling proud to be
Indian&amp;hellip;.really AmazingIndia! Abundance of natural
beauty ranging from beautiful snow-capped and green mountains, at times
rolling hills, valleys, mountains cut in mushroom shape to give way to
narrow roads and tunnels, gushing river like Satluj, Beas, Ravi etc,
meadows giving ways to rock around highest peak,waterfalls,apple
orchards with great variation in climatic condition&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Tanflora -- Our own Keukenhof around Bangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-03-29-tanflora-our-own-keukenhof-around-bangalore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 17:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-03-29-tanflora-our-own-keukenhof-around-bangalore/</guid><description>Got an invite to visit a Rose farm from one of our running group member.
Though this trip was long due it was like now or never as the season for
roses almost comes to end with HOT Indian summer. From Bangalore we need
to go via Sarjapur, Bagalur in Housr District of TamilNadu. Google name
is Amuthugondapalli. Due to exam time many people could not come but it
was still a sizable group of 30.</description></item><item><title>A Weekend - supposed to be perfect</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-03-18-a-weekend-supposed-to-be-perfect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-03-18-a-weekend-supposed-to-be-perfect/</guid><description>Aarush reminded me it&amp;rsquo;s Friday, at breakfast table and that he should
have the I-Pad with charger for the Weekend; somehow he remembers when
it is Friday very well for his age. Well the weekend was supposed to be
a just another weekend on the calendar with no specific plan. There were
some weekend work/changes/releases at office but not a major ones.
Nowadays my running group is doing long runs on Saturday instead of
Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Pinkathon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-02-17-pinkathon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 03:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-02-17-pinkathon/</guid><description>Pinakthon is a initiative to encourage todays women of India to
participate in active life style. Being little active myself I know it
is very difficult for modern urban Indian women to follow the same.
There are many logistical issues staring from family, in-laws, sons,
daughters, job and what not.
But the biggest block I think is they themselves as to take initiative
of starting an active lifestyle and being committed to it which is not
an easy commitment .</description></item><item><title>Planning a summer escape - 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-01-28-planning-a-summer-escape-2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-01-28-planning-a-summer-escape-2014/</guid><description>View Driving directions to Chandigarh, Chandigarh,
India
in a larger mapLooking for travel advice!!! Ticket booked from Bangalore to Chandigarh
round trip. We flyout on Sunday(13th April) and stay that night at
Chandigarh and next day would like to start for Himachal Pradesh. And
return after almost 2 weeks, on Friday to Chandigarh and take next
Morning flight to Bangalore on Saturday (26th April).</description></item><item><title>Goa ... beach and x-mas</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 12:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</guid><description>In 2013 we had very little family vacation time. I personally travelled
here and there for single nights few times due to running and other
personal work. The worst was to spend a week in Calcutta just after
Durga Pooja and not able to accomplish anything there. So when December
vacation time was only few days away I booked for Goa for 4 nights
without much thinking. Personally felt quite happy with the booking as
got a decent price for Goa just before X-mas.</description></item><item><title>PHP iptcembed Gallery3 to Flickr</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-12-18-php-iptcembed-gallery3-to-flickr/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 18:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-12-18-php-iptcembed-gallery3-to-flickr/</guid><description>A journey of sharing photo only got me into having a website of my own.
When digital camera came out with decent mega pixel was an early adapter
of the same. But soon realized sharing Pictures on email was not an
option and hosted pictures on Tripod. Oh! they used to give 10MB of
free hosting :) now Flicker gives one 1TB free. So long story small
after the managing own gallyery app writen initally with csv and php ,
later mysql and php and lastly Gallery for almost 10 years.</description></item><item><title>Moving away from self hosting</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-12-14-moving-away-from-self-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-12-14-moving-away-from-self-hosting/</guid><description>Well after all these years of self hosting and WordPress I am kind of
let go the Self-hosting. Moved
pamela.santm.com to Tumblr and all the
pictures from Gallery3 to
Flickr. Still need to move www.santm.com somewhere and aarush.santm,com pictures
to somewhere, most likely it will be Flickr again. hope to complete the
all these before 2013 finishes.</description></item><item><title>Kurseong</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 03:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</guid><description>The
first-daywe
got little suspicious with the transport rates being quoted by Kanchan
View Hotel Manager. We reported
that back to Calcutta the tour operator Mr. D. Ghosh. But once you are
away from home and you have limited option to negotiate a bargain. The
Hotel person by now have charged us 2500 for the first day covering only
Tagore Smritivan , monastery and forest bungalow. For the second day we
paid 2500 to cover 5/6 places but the distance was more.</description></item><item><title>Mysore Half Marathon 2013</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</guid><description>This was Mysore Celebration Run 2013 ; well there was BIG celebration at
Pacemakers running group. Coach was brand ambassador of the run, we had
a promo run in Bangalore for the same. Few runners from group also got
featured in Life is Calling&amp;rsquo;s web
site.
Initially I was against this run as I rescheduled my Mother&amp;rsquo;s return
flight from Bangalore to Siliguri on the same Sunday :(. But big thanks
to Maa and Pamela as they supported to run me this event.</description></item><item><title>West Sikkim - Hee Bermiok</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-19-west-sikkim-hee-bermiok/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-19-west-sikkim-hee-bermiok/</guid><description>We initially planned to visit Bhutan during summer vacation of ’13.
Somehow during the planning phase we found it was overshooting our
budget. And moreover, was advised against it during late April &amp;amp; Early
May as there is a high chances of rain during that time. So we had no
plan and no places to visit while we are going to be in Siliguri for
10/12 days.
We called one travel agent in Calcutta from train and told him about our
requirement and he said he would be able to put an itinerary of 6 nights
( 2nights Sikkim, 2 Kursuang and 2 in Darjeeling).</description></item><item><title>Indian Babus(Govt Official)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-05-indian-babus-govt-official/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-09-05-indian-babus-govt-official/</guid><description>Today went to the local BBMP (Bruhat Bengaluru Mahanagara Palike) office
to get my property Tax receipt which I paid in June there. Was told to
go other one as this office is being closed. God only knows why
Government build office first and operate there for few years and move
to another one. On going to next office
 The guy told without looking at me &amp;ldquo;Come Monday&amp;rdquo;
Me - ** &amp;ldquo;Sir Monday is Off due to Ganesha Festival&amp;rdquo;**</description></item><item><title>Blessed</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-28-blessed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 03:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-28-blessed/</guid><description>Blessing is a simple word, but yesterday night (Monday) just before
sleeping I was thinking about the same again and again. Wished for a
gadget to record my thought as I was too tired to use any keyboard or
voice recorder. At times we wonder and sometime make fun of those award
ceremonies where people on the stage keep on thanking people around him
or her and sometimes even their dogs.</description></item><item><title>Pipeline Road Run</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-04-pipeline-road-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 23:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-08-04-pipeline-road-run/</guid><description>There was a discussion in the running group to practice hill-run before
upcoming Hyderabad run which I am trying to be a regular member.
Normally the &amp;ldquo;numero uno&amp;rdquo; destination for hill training around Bangalore
is Nandi Hill ; which is 60KM north of the city. Have already run Nandi
hills few times and yes Nandi is grueling specially the last 3 KM. Nandi
run is 15KM in total where you go 7.</description></item><item><title>1st class sleeper</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-15-1st-class-sleeper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 21:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-15-1st-class-sleeper/</guid><description>It was a dream from a long time to travel in 1stclass in
Indian Railway. The last time I traveled in 1stclass was
early 1985 when we went to Puri ( a must stop for Bengali
).
So when the dates for summer vacation became clear started booking for
train tickets. It was month of December when we booked ticked for April.
Wanted to book 2ndAC ticket but to my surprise it was
already sold out so opted for AC 1stClass.</description></item><item><title>Chennai DRHM</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</guid><description>Chennai DRHM ( Dream Runners Half
Marathon) was on
1st Sunday of July i.e. 7thJuly 2013. It was the first run
out of Bangalore for me. Last time I registered for Mumbai Standard
Chartered was in 2008 and was gifted with Aarush just few days before
the race :D Well Aarush is the reason why I can not run on weekdays
morning but he is the catalyst who introduced me to The Pacemakers
running group of Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Google Page Test, CloudFlare and W3 total Cache</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-03-google-page-test-cloudflare-and-w3-total-cache/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 17:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-07-03-google-page-test-cloudflare-and-w3-total-cache/</guid><description>Installed all these three on pamela.santm.com and blog.santm.com which
are running on wordpress 3.6 trunk. moved the dns details to cloudflare.
While Pamela&amp;rsquo;s hobby site did very well Google page test result our blog
result was not great. Looks like the culprit is inbuilt gallery of
wordpress which is re-sizing images and seving them on fly causing high
server time. the command that helped me a lot is &amp;ldquo;mogrify -strip *.</description></item><item><title>Aarush~nama</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-24-aarush-nama/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 19:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-24-aarush-nama/</guid><description>Last Saturday, it was father &amp;amp; son time again as Pamela in school after
a long summer vacation. Aarush was doing his part to keep my hands busy
and asked him are you a Nut for being such naughty? And the apt reply
was “Yes, I am; I am a coconut”. I could not stop laughing for a
long time. Even though we call it a nut but coconut is not a nut
botanically?</description></item><item><title>Handshake</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-07-handshake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 01:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-07-handshake/</guid><description>A great gesture of being humble by Mr. David Thomson today. He did
shook-hand with the entire front row as we officially inaugurated of
our new Office today. Luckily I was there early bird :) and was
touched by his firm handshake. He is the wealthiest man personally saw
in person he used to be ranked in top 10 richest man according Forbes
few years back.</description></item><item><title>BookShelf</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-04-bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 02:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-04-bookshelf/</guid><description>This was complete DYI project. Theses books are not going to be touched
soon.</description></item><item><title>10 years hitch</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-04-10-years-hitch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 01:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-06-04-10-years-hitch/</guid><description>Wow it is 10 years already for a blog/web site which has always been
early adopter of WordPress trunk :)</description></item><item><title>Opinion - does it really matter ?</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-04-09-opinion-does-it-really-matter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 20:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-04-09-opinion-does-it-really-matter/</guid><description>Opinion – a simple word everyone has one. Thanks to new social media
which makes it so easy to spread it. They express it say it is personal
(me included). Does it really personal once expressed ? I am not a
social science expert but there are some opinions heard, read in recent
time wondered what to do with them. Tried argue with few at the
beginning but at the end ignored them all.</description></item><item><title>Mangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-03-04-mangalore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 18:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-03-04-mangalore/</guid><description>As mentioned we split the travel in
October
with a week in between at Bangalore Durga Pooja. The destination for
part two had to have sea and beach to cleansing the body and soul.
Personally more of sea person if I have to choose between hills &amp;amp; sea. We settled for Mangalore. We booked for one hotel in the city which had
maximum discount for 3 nights. We tried
SumerSands the
number-Uno destination for Managlore on travel.</description></item><item><title>Bijapur-Chitradurga</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-bijapur-chitradurga/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-bijapur-chitradurga/</guid><description>Day-5, Woke up at 4:30 in the morning as I could barely sleep whole
night. Had mu bath and got little bit packing down to ensure we leave
Bijapur at the earliest. Woke Pamela &amp;amp; Aarush around 5:30 and we started
to walk to Gol Gumbaz. Unfortunately the lady who manages the ticket
counter did not show up till 6:30. We were the first one to enter. After
the local guard gving us little more history lesson asked us to climb
the steps quickly before anyone.</description></item><item><title>Badami and Bijapur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 01:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</guid><description>Day-4, Morning we woke up early and headed towards to Bansankari
Temple to start our day. Bansankari has lady idol with eight hands which
is worshiped meticulously around. We saw one lady rolling herself around
the whole temple periphery with wet cloth which signifies she just took
a bath in the nearby holy-pond. We got a good darshan of the devi idol
as there was not much crowd in the morning.</description></item><item><title>Aihole and Patadkal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 01:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</guid><description>Day-3, post breakfast we hit the road, this time we followed the GPS
voice of Pamela’s Lumia more attentively and with ease we head out of
Hospet and join the highway. The highway NH-13 between Hospet and
Bijapur is recently widen to 4 lane. It was a pleasure driving, the road
was not at all crowded and surprisingly the trucks maintained the left
lane. Was driving around 110/120 KMph without any trouble and soon
reached Hungund.</description></item><item><title>Hampi - history carved in granite</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-hampi-history-carved-in-granite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 18:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-hampi-history-carved-in-granite/</guid><description>Day – 1, As planned we left Bangalore quite late in our standard
after a big breakfast at home around 11, the traffic on a Saturday as
usual was very heavy and it continued that way till we crossed
Nelamangala. After that the traffic got better but there were too many
diversions as there was work going on to build flyovers and road
widening on NH-4. We filled fuel somewhere after Nelamangala, and
noticed there were not many decent stops like CCD or others.</description></item><item><title>Road trip - October 2012</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</guid><description>Visiting the northern part of Karnataka for its historic and artistic
monuments were long due. We thought of doing it two years back during
15th August long weekend but postponed the same due to late rain and
high water level at Tungabhadra Rivers. This year we started to plan
early and consulted two avid travelers and their guidance in setting up
the itinerary. It was planned that we would use the 2 weeks school
vacation for this trip, but then I personally felt it would be a great
miss Durga pooja twice in a row.</description></item><item><title>Coonoor - Acre Wild</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-21-coonoor-acre-wild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 19:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-21-coonoor-acre-wild/</guid><description>We followed road suggested by Mr. Vijay to reach Coonoor, which was
quite deserted except few local people we were the only one on that
road. This road goes via tea gardens and gives a treat to your eyes.
Once we reached Coonoor we parked next to the bus stand and had a quick
thali lunch in nearby busy restaurant. After that we headed towards our
Farmstay - Wild Acre. The direction given by Mr.</description></item><item><title>A magical gateway called - RedHill</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-09-26-a-magical-gateway-called-redhill/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 22:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-09-26-a-magical-gateway-called-redhill/</guid><description>The drive to Ooty was thrilling with those 36 hairpin turns. We reached
the outskirt of the city and asked for direction to Emerald/Avalanche
and reached bypassing central Ooty town. We passed Ooty lake on Lake
Road and crossed Good Shepherd School, Fern Hill Road and at last drove
on Avalanche Road. The place ‘Avalanche’ gets its name as there was a
massive land slide in early 1800. From Emerald (after the bridge) we
took a left and the road condition continued to degrade as we crossed
Avalanche Lake.</description></item><item><title>Masinagudi</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-09-14-masinagudi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-09-14-masinagudi/</guid><description>The long waited Summer Vacation of 2012 ; earlier we used to escape the
peak season madness now we are in the madness since both Aarush and
Pamela are now part of active school. And we are going to be like this
for years to come with no other choice. With that said, still wanted to
avoid the crowded destinations. We wanted to visit ‘ Nilgiris’ the
number uno summer destination of South India and picked Mudumalai,
Ooty(Red Hills) and Connoor.</description></item><item><title>South Trip</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-22-south-trip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 18:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-22-south-trip/</guid><description>Our trip to South was one for which we hardly planned meticulously.
Moreover, my son got fractured elbow but then also our spirit was on
high although bit dampened that whether we will enjoy or not; kind of
excitement mixed with anxiety, hope and happiness. I still remember the
moment we sat in the car and started for the trip which was going to be
one of the longest drive with Aarush.</description></item><item><title>Malampuzzha</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-22-malampuzzha/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 17:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-22-malampuzzha/</guid><description>After being guest of GK Homestay for 2 nights at 7.00 we hit the road
towards Malampuzha. It is about 8 km from the Palakkad town; Palkad is
known as gateway between Tamilnadu and Kerala as it is a valley between
hills. It is major rice growing area and home of many Tamil Brahmins who
are living in Kerala for centuries.
Malampuzha Garden is build next to reservoir on river with same name.</description></item><item><title>Backwater:Kumarakom</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-17-backwater-kumarakom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 14:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-17-backwater-kumarakom/</guid><description>Around 10 we started for our next destination to Kottayam which was
around 140K M away. From Varkala we started following the road signs for
Kochi but once we almost approached Kottayam/ Kumarakom we got little
bit lost but soon found our way towards Kottayam. Roads were good except
last part near GK Riverview home
stay
(Rough Guide recommendation). The owner of the homestay tried his best
to discourage from coming with a small kid which infact made us more
determined to stay with him.</description></item><item><title>Kovalam and Varkala beach</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-14-kovalam-and-varkala-beach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 14:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-14-kovalam-and-varkala-beach/</guid><description>Drive from Kanyankumari was smooth, Aarush took a small nap. The road
was undivided two lanes so the speed was limited but the lush green from
paddy field , coconut grove and plantation leaves was pleasant for eyes.
We reached Kovalam as per our plan, saw sunset which was magnificient.
It was great to watch perfect sunrise and sunset on a same day. Public
Beach was next to Taj and Leela hotels where large part belongs to them
for their private beach.</description></item><item><title>Kanyakumari : Where the Seas Meet</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-02-kanyakumari-where-the-seas-meet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 16:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-08-02-kanyakumari-where-the-seas-meet/</guid><description>Continuing from Madurai
(2010-December); we setup the alarm clock to ensure we do not miss the
sunrise. But to our surprise we were awaken early by anxiety and
whispers from the corridors. We went to see if the Sun was rising soon
but the horizon was dark and there was faint rays of light. We let
Aarush sleep and went to the rooftop where we saw every hotel rooftop is
full of people as all are waiting for the Sun-rise.</description></item><item><title>Yercaud - March'12</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-07-30-yercaud-march12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 17:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-07-30-yercaud-march12/</guid><description>Yercaud is mentioned as poor man&amp;rsquo;s Ooty in 52 weekends
gateway
but the article also mention it is a smart choice compared to Ooty. We
were supposed to visit Yercaud in 2011 September but after wonderful
vacation of
Munnar
and just before Gujarat we cancelled the booking as it was becoming too
much travelling in short span. I strongly believe in the words of
Tagore that good things in life needs to scared or they will become
mediocre :-)</description></item><item><title>Anandhadam</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-04-03-anandhadam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 04:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-04-03-anandhadam/</guid><description>Prologue, On 2ndof Feb received an open invitation from our
MD to be a part of her team to walk 100KM within 48hours. The walk
was organized by OXFAM to raise funds and awareness of their work among
poor section of society. I immediately hit reply as my earlier
discussion with another friend on the same walk did not materialized.
In the late afternoon I received confirmation that I am in and need to
walk on 10 &amp;amp; 11thFeb.</description></item><item><title>Rameshwaram</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-02-24-rameshwaram/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 16:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-02-24-rameshwaram/</guid><description>After complete rest and rainy night we woke up to find a perfect morning
in Madurai. Breakfast at the hotel was quite elaborate and we did a good
one before starting for Rameshwaram. The hotel guys were kind enough
to give us elaborate maps which really helped us to exit Madurai without
asking for any direction. One thing we noticed in Tamil-Nadu the
direction boards are mostly in Tamil and less of English compared to
Karnataka.</description></item><item><title>A small nano but long wait</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-09-23-a-small-nano-but-long-wait/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 18:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-09-23-a-small-nano-but-long-wait/</guid><description>Beginning of this year sold our Indica and bought Swift-Dzire(ZDI) which
we found very practical and perfect for our Indian need. And we did not
thought of booking any new car in recent time. Suddenly things got
changed when Pamela started a new job in May. We were quite happy with
single car and personally opted for BIAS (Bangalore International
Airport - Volvo) as I commute from Hebbal to Old Airport read every day
around 20KM one way.</description></item><item><title>Munnar in Monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-08-31-munnar-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-08-31-munnar-in-monsoon/</guid><description>It was the first long weekend of Independence day of 2011 after Pamela
had joined her job. We were very keen to get away from Bangalore as last
time it was March when we went to
Chickbelapur.
Initial plan was to visit Hampi; but after talking to few homestay
around we decided against it as that part of Karnataka was expecting to
get unusual amount of rain and flood could be any time.</description></item><item><title>A quick post</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</guid><description>Reading old newspaper clipping fascinate me; an article which earns a
good amount space on that day and most likely people read and forgot.
and here I am reading it after days with a fresh eye. And most times it
turns out to be a great story to read with eagerness.
This one was bit special which caught my eyes today was &amp;ldquo;Chaturanan
Mishra
passed away&amp;rdquo;; now there are few things which made me to write this quick
post.</description></item><item><title>Page Speed - Web site broken</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-07-01-page-speed-web-site-broken/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 18:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-07-01-page-speed-web-site-broken/</guid><description>Playing with Google lab and its &amp;ldquo;Page
speed&amp;quot;. Hope things gets fixed soon.</description></item><item><title>Father Day - Thank you Aarush</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 19:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</guid><description>During month of May there were some sudden turn of events happened that
changed the course of my life as father. Well I am quite positive on
this sudden turn of event that this happened for good. Pamela suddenly
jackpot a teaching Job with one of the premier institute of Bangalore.
And they asked her to join immediately. The first week was in training
in Kormangala was OK OK as Aarush had his summer camp in his old
school.</description></item><item><title>Madurai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-05-04-madurai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 17:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-05-04-madurai/</guid><description>Started very early morning around 5.45 from our parking lot and with one
stop at A2B restaurant at Krishnagiri reached Madurai exactly by
11.30AM. Then took some time to find out decent hotel two friends
recommended “Royal
Court”
near Madurai railway station. The hotel is clean and neat the management
was great to upgrade our room to executive suite as the original room
smelt cigarettes.
After settling we had a vegetarian south Indian lunch at market area.</description></item><item><title>Chikmagalur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-05-02-chikmagalur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 21:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-05-02-chikmagalur/</guid><description>After finishing
Belur-Halebid
by 3.00PM we moved towards Chikmaglur as we wanted to reach our
Apna-Sapna homestay
before dusk. For God knows what reason here all homestay are highly
priced based on per person per night. The Mountain section from
Chikmaglur to Attigundi (village) was excellent and fun to drive on the
twist and turn. The last part was a dirt road where we took diversion
for our homestay a downhill road.</description></item><item><title>Sleeper Class</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-04-20-sleeper-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 02:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-04-20-sleeper-class/</guid><description>Indian railway ferries millions of passenger each day. The network is
vast and somewhat efficient. But it is no way near to world class even
though it was one of the best luxury trains in its flight. For most
Indian travelling in train means a sleeper class more and more prefer AC
one now days. With ticket price of Airlines going up more and more
people are going back to train as it is still easy on pocket.</description></item><item><title>Halebid-Belur:living with past</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-29-halebid-belur-living-with-past/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-29-halebid-belur-living-with-past/</guid><description>It has been a long time that we ventured on NH-48; last time we visited
Shravanabelagola
in 2009. From then on it was always in discussion to visit Belur-Halebid
known for its hoysala architecture. This time we covered both
Belur-Halebid along with Chigmanglur on 3 day trip. We started at
7.10AM from our parking lot and reached Halebid by 12 with two breaks -
breakfast at Hotel Mayura and at Hassan for ATM.</description></item><item><title>With elephants @ Dubare</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-with-elephants-dubare/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-with-elephants-dubare/</guid><description>This year we didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate Aarush B&amp;rsquo;day as we moved to our
own apartment. Being new to complex we hardly knew anyone to invite.So
decided to celebrate his B&amp;rsquo;day at school which he of-course didn&amp;rsquo;t like
much as he didn&amp;rsquo;t receive any gifts and top of it he has to give return
gifts to his school mates….which he did so with heavy heart.
We decided to take him to Dubare elephant
camp.</description></item><item><title>Chokhi Dhani- Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</guid><description>Last day at Jaipur, today we have kept ourselves more or less free for
shopping. Had breakfast at hotel lawn for the first time. The buffet
breakfast at Hotel Madhuvan worth only when you have time to enjoy
it. We met one Indian family who were travelling from Gujrat for the
Diwali weekend to Jaipur and wanted to join us at Chokhi Dhani later in
the evening. Around 10 we left for shopping with Mr.</description></item><item><title>Maro des “Rajasthan”</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-18-maro-des-rajasthan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 17:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-18-maro-des-rajasthan/</guid><description>The first thing that struck me about Rajasthan was its roads when I last
went in 2000 with my parents. Rajasthan roads are amazing; and they are
very well connected interms of bus, train, private cars, even one can
hire cars to drive around between different places with in state. This
makes travelling in Rajasthan quite safe and less tiring. With good road
conditions you can also explore the interiors of Rajasthan.</description></item><item><title>Ajmer-Pushkar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-14-ajmer-pushkar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 23:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-14-ajmer-pushkar/</guid><description>Early morning reached Jaipur from Jaisalmer by train. This time our
cab driver from hotel (Madhuban) was waiting and on reaching hotel
relaxed for while. Before leaving for Jodhpur, we have fixed
with Mr. Singh (our reliable cab driver) for this trip to
Ajmer-Pushkar. As usual, he was there on time; left hotel room
around 8.00am. Had our breakfast on way at small neat and clean dhaba.
Road being 6 lane; had very comfort drive and was hardly crowded.</description></item><item><title>Jaisalmer</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-11-jaisalmer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 00:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-11-jaisalmer/</guid><description>We reached Jaisalmer early morning around 4.00am.Going from station
to hotel is another headache if you don’t have pick-up service
particularly at wee hours. We didn&amp;rsquo;t had that service from hotel as it
was extra 100INR so on reaching station we found, 10 people surrounded
us even they don’t allow couples to talk among themselves. Finally
hired one for 40 INR to go to Deoki Niwas hotel. When we reached, we
literally had to wake them up.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-09-jodhpur-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 22:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-09-jodhpur-ii/</guid><description>We started early morning after breakfast around 8 .00am. But luck is
always not in favour we got one nasty cab driver unlike Jaipur. Although
hired cab through hotel and asked to take us to Osyian but he insisted
on going to majestic sandstone palace of Umaid Bhawan. Before going
there he took us to shops for early morning shopping but we
didn’t.(they get commission when they take clients to their choice of
place).</description></item><item><title>Shravanabelagola - 18th October 2009</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-06-shravanabelagola-18th-october-2009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 14:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-03-06-shravanabelagola-18th-october-2009/</guid><description>Me and Aarush just returned a day before Santanu’s birthday from Durg
and he wanted an excuse from strenuous week at IIM-B and we ended up
planning to visit Shravanabelagola right after Diwali day. Unlike
his earlier trip he just had a casual look at the route map to
Shravanabelagola, it is a religious spot, a Jain pilgrimage centre.
The place is famous for 58ft. high monolithic stone statue of the Lord
Gommateshwara.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur 1st Nov 2010</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-22-jodhpur-1st-nov-2010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-22-jodhpur-1st-nov-2010/</guid><description>31stmidnight boarded train to Jodhpur from Jaipur after a
long day we were very tired . The train was late as it arrived from
Delhi. On the train meet Subhojit who was also in Rajasthan for one
long week break just like us from Bangalore. Their itinerary was bit
different compared to us and they were going to Jaiselmer. On the wee
hours of 1st November reached the platform of Jodhpur and thankgod for
ensuring that hotel provided a cab for pickup.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-01-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 02:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-02-01-jaipur/</guid><description>We woke around 7ish and left by the same Cab with Mr. Singh (who took us
to Shekhawati) around 8:30 from hotel. As Mr. Singh said jokingly lets
start the day in auspicious way – which mean Birla Temple was first
on the list and we reached the parking lot at dot 9. The journey took us
trough the posh residential area of Jaipur with huge bungalows which
have similarities with the Lutyens’ Delhi but a rarity in modern India.</description></item><item><title>Chod Aaye Hum Woh Galiyan</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2011-01-17-chod-aaye-hum-woh-galiyan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 04:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2011-01-17-chod-aaye-hum-woh-galiyan/</guid><description>This is our 4th move in last eight years. It was a different protocol
each time. Today I am lost in a mysterious maze of chasing thoughts;
want to pin them down and seal them in jars before they disappear
leaving behind nothing but an empty spot. I came to Tata Sherwood when
my son was 5 months old and today he is almost 3 yrs old. In this time
span I met so many people.</description></item><item><title>Shekhawati - Open Air Art Gallery</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 17:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</guid><description>29th Oct - We took SpiceJet flight to Jaipur but unfortunately could
not make it within time due to technical problems and traffic congestion
we were made to wait for 3 hrs inside flight. We reached around 22:00 to
our pre-booked Hotel Madhuban by prepaid taxi.
On reaching hotel driver says &amp;ldquo;kya bekar hotel liya hain sir&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;.ughh.
Lump in my throat as all booking was done by me. It was a laborious,
monotonous job going through website after website, jotting down details
regarding price.</description></item><item><title>Landed to jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-18-landed-to-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 14:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-18-landed-to-jaipur/</guid><description>29th oct- We took spicejet flight to jaipur but unfortunatley couldnot
make it within time due to technical problems and traffic congestion we
were made to wait for 3 hrs inside flight.We reached around 10.00pm to
our prebooked hotel by prepaid taxi.On reaching hotel driver says &amp;ldquo;kya
bekar hotel liya hain sir&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;.ughh lump in my throat as all booking was
done by me. It was a laborious, monotonous job going through website
after website, jotting down details regarding price.</description></item><item><title>Another Move</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-15-another-move/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 20:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-11-15-another-move/</guid><description>A few more week we will move from our current address; this time within
Bangalore. So compared to last moves it is going to be a very small
one. In 2003, we crossed Atlantic (California to Paris), in 2006 we
crossed Indian ocean (Paris to Mumbai) and in 2008 we moved within India
(Mumbai to Bangalore). Now this is just 20 Km move within Bangalore
city.
The painters from Asian Paint Home Solutions are doing the paint job and
they are supposed to finish by 25th November.</description></item><item><title>Des vacances</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-29-des-vacances/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 02:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-29-des-vacances/</guid><description>We are off to Rajasthan starting tomorrow. Here is the plan lets see
what we achieve in next one week-
29th Oct Fly to Jaipur on SpiceJet 30th Oct shekhawati day trip from Jaipur 31st Jaipur ; in the night catch train for Jodhpur 1st Nov in Jodhpur 2nd November in Jodhpur catch night train to Jaisalmer 3rd November in Jaisalmer and sunset in desert 4th Nov in the evening catch train back to Jaipur 5th Nov relax in Jaipur celebrate Deepavali 6th Nov if possible make a trip to Ajmer and Pushkar 7th Nov fly back to Bangalore All the bookings are done and big thanks to Pamela.</description></item><item><title>Auroville</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-18-auroville/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 04:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-18-auroville/</guid><description>Almost
after one and half year we went for a long weekend out of Bangalore; our
very first road trip of 2010. We were looking for something near to
beach and thought of heading towards Pondichery but due to
unavailability of any sea facing hotel we opted of Auroville.
Certain thing really happens for good. The road was Bangalore -&amp;gt; Krishnagiri -&amp;gt;
Tiruvanamalli -&amp;gt;Tindivanam-&amp;gt; Auroville.As usual Santanu had production outage @ work and went to sleep around 2
AM thanks to ‘new era new tool’ at work.</description></item><item><title>Puri – Konark</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-03-puri-konark/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 21:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-10-03-puri-konark/</guid><description>We had to extend our planned holidays as we
got a last minute invitation for my cousin&amp;rsquo;s marriage now both marriages
were only 6 days apart. Personally was quite unhappy about the whole
situation of attending two marriages; instead of voicing opinions, kept
cribbing and ranting. Confronting such family matters does not work as
no one is right. Anyways, at times you are forced to go along with such
decision whether you like it or not.</description></item><item><title>Lalbagh Flower Show'10</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-08-14-lalbagh-flower-show10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 19:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-08-14-lalbagh-flower-show10/</guid><description>Finally went to Lalbagh flower show last weekend (8th Aug). Thanks to my
work; was awake from 3 AM and had no trouble of getting ready early on
Sunday. By 8:40 AM we reached; crowd just started to show-up there was
not much problem of parking and all. As soon after we entered the main
glass-house Aarush started to sneeze incessantly. Among many varieties
of flower main attraction was off course the huge structure of India
Gate made of roses; it was tribute to soldiers who lost their lives
during the Second World war.</description></item><item><title>Coffee – makes me happy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is not new and there are few
posts on the same subject
in past. The culture of having a good time with a cup of coffee is
catching up in India. Café Coffee Day aka CCD is expanding its
footprints in rapid speed from past few years; people close to the
business speculate they are just spending money and expanding in hope
for a bought over by some FDI like Starbucks if the later enter
Indian market.</description></item><item><title>Circle and Cycle</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-07-02-circle-and-cycle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 17:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-07-02-circle-and-cycle/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Progress @ New Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-30-progress-new-apartment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 20:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-30-progress-new-apartment/</guid><description>Some update from previous
post . Till far we
made numerous trip on weekdays and weekends. We are almost done as far
as carpenter work and civil work is concerned. There are still few
things pending but we can wait for now. The next major one and obvious
ones are hardware and shower enclosure fixing at bathrooms along
with painting and electrical fittings. We need to make all the
necessary holes for pictures and wall hanging before final painting
work.</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-28-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 22:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-28-another-weekend/</guid><description>The past weekend was very low key just wanted to laze around to be
honest. It was great to watch to few late nights World Cup Football
matches live with Jishu. Saturday went to usual vegetable market at HAL.
After a quick and early lunch we went to southern part of Bangalore to
drop Jishu back home. It started to drizzle at first and very soon it
was pouring by the time we reached BTM layout.</description></item><item><title>Weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-24-weekend/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 18:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-06-24-weekend/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Aarush's-Free ride</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-05-11-aarushs-free-ride/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 22:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-05-11-aarushs-free-ride/</guid><description>Well another small post with pictures. These pictures of Aarush are
months apart. One on left with motorcycle are just after his tonsuring
and on the right are just weeks old. He really likes to ride like any
other boy. And if we try to stop him it does not go well at public
place. When we were in Star Bazaar @ Kormangala few weeks back he
remembered where this toy car was kept and every time we tried to
refrain him he used to go back there.</description></item><item><title>Whats happening</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-05-09-whats-happening/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 16:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-05-09-whats-happening/</guid><description>If long hours in the office and the phone calls at 2AM does fail to keep
me busy this is another Work in Progress which is keeping me recharged.</description></item><item><title>McAfee antivirus program freezes PCs</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-23-mcafee-antivirus-program-freezes-pcs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 17:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-23-mcafee-antivirus-program-freezes-pcs/</guid><description>After starting my office laptop it goes for freeze within 5 minutes. I
was very worried what went wrong; my current laptop is cranky and that
is why ordered a new one which was delivered yesterday. The new laptop
is getting build by the IT Team as I write this post. But i was worried
that I will lost all my data like a horror movie where every thing you
do goes wrong.</description></item><item><title>IKEA - made in India</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-23-ikea-made-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 01:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-23-ikea-made-in-india/</guid><description>It is no secret that I am a big fan
of IKEA&amp;rsquo;s clean cut design. And now every time I go outside of India try to pick something from there. Wished we got the whole modular
kitchen, beds, chest of drawers, leather sofa while moving back from
Paris. This time I visited IKEA store was next to Newark Airport(EWR,
NJ) and picked some small stuff for Aarush. When a neighbour looked at
the &amp;ldquo;Made in India&amp;rdquo; level asked from which store we picked up?</description></item><item><title>Thursday - Arab Street</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-19-thursday-arab-street/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 21:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-19-thursday-arab-street/</guid><description>Today was last day at Singapore. Packed everything night before so that
after breakfast we can check-out without much wasting of time.It was
holiday at Singapore as of some Muslim festival. My plan was to go to
Arab Street. This area has beautiful old shop houses that line the
streets. 
The highlight of the area is the grand Sultan Mosque, which was
crowded as people were coming out after prayers.</description></item><item><title>Wedneday- Visit to China town</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-wedneday-visit-to-china-town/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 17:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-wedneday-visit-to-china-town/</guid><description>It was the day to visit china town and particularly Buddha tooth
relic temple. The day was very bright with little could in the sky.
This is the view from our hotel room looking central Singapore Business
District.
After a good breakfast headed out of hotel. Got down by MRT at China
town &amp;amp; took exit to Pagoda street. One can&amp;rsquo;t miss the colorful row of
shop-houses along that street, with baby blue and yellow flowers painted
all over.</description></item><item><title>Hectic Tuesday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-hectic-tuesday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 14:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-hectic-tuesday/</guid><description>We woke up bit early; had heavy breakfast as usual. For today I have
already decided to go to Botanical garden in first half of the day.
So took a cab from hotel and I figured it was very nearby. This
botanical garden is must if you want to see the greenery and variety of
plants and flowers they have. Excellent maintenance, people come here
for jogging, picnic and touristy purpose.</description></item><item><title>Sleepy Monday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 11:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</guid><description>Monday morning mother-son woke up pretty late. Santanu already left for
office while we were in sleep. Around noon we went out of hotel to
nearby mall. Today I was not much interested in exploring rather looking
for kids activities. Spent almost half day at Toys R Us play area in
Paragon mall where Aarush enjoyed to fullest. He did not want to
give-up the car and was seating there for hours.</description></item><item><title>Jurong bird park</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-22-jurong-bird-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 18:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-22-jurong-bird-park/</guid><description>After a full day @ Santosa on Sunday we woke up pretty late. We decided
to go for Jurong bird park and offbeat track -Kong Meng San Phor
Kark See Monastery, is the largest monastery in Singapore.
We had breakfast at ChatterBox as the normal breakfast side was packed.
The menu was quite different from the normal side as we had lots of
traditional dishes to choose from. As usual Pamela had lots of dim-sum
and I preferred the usual cereal and fruits.</description></item><item><title>Visit to hungry tide- Sunderban</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 20:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</guid><description>For the first time in my life I spent more than 2 nights in a row at
Calcutta. The initial plan was to attend Papai’s wedding reception and
travel to some where around like Digha and back to Bangalore. We got our
Bangalore – Calcutta ticket booked. Going was by train to save money and
return was on flight so that we save time &amp;amp; energy before getting back
to our daily routine.</description></item><item><title>Aarush turns 2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-16-aarush-turns-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 22:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-16-aarush-turns-2/</guid><description>Aarush tuned 2. Need to add few pics from the party at home in Tata
Sherwood apratment</description></item><item><title>Day-3 Sentosa visit</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-11-day-3-sentosa-visit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-11-day-3-sentosa-visit/</guid><description>Saturday, we planned for Sentosa Island – Sentosa is the top tourist
attraction if you ask any Singaporean tourist information or locals.
Sentosa has it all – beach, corporate team building activities,
aquarium, great food and entertainment and soon there will be Casio and
entertainment park with roller coaster rides. We planned for complete
day-trip; as usual after heavy breakfast we went by metro to Harbour
Front MRT station. From there took Sentosa Express (Monorail train)
from Vivocity mall’s top floor.</description></item><item><title>A quick fix</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-06-a-quick-fix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-06-a-quick-fix/</guid><description>A quick post to start the year.</description></item><item><title>Friday - Black Peper Crab</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</guid><description>On Friday we woke up early; had
breakfast- an elaborate one. Me and Aarush after shower around 11am left
our hotel room. Today again we walked on other side of Orchard
Streettill Dhoby Ghat Station. Now
a days; I too feel sick like my hubby when too much time spent at malls
… am I growing old ? :D It was good to be in mall when it is raining.</description></item><item><title>First day @ Singapore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-21-first-day-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 05:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-21-first-day-singapore/</guid><description>Viewing Singapore through a lens of mother of 22 months old baby was not
fun all the time but enjoyed our stay there for 9 days. Actually this
journey is because of Santanu who went almost every year after returning
to India. Each time after his official trip he use to complain about his
loneliness and etc. So this time we made sure to accompany him. But what
a luck! he was damn busy in his office.</description></item><item><title>It came to an end</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-11-19-it-came-to-an-end/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-11-19-it-came-to-an-end/</guid><description>Officially it is over… ten month long journey came to an end. There were
two exams and one submission before pulling the final curtain by
November end.
Before writing further I must thank Pamela for persuading me in
enrolling in to this Executive MBA (EXMP) of IIM Bangalore.
The course in nutshell covers almost all the areas of management and
gives you enough foundation to build your own interest in specific area.</description></item><item><title>Tonsuring my baby’s head: Tirupati</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 13:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</guid><description>Ever since from childhood heard about Tirupati but never had a chance
till date or never understood why people use to grumble till they had
darshan. May be god wanted me to experience the same. Few days back
Santanu suddenly decided to visit before his upcoming hectic weeks at
office. So it was kind of planned-unplanned trip. Why unplanned
knowingly was&amp;hellip;.we didn&amp;rsquo;t had any ticket in hands before starting the
journey nor we had any references to make use of.</description></item><item><title>Another year passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 14:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</guid><description>Another year passed and more grey hairs to take care now. Well this time
I cut the cake at office with my team. Cake came off course from Cake
Walk. Well I never had any no birthday resolution there was no
difference this year as well. Big thanks to those who wished me on time
or belated. For others this post is few weeks old in itself.</description></item><item><title>Madras Filter Coffee</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 18:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is old an old one. My morning does not start
without coffee on weekdays. I am not quite human still have my
morning coffee will probably describe it best. In India coffee is very
different from West. I came to know recently that Indian Coffee Board
is head quartered in Bangalore. The main coffee producing region of
India(hills of Coorg, Niligiris and Wayanad&amp;gt;) are not very far off
Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>New widget with Media RSS</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-09-27-new-widget-with-media-rss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 22:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-09-27-new-widget-with-media-rss/</guid><description>It was a long time I played with new technology and changed any the way
the this blog looks to you. Liked few themes and tried to put them in
my own taste before I found the
current one. But some how those themes really did not looks so cool to
and attractive to me at the end. So I went with the current one and did
not did not did much changes.</description></item><item><title>Happy Durga Puja</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-09-22-happy-durga-puja/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 06:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-09-22-happy-durga-puja/</guid><description>Hello everyone, happy festivity it is time of celebration in India
specially north and east where it is NavaRatri in North and Durga Puja
in East. Pamela and Arush left on Sunday for Durg. It will be almost
after 8 years Pamela will be at her mother house to celebrate Durga
Puja. For Bengali&amp;rsquo;s it is the most special occasion in the whole
calender. According to mythological believe Goddess Durga is a daughter
of every Bengali and she visit her parents with her four children.</description></item><item><title>Seventh month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-15-seventh-month/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 13:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-15-seventh-month/</guid><description>(17th July-16th August)
Being uncertain about travel plans ahead we got his passport ready in
hurry-burry where my darling posed in front of camera without much
hesitation.
He can balance to sit unsupported but for short time while leaning
forward and spreading his legs out wide and straight for support. He
started to recognize people. On calling his name from back he use to
turn around to find where sounds come from.</description></item><item><title>Cost cutting Travel and more</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 07:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</guid><description>My last week trip to Singapore was a hectic one. Too many meetings and
meetings at work; best part is now a new Starbucks at Science Park
Drive is opened close to work; was very lucky where every other day got
pampered by my host with a coffee.
The flight from Bangalore was a nightmare I never experienced such
horrible service from any airline in my travel history. For Airlines
each seats are perishable commodities, which is lost as soon as the
flight takes off and it is a dream come true for Airline Company when
they have one.</description></item><item><title>Depuis Longtemps</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-21-depuis-longtemps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-21-depuis-longtemps/</guid><description>In recent time, there is no post in our blog. Few days back, newspaper
mentioned popular blogs are drying as &amp;ldquo;twitter or facebook&amp;rdquo; becomes
popular ways to communicate with readers. Many bloggers started to
update about themselves in social-site or micro-blogging using SMS and
original blog surffers. For us nothing as such happened; we just got
super busy from busy.
We were very happy that my younger brother and his wife took the pain to
come over to Bangalore (10-13thJuly).</description></item><item><title>Playing football</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-playing-football/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 06:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-playing-football/</guid><description>Aarush having nice time in green patch of IIM Bangalore Campus. Color of
ball and his T-shirt coincidently matched and isn&amp;rsquo;t that look nice on
green background? I took Pamela and Aarush to show them the southern
part of Bangalore which I am visiting quite often this year on academic
purpose. A great place to escape from routine life and bring back
memories of &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Purani Jeans Aur Guitar&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; days.</description></item><item><title>Vote for us The Great Driving Challenge !!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 05:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-07-04-vote-for-us-the-great-driving-challenge/</guid><description>We are inviting you to post your vote in support of travel. Visit our
application page by clicking on this link here.
Cast your vote and support
us.
This is our great grand escape plan
View GDC -
NH17
in a larger map</description></item><item><title>Aarush @ Swimming pool</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-24-aarush-swimming-pool/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 05:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-24-aarush-swimming-pool/</guid><description>During April and May Aarush and Pamela went to Swimming pool almost
daily for a few weeks. Every day around 10:30 or so he would make his
best effort to get his swimming gear and would ask us to put it for him.
But after few weeks we had to stop as we realized his cough was not
getting cured and he got lots of sun tan. And now after the operation he
is out of scope for any water sports for next one year.</description></item><item><title>Yelagiri</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-19-yelagiri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 00:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-19-yelagiri/</guid><description>Really do not recollect how I came first time to
Team-BHP web site, specifically their
forum. And from then on is kind of hooked though not a car freak myself
with limited understanding for these electro-mechanical wonders. What
fascinates me is travelogue section of this forum. It is great to find
so many passionate souls sharing their trips and tricks. Last November
got an unexpected mail about a meet-up @ Yelagiri for Bangalore
team-bhpean; was not sure to join or not.</description></item><item><title>Sixth month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-17-sixth-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 00:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-17-sixth-month/</guid><description>(17thJune - 16thJuly)
After rice ceremony at Siliguri we finally came to Bangalore. This time
he was fine both in train and plane. We stayed in service apartment for
3 nights till our things moved to our rented apartment.
Too many changes of weather, locations and little less care Aarush got
high fever for the first time and we had to rush him to Manipal. When it
settled we started to strolled within our apartment complex to know our
neighborhood more.</description></item><item><title>Madikeri and around</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-05-madikeri-and-around/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 18:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-06-05-madikeri-and-around/</guid><description>(&amp;hellip;.Continued&amp;hellip;)
Next day we woke up leisurely had a wonderful breakfast . Our host
meticulously wrote down all the attractions near Madikeri. The list
included Tala-Cauvery – birth place of river Kaveri, Raja seat,
Abby Falls, Omkareshwara Temple, Cauvery- Nisargadhama. We
decided for all except the last one as we wanted to take it easy and not
rushing between attractions.
As soon as we started driving to Madikeri (district headquarters of
Coorg) the real beauty of Coorg started to unveil itself.</description></item><item><title>Visit to OT</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-30-visit-to-ot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2009 05:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-30-visit-to-ot/</guid><description>Aarush was having cough for long time almost few months from now. Every
now and then it used to increase and then it subsided with cough syrup.
Every time we thought after a week of cough syrup treatment it will be
better but it somehow never got cured completely. In between, we tried
different &amp;ldquo;pathys&amp;rdquo; as suggested by experienced parents. Now last month
while he was getting immunization after 15th months doctor suggested to
visit ENT specialist because of prolonged cough and speech delay.</description></item><item><title>Little Tibet</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-26-little-tibet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 06:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-26-little-tibet/</guid><description>(&amp;hellip;.Continued) Soon after leaving Brindhavan garden and on touching
the highway (SH88) road condition improved which looked like recently
renovated. Aarush was fast asleep after having his lunch which always
translates in smooth driving and I was able to drive at 80-90 KM. Along
the road crossed Bilikere, Husur &amp;amp; Piriyapatna before reaching
Bylakuppe. It is an odd name which houses one of the largest Tibetan
settlement in India. We had to take a left turn from SH88 to go to the
monasteries.</description></item><item><title>Sondesh</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-21-sondesh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 12:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-21-sondesh/</guid><description>Bengalis are considered as food-lovers (khadya-rashik).For them any
sumptuous bengali meal is always incomplete without a sweet dish. Just
like any french meal which would remain incomplete without a bottle of
exquisite french wine.
I was not a big fan of sweet earlier but when you live with someone for
a long period of time, you quickly start to adapt some of your partner’s
habits be it deliberately or inadvertently.</description></item><item><title>Fifth Month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-15-fifth-month/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 05:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-15-fifth-month/</guid><description>May 17- June 16
By 5th month slowly started introducing solid food like banana and
apple puree to Aarush. According to our custom till
&amp;ldquo;Annaprasanna&amp;rdquo;
we are not suppose to introduce solid food like rice or wheat to baby.
And his didu was also against using common baby food item like &amp;ldquo;Cerelac&amp;rdquo;
as they contain rice or wheat. This resulted in his first solid bite
being fruit &amp;ndash; mashed banana. The first spoon he swallowed as my mom
fed him, but little man has a frown of disapproval, like &amp;ldquo;what the heck
they are feeding me?</description></item><item><title>Coolie</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-09-coolie/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2009 12:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-09-coolie/</guid><description>These people in red shirts are commonly known as “coolie” or porters
who are commonly seen at Indian Railway Station. They remind me of those
childhood days when they were part of our vacation (mass aviation is
still in infancy at India). They help to carry big over sized luggage
that Indian travelers travel with. As Indian travelers are not that
physically fit like westerners to lift their own luggage.</description></item><item><title>Gallerry 3 sneak peak</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-08-gallerry-3-sneak-peak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-05-08-gallerry-3-sneak-peak/</guid><description>Gallery 3 is
going to a big change from current gallery 2 and initial alpha release
did not have any migration path from gallery2. It was pushed to Beta
release after 2 alpha releases. but to my surprise I found it was
implemented in alpha 4 and here is the test result of a new neat code. I
am really liking the new compact code making gallery 3 faster and lean
compared to its predecessor.</description></item><item><title>playing with bubbles</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-28-playing-with-bubbles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 04:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-28-playing-with-bubbles/</guid><description>Aarush and Pamela playing with soap bubbles ; this video is bit old when
he did not started walking at that point of time. He was bit amused with
bubbles trying to catch them but could not.</description></item><item><title>Fourth month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</guid><description>(17th April - 16th May)
Normally A is taken to doctor for monthly check-up once other then that
no outing for him. As he is considered too small for all these by my
parents. So they neither allow him nor me to go anywhere. After birth it
was third time when Aarush was taken out of the house to meet people
other then his doc&amp;rsquo;s clinic. Moreover because of weather it was
difficult for us to go anywhere.</description></item><item><title>Third month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-15-third-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 11:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-15-third-month/</guid><description>(17th March-16th April)
Now, Aarush started to twitch, smile, frown and stretch a lot after
waking from sleep. Amazingly ( I never knew this) and apparently babies
between three to four months are at the stage where they get very
playful and drinking milk is not a priority anymore, I believe. They
prefer to talk and coo to adults, and being very observant at this stage
and they are attracted to moving objects, colours and everything new
around them.</description></item><item><title>Wayanad-III</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-14-wayanad-iii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-14-wayanad-iii/</guid><description>On second day we went to see Lakidi view point, Phookot lake and
Vythiri resort. Lakidi is about 2 km south of Chain Tree and is the
gateway of Wayanad which is on highway to Calicut. It is a ghat pass at
an elevation of 700m above sea level.We crossed Kalpetta and drove
mostly on NH 212.
Overwhelmed with scenery as this highway is heaven on this earth , a
beautiful place with lot of tea gardens on the way.</description></item><item><title>Wayanad-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-13-wayanad-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 12:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-13-wayanad-ii/</guid><description>After a deep slumber the next morning we woke-up fresh and energetic.
Aarush wanted to play seeing an open space- courtyard. They have toys,
cycles, carom board, badminton court, balls to play with. He was really
happy to get all these stuffs. What more parent wants if kid is happy
you are happy otherwise nothing on earth can make you happy.
Morning, we were shown all rooms available there. It was a nice room
with a central common area and one room each on either side.</description></item><item><title>Visit to North kerala- Wayanad</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 06:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-12-visit-to-north-kerala-wayanad/</guid><description>From the time Santanu having classes and top of it exams this month; its
really a grueling month for both of us. For this I too was not getting
some time off from “Our little one”. There was absolute need of one
break. Santanu suddenly said two days before last exam that he is having
leave and if interested then we can go somewhere near by. Then he only
started reading on net and ended up saying we would go to
WAYANAD- Northern region of Kerala.</description></item><item><title>Second month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-04-second-month/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 01:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-04-second-month/</guid><description>(17th February- 17th March)
Parenthood is a lifelong journey. No amount of training and
preparation can ever prepare fully for it. We are learning about our
little helpless bundle and same probably on his side. After returning
from official trip santanu was agog to spent more time with Aarush as if
it was ages he has spent not seeing him.
Aarush now learnt to squeal in delight as his arms flail about in the
air above him.</description></item><item><title>Playing trumpet</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-03-playing-trumpet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 23:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-03-playing-trumpet/</guid><description>Aarush playing trumpet, he was around 11 months old that time and did
not started walking but was master of climbing and crawling.</description></item><item><title>Birthday Video</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-03-birthday-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 05:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-04-03-birthday-video/</guid><description>A long waited video from Aarush&amp;rsquo;s Birthday. This is a unedited video of
16 minutes long, I have no knowledge on video editing. The video was
captured by Jishu-Dadu of
Aarush.
The video quality after uploading to Google does not seem that great,
let us know your feedback. Going to publish few more videos of Aarush
soon.</description></item><item><title>IPL 2.0</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-23-ipl-2-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 23:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-23-ipl-2-0/</guid><description>IPL – Indian Premier League goes out of India. You do not need to be a
cricket fan to follow this news as it is every where. I am literally out
raged with this news can you think suddenly British (Barclay)
premiership moves to Spain as cold winter stormed as swapped across
Britain. Mr.Lalit Modi is a big favorite be it media or those franchisee
owners but certainly things will be different after this summer.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holi</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-11-happy-holi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 05:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-11-happy-holi/</guid><description>Have a safe holi; this picture was taken on night before celebrating
holi-ka-dahan</description></item><item><title>First month</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-07-first-month/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-07-first-month/</guid><description>Tiredness was still there after delivery and by now I realized what
people were talking about… shamelessly take advantage of this period to
rest yourself. On other hand I was desperate to take a step outside
house of my own after 9 months bed rest to feel the breeze brushing
against my skin. But it never happened because of customs.
Ooof&amp;hellip;. On 10th day took a complete shower from head to toe as on
same day my stitch was removed which took hardly few minutes.</description></item><item><title>Drive to heritage site - Lepakshi</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-03-03-drive-to-heritage-site-lepakshi/</guid><description>My 1st term is coming to an end and we are given the upcoming test as
well project submission dates. On reaching home from class on Saturday I
was desperate to go out of Bangalore to get charged to combat the
upcoming gruelling weeks at work and personal front with study. I had no
clue where to go for a day and started to check my faithful websites and
zeroed on Lepakshi from Anita’s
site.</description></item><item><title>Birth of a Mother-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-25-birth-of-a-mother-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 05:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-25-birth-of-a-mother-ii/</guid><description>Truly said-
The moment a child is born,the mother is also born.She never existed
before.The woman existed, but the mother, never.A mother is something
absolutely new.
~Rajneesh
As soon as I was moved out of O.T. Aarush was brought to his crib next
to me. His didu was first to hold him in her arms then was given
forcefully to his thamma. She didn&amp;rsquo;t wanted to take him as it seems he
would become &amp;ldquo;Kol-lengra&amp;rdquo; (will get use to be in arms).</description></item><item><title>Birth of a Mother-I</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-22-birth-of-a-mother-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 03:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-22-birth-of-a-mother-i/</guid><description>It was 11th Jan when I went to my gynecologist in emergency as
couldn&amp;rsquo;t feel the movements. After check-up she mentioned that if my
baby didn&amp;rsquo;t arrive anytime sooner than 15 she would have to perform an
induction. She didn&amp;rsquo;t wanted to take any risk at this stage because of
cervical incompetence and heart problem. So at last, we opted for
planned c-section on 17th Jan.
Night before took admission at MGM Belapur, Navi Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Feeling the Kicks</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-19-feeling-the-kicks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 04:48:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-19-feeling-the-kicks/</guid><description>Friends and near ones use to ask me quite often then - Do you feel the
movement?
No (use to be my reply).
Somewhere, I use to wonder how it feels like the movement of the baby
inside. It was tough to answer as first timer. On routine check -up my
doctor asked the same whether I feel the movement and I nodded in
negative. Immediately asked her how it actually feels.</description></item><item><title>Road trip to Mysore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-17-road-trip-to-mysore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 04:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-17-road-trip-to-mysore/</guid><description>Applied for a whole week off in December as I had 25+ days off to
take for year 2008 - this gave us 9 days off with two weekends. I
preferred a week before Christmas to avoid traffic and tourist.
Initial plan was to leave Bangalore on Sunday for Mysore and move
from there depending on Aarush&amp;rsquo;s comfort. Stepping out of the home with
him means a disrupted routine and adapting to a new environment for all
us.</description></item><item><title>Lavazza in India</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 18:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</guid><description>Just saw this advertisement on BBC website while checking my morning
dose of news. I was quite fascinated by this ad. Immediately started to
think “Oh this is great!!” now I can get a great coffee to start my
day at home by pressing a button.
If you are not familiar with this machine or not a coffee person this
machine uses special coffee capsules to dispense coffee. There are
varieties of flavor to choose from and trust me it really makes great
coffee.</description></item><item><title>My baby shower</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 15:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</guid><description>My
baby shower was done in the Bengali traditional way which is called as
Saadh in Bengali. It is meant mostly to pamper the first-time mother
to be and cheer her up as she accumulates courage to face the most
testing time in her life which will soon change her life in and out.
Normally, held in the seventh or ninth month of pregnancy on a
specified day when mother-in-law will organize this ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Journey to Motherhood</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-04-journey-to-motherhood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 15:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-04-journey-to-motherhood/</guid><description>Remembering my journey to motherhood as Aarush turns one year old. After
4 years of marriage and lot of traveling around Europe Santanu decided
to move back to India to find a better professional career. Life as
couple was not full of hip and happening but we were happy and carefree
about the same. I use to scorn at people whenever brought up kids in
topic; balked at elders. After getting back to India this pressure was
getting on me.</description></item><item><title>Joyeux Anniversaire- mon petit</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-02-03-joyeux-anniversaire-mon-petit/</guid><description>As usual there is lots of gaps of posting. Last month was quite hectic
as we celebrated Aarush&amp;rsquo;s first birthday
We started planning from December onwards. As our schedule now revolves
around his nap-time and whims we hardly get time for each other or to
discuss any matter it’s just a lot more rare these days than it used to
be. So, gone are the days of last minute plan. Despite how he has
completely turned our lives upside down we wanted to celebrate his first
b&amp;rsquo;day which I know he hardly will acknowledge at this age.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 17:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</guid><description>**Happy New Year everyone!!!**. Wish
you all the best for next 361 days; already late by two days to post the
first one of &amp;lsquo;09.Only one resolution we take &amp;ndash; that is to update our blog often and
complete the list of posts we are supposed to for long time; there are
some of travelogue too to complete. Keep coming back and put your
comments that really makes us going.</description></item><item><title>2008 - mixed bag</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 17:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</guid><description>Thinking of 2008&amp;hellip; it was an eventful year. We started by adding a new
member to our family after going through lot of apprehension. Now our
new world started to revolve around baby with umpteen number of diaper
changes and sleepless nights, his cries, bowel movement and what
not&amp;hellip;..
Pamela&amp;rsquo;s parents were at Mumbai to help us in our happily tough times.
Even before completing two months Aarush left Mumbai for Pamela&amp;rsquo;s
hometown.</description></item><item><title>Peekaboo</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-11-peekaboo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2008 05:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-11-peekaboo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>chocolate Banana Muffins</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</guid><description>First weekend of December past with lots of activities - a trip to
commercial street, malls and office. On Saturday Aarush forced me to
leave bed early - deprived me of extended sleeping on the weekend. After
that I was busy with him mostly for breakfast. Nowadays he has developed
a nasty habit of prolonged (around an hour or more) eating times be it
breakfast, lunch or dinner. After that he played for while but soon he
was sleepy for nap.</description></item><item><title>Wear the red Ribbon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-01-wear-the-red-ribbon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 23:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-01-wear-the-red-ribbon/</guid><description>December 1st 2008- World AIDS Day - today, AIDS is one of the main
causes of mortality on the planet. 33 million people are HIV-positive in
the world, but 90 % of them ignore it. Given the numbers, there is a
definite need to increase the awareness levels about the disastrous
effects of this incurable disease.
I am sure there are plenty online about the same which can be accessed
quickly but the main problem remains in uneducated rural areas where it
is not even mentioned forget about a healthy discussion.</description></item><item><title>Change</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-21-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 19:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-21-change/</guid><description>In last 20 months “change” was one of most used word thanks to new
President elect Obama. I admire the way he delivers speeches and uses
words. Most reporters must be missing those malapropian phrases used in
last 8 years.
I took this picture in February at Mumbai Airport; personally I too was
thinking about the change and transition I was going trough at work and
home at that time.</description></item><item><title>Back to Bangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-21-back-to-bangalore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 06:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-21-back-to-bangalore/</guid><description>It is almost a month posted any thing on the blog. It’s neither that
boring nor that there are not enough events happening in our life which
can be shared with you. It is just that we do not have any time for
ourselves where we can sit and relax which sometime looks like a very
remote luxury now.The day starts quite early at around 6:30 when Pamela
gets up and prepares breakfast for Aarush ; that allows some extra sleep
for me if Aarush permits.</description></item><item><title>As time flies...</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 06:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</guid><description>We feel elated to celebrate our sixth year of togetherness @ IndiJoe. A
journey full of sweet, bitter, sour, spicy and many more&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; flavours.
After all soft items like paper, linen etc finally we reached
anniversary which is represented by metal -&amp;ldquo;Iron
Anniversary&amp;rdquo;.
This year&amp;rsquo;s anniversary is extra special because we were given a very
precious gift from God, our son Aarush, and now we&amp;rsquo;ve moved on from
&amp;ldquo;couple&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;small family&amp;rdquo;, and it feels amazing.</description></item><item><title>Long Time no see ...</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-10-29-long-time-no-see/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 07:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-10-29-long-time-no-see/</guid><description>Well we are still connected to internet just not having enough time to
spare to post. There are few posts which are long overdue. Only time we
can type in peace when Aarush is sleeping but by that time we are so
tired that we retire quickly. Do not worry will post more often as we
try to get back into a more strict routine. BTW I just registered myself
in Facebook after lots of deliberation.</description></item><item><title>Wish Pamela</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-09-17-wish-pamela/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 23:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-09-17-wish-pamela/</guid><description>If you are reading this post on 17th September please call up, e-mail if
you have not done so yet.
Well why I am writing this post &amp;ndash; I am stuck in a business trip and
missing her and Aarush for last 3 weeks. Sometime I wish I just could
dump my current job and spend some quality time with Family. But with
Financial commitment I don’t think I can do that soon :(.</description></item><item><title>Extempo Performance</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-28-extempo-performance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 04:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-28-extempo-performance/</guid><description>Pamela&amp;rsquo;s maternal cousin
Jeet
was our guest in Bangalore for three nights from Calcutta. His purpose
of this trip to meet his school and college mates as most of them are
working in Bangalore IT sector. Jeet plays guitar and mouth organ as
hobbies. His musical talent is in his gene , he got it from his
mother
who is a trained singer and used to perform in All India Radio in her
young days.</description></item><item><title>ZoneAlarm Patch Tuesday Promotion</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-13-zonealarm-patch-tuesday-promotion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 00:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-13-zonealarm-patch-tuesday-promotion/</guid><description>Get yourself a free copy of Zone
Alarm Firewall completely free for one year. The offer is valid for one
PC per e-mail id. The offer just started at 6AM PST and will be there
for next 24 hours. So do not waste your time and rush to get a free
copy. If you are not sure what Zone Alarm is and why you need
one copy or a similar product for your PC I am sure there are zillion of
web pages to guide you.</description></item><item><title>Rejuvenating old I-Pod</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-07-rejuvenating-old-i-pod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 21:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-08-07-rejuvenating-old-i-pod/</guid><description>Our old faithful I-pod’s
battery died last year; nothing to complain about the same. We have used
it enough and did not have any complain. Only thing that happened is the
battery started to loose charge more often and at the end it stopped
charging altogether. Just after I got this I-Pod, Apple had to settle a
lawsuit for low
quality batteries. That way I must say I am happy to survive for 3 years
with one battery.</description></item><item><title>Whatz FRESH about Reliance Fresh ?</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</guid><description>As we are new to Bangalore trying to explore all nearby hypermarket,
supermarket and open markets as we settle in. This is also giving us as
chance to explore places around. The first one we tried and explored was
BIG-BAZAR on Old Madras road. As it is just near to one of our
office address in Bangalore I knew how to reach there without being
lost. Then weekend after we tried SPAR at Kormongala followed by
Nilgiris.</description></item><item><title>Bombay to Bangalore by Car(NH4)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-17-bombay-to-bangalore-by-car-nh4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 02:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-17-bombay-to-bangalore-by-car-nh4/</guid><description>View Larger
MapA journey of 1000 KM from Mumbai to
Bangalore
I was asked to reallocate to Bangalore in early May from my work; as
usual had no plan till the last minute. Sitting in Durg (center of
India) was thinking what will be best way to reach Bangalore on Monday
via Mumbai. I have to reach Mumbai to pick my bare essential before
heading south. And my flight from Durg was on Saturday noon.</description></item><item><title>Wordpress 2.6</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-15-wordpress-2-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 20:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-07-15-wordpress-2-6/</guid><description>Just upgraded to Wordpress
2.6 for
both blog.santm.com and
pamela.santm.com without any hitch :)
Upgraded few plugins as well and so far so good.</description></item><item><title>We are @ Bangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-06-20-we-are-bangalore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 16:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-06-20-we-are-bangalore/</guid><description>This post is going to be a quick one, need to write and publish in next
8 minutes time I have from my grueling schedule. Just to let you know we
(this time Aarush &amp;amp; Pamela accompanied me) reached safely after
traveling from west to central-part to east and then to south of India .
The details of long travel will require several small posts but with
Aarush, new apartment and work do not think we will be left with ample
time to write those.</description></item><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Our sleeping beauty</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</guid><description>Aarush never likes to sleep when ever we tried to tuck his hands&amp;hellip;.I
mean with buritto wrap. If wrapped he keeps on moving his hands in
discomfort until he is unwrapped. He always loves to have his hands
free, outstretched in upward direction. This series of pictures which
were taken during half an hour cat&amp;rsquo;s nap. So many positions for two
little hands :D</description></item><item><title>Letter to my son</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 23:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-15-letter-to-my-son/</guid><description>Hello Aarush,
Today you are four months old&amp;hellip;though nothing remarkable but for me it
has been days now since we met last. Hope you to be fit as fiddle.
I came to know from your mom that now your vision is focused more or
less, you are trying to grasp objects; can bat and swipe at dangling
toys. It seems now you are ready to rock and roll as you have started
taking side turns with squirms, giggles and wails&amp;hellip; You respond to your
nani (granny) and aunt with big toothless smiles as well with coos and
making happy noises.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye – Mumbai – a quick update</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</guid><description>I
did not want to use a title like “Welcome to Bangalore” or “Here I
come to Bangaloru” on purpose as need some time before I can call this
my new home. From long time we were knowing that we have to move to
Banglore but on personal grounds I had to postpone it which was readily
accepted by my company. In recent months, I was waiting for that green
signal from my company that I have to move in any case.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Parking</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-18-perfect-parking/</guid><description>Encountered this perfect parking on a small by-lane in Bangalore. For
sure I will not be able to park like this; normally have enough
difficulties in parallel parking on the street between cars. I was
failed (fatal) as rear tire touched the ramp in my first attempt to
secure Californian driving License. Looks like the owner will not be
change car as this is customized parking only which can accommodate
small car.</description></item><item><title>Nagaon - a sleepy sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-12-nagaon-a-sleepy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 22:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-12-nagaon-a-sleepy-sunday/</guid><description>Currently I am spending my life as forced bachelor with Pamela ‘n’
Aarush at Durg. I was looking for an outing from a long time as
completely burn-out with new and old responsibilities at personal and
professional level. Spending weekends, doing absolutely nothing other
than sleeping and delaying all household work for next weekend. Made few
phone calls here and there to old friends to know about their latest
updates.</description></item><item><title>Shiv Jayanti</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid><description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night of
lord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindu
mythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birth
anniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17th
century fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He was
named Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabai
had prayed for a son.</description></item><item><title>Bhat Suar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid><description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”
(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my college
days. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of same
state 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similar
to an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”
and second part “suar which means pig”.</description></item><item><title>Geography - mismatch</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 05:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-13-geography-mismatch/</guid><description>For any fifth grader Mumbai is located in Western part of India if asked
north or south answer will be south. So how can there be a church of
North India which is located in posh south Mumbai in a stone throw
distance from famous Flora Fountain? You may wonder - in the world of
bharat-todo (Break India by new politicians) how all bhaia&amp;rsquo;s(people from
North India Bihar and Uttarpradesh - speaking Hindi) suddenly built a
church for themselves.</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Hebbal Lake</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid><description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress on
construction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as at
work things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is a
nice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes a
happy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in next
month this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that is
going to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description></item><item><title>SMS received</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 18:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</guid><description>As I said before I went to hospital on d-day with my Laptop and all
cables needed for announcing the arrival of Aarush. Few starring eyes
caught me in action when I did fired-up SMS from my laptop. There was no
way I could have managed sending all SMS(es) by phone only. So, I had to
send SMS in batches : one to my professional contacts, other to extended
family and rest to Pamela&amp;rsquo;s contact list.</description></item><item><title>Free Theme</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-13-free-theme/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 15:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-13-free-theme/</guid><description>I just found out d-atmosphere.com is holding a competition where they
are offering a free wordpress theme called WP
Remix. It’s a very nice theme with loads
of features.
The rule is simple - just write about the competition in your blog and
post your link back in the comments on the contest page.
The winner will be announced on March 1st.</description></item><item><title>Indian Inglish</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</guid><description>The biggest asset of 21st century modern India is its big chunk of young
educated Indian who can speak decent English. There is lot of buzz and
business happening in India as there are numerous outsourcing
operations.
But on the ground we speak very different English with borrowed words
from Indian regional languages that do find their way into our writing,
advertisements and newspapers, TV spots and shows from north to south or
east to west.</description></item><item><title>An announcement</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 01:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</guid><description>This announcement was long due on our blog. Though this breaking news
was shared on d-day instantly with friends and families from Hospital
via SMS and emails. I specifically carried my camera, laptop and
wireless data card for the same.
I created two announcement cards one in pink and other in blue with two
names (for girl and boy) and kept them ready. We never disclosed this
big-news in last few months in our blog in-fact it was kept secret to
many except close family members and few friends.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary- Potsdam</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</guid><description>Today sun and clouds chase each other across the skies along the shores
of Berlin as it glides past. We decided to visit Potsdam city situated
on southwest of Berlin known for Sanssouci (without worries) palace;
reached there by train.
As we were short of time having our return ticket to Paris same evening
we opted for sight-seeing guided tour bus available right outside the
train station. So along with other tourists we visited new palace, old
town hall, Fortunaportal and Nikolaikirche at Alter Markt, Schloss
Cecilienhof, Potsdam’s Brandenburg gate, Dutch colony, Russian colony
Alexandrowka providing flair of a city steeped in European tradition.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Venice at leisure</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid><description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after two
days of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s
Square. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was too
crowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out of
time and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.
Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear end
which is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description></item><item><title>Half day at Florence and Venice</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-26-half-day-at-florence-and-venice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 20:23:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-26-half-day-at-florence-and-venice/</guid><description>After spending three nights in Florence it was time to move on. We
packed and checked out, keeping our luggage in the hotel. We walked
towards Palazzo Vecchio (Piazza della Signoria) - city square
adorned with fine arts. Basically, Florence is full of timeless beauty
which can keep you captivated. Close to this square is Uffizi which
we reached by 8:30 AM for our visit. Uffizi’s structure is like a long
rectangle; it is not very big in structure like other top European
museums.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>Florence</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-24-florence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2007 20:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-24-florence/</guid><description>Yesterday, late evening when we reached Florence it was drizzling and
continued raining during the night. We got up to find grey sky - a very
big disappointment compared to last few days as we had picture perfect
blue sky. We also had to take out light jackets as temperature dropped.
The hotel we stayed was not great but it was clean and functional in the
centre of city even we could see the dome of famous cathedral from our
hotel room window.</description></item><item><title>An afteroon at Pisa</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</guid><description>Being exhausted from last evening we got up bit late and had very good
breakfast before hitting the road. According to our itinerary, distance
to be covered was long one as our hotel was booked at Florence.
We took train to La Spezia, it was a crowded, got packed with each
passing stations of Cinque Terre but became empty as soon as we
crossed Riomaggiore. We had to wait a bit at La Spezia as train was
coming from north was late.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Tomato Soup</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 20:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</guid><description>Till far only soup ever tried to make was carrot soup in Paris that too
in bleak winter. Big thanks to my French Teacher for sharing the
recipe en Français. Recently, went to local vegetable market; seeing
tomato got so tempted that without thinking bought two kilos. Then I
brainstormed a bit to think and idea of soup came as an escape. Here is
my 2 cents recipe. If craving for something sweet and sour at the
same time just have a bowl of creamy tomato soup to satisfy your desire
as an appetizer.</description></item><item><title>Playing with shutter speed</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 18:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-playing-with-shutter-speed/</guid><description>Love taking pictures with long shutter speed at night - technique is
very simple. All I needed was a tripod to secure camera from shaking
while leaving the camera shutter open. I know this is not a great
picture but that is what I got from my balcony. A better one with
Kharghar landmark Utsav Chowk is posted
here.</description></item><item><title>Got G(oogle)-Phone</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-got-g-oogle-phone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-12-got-g-oogle-phone/</guid><description>Well downloaded G-Phone application from
Google. on my Blackberry. All I needed was
data access enabled phone to download G-phone. The speculation was
running high about a new hardware from Google in lots of web sites. Lets
see how these applications (Gmail, Google maps, Google news, Google
search, Gtalk, Google calender) will work on a normal phone where the
display is not as big as Blackberry and you do not have full keyboard or
track wheel.</description></item><item><title>Festival of lights</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</guid><description>Today as we celebrate India’s grand festival of Light signaling triumph
over evil after a protracted fight which is marked by lighting of oil
based traditional earthen or clay lamps as they shine brightly in each
and every home - Be it lowly or mightily from the hut of the poor to the
mansion of the rich when good with all its might, leads us from darkness
to light. A day when old and young indulge in royal feast on this
festival of snacks and sweet.</description></item><item><title>Sunsets in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 21:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Sunset with blue sky of late October seems “magnifique” along with open
space of Navi Mumbai as viewed from local train (picture taken through
window)
This one I clicked last Saturday when I was stuck in middle of JJ
Flyover - the longest flyover in Mumbai (2.3 KM). It is constructed like
a snake, which makes its way through labyrinth of old buildings on
either side; basically you bypass the busy, crowded market underneath.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Belgium</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</guid><description>While categorizing our old travelogs I found there was no post on
Belgium
which values a lot for me. As I go down the memory lane&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;year 2003,
within 2 ½ months of marriage we have to move to Paris from US which was
a big change for me. Apart from the cultural shock, language was immense
barrier for day today life as well to mingle up with people around. Not
only that, in Indian arrange marriage, it takes time to understand each
other with each one&amp;rsquo;s weaknesses and failings.</description></item><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>Sweet potato dessert</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</guid><description>Sweet potato dessert (Ranga Alur Puli) is an age old Bengali dessert - a
sweet lover&amp;rsquo;s delight for sure. Its crispy outer layer mesmerizes
gastronomic senses. As for its availability, it is more of a
traditional sweet, prepared in households. These days some sweet shops
are starting to include this in their repertoire to cater to the
time-constrained generation.
My hubby being born with a sweet tooth, do enjoy sweet of any kind.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Thread of love</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</guid><description>It is a celebration of unconditional love between brother and sister in
Hindu culture. This age old celebration tries to remind us of the
beautiful and unique relationship between brother and sister celebrated
since time immemorial. Sisters tie sacred threads on brothers wrist
asking for longer &amp;amp; healthy life of brother and brothers in-turn vow to
protect (to save her- Raksha) their sisters from any unpleasant
situations of life on this day.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Arrived Singapore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-23-arrived-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 20:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-23-arrived-singapore/</guid><description>Reached Singapore on a business trip for about 26 days. Will try to
post more often as I explore Singapore from my angle.</description></item><item><title>Bombay International Airport</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid><description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far as
my International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is getting
better and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the pictures
for the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictures
looks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may be
not …quality wise.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</guid><description>Looking at those plastic chairs brought back my memories of
Anandamela (a Bengali
children magazine - published fortnight. They used to have picture of
common objects in obscure way and you have to identify the same. I know
this picture is a far cry from those -any way some sweet memories to
reflect upon from fourth floor while taking this picture.
In India celebration is part of life whether big or small ones.</description></item><item><title>Cart in city road</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 21:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</guid><description>While coming to work this morning oxen (castrated male) cart
carrying sugar canes caught my attention. It is not a common site to see
a bullock cart or hand pulled cart (pulled or pushed by a man) at the
heart of Mumbai city next to VT Station.
They are not allowed in the main roads of the city but can only move in
the peripheral roads of the city. These kinds of slow moving objects
cause most notorious traffic jam in India.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</guid><description>This picture was taken from my phone camera when I went to do our weekly
vegetable shopping in APMC [Agro Product Market] close to Vashi.
Prices for every vegetables went up. Due to lack of infrastructure it
was a shame to see so much wastage due to heavy rain. From the posture
of the seller it was quite clear he was not looking for lot of customers
as he stretches his back.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Courtesy still … in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-31-courtesy-still-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 04:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-31-courtesy-still-in-mumbai/</guid><description>With all its busy, speedy life I found courtesy still existing within in
Mumbai-local; an unexpected encounter with refined human behavior in
this Maximum city. I was retuning home in a local train and lucky to be
seated as I started from VT terminus. In the mid way a family of three
boarded the train; it is quite out of the way for a female passenger to
get into general or male compartment at the rush hour.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item><item><title>Skittlish Theme with Silk Icons for Wordpress</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-25-skittlish-theme-with-silk-icons-for-wordpress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2007 21:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-25-skittlish-theme-with-silk-icons-for-wordpress/</guid><description>Trying to jazz up skittlish theme of
wordpress
with silk icon sets from
famfamfam.com.
In recent time there is new version of skittlish supporting widgets so I
thought it might be a god starting ground. Best part - for few colors
(red, orange, green &amp;amp; blue) there are icons available for tag, user
(author). But for rest there is none. As I am not a graphic person not
sure how should I go forward.</description></item><item><title>China rose</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid><description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soul
into. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit if
they fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,
the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No one
wants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description></item><item><title>W questions of Indian life</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</guid><description>In India, life of middle class is different compared to occidental
culture. There is a vast population of middle class in India and within
middle class there are three distinct sub-divisions - “lower
middleclass”, “middle middleclass” and “higher middleclass”.
Comprehending the complexities of Indian society is not that easy.
Though there are variations in socio-economic life within these three
but one thing is common between all of them - everyone is curious to
know whatz happening in others life despite of their own busy life.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Adios</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 05:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</guid><description>Last day, woke up very early in the morning to visit Candolim, Sinquerim
beach- Just to avoid scorching heat of sun. The shimmering sea stretches
to the horizon. Spent some time to savour the view then headed to Fort
Aguada. Fort Agauda crowns the rocky flattened headland at the end of
the beach. Constructed in 1612 to protect the northern shores of Mandovi
estuary from Dutch and Maratha raiders. It was a reference point for the
vessels coming from Europe at that time.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid><description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arranged
for two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. We
opted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in a
non-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary included
Dona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilica
and se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurga
dedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit to
Ancestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid><description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperative
if you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedom
but can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggled
at least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activa
for Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get good
price). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim to
visit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid><description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I got
opportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, I
couldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarried
Indian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as an
escort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered like
friend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description></item><item><title>Little Visitor at Office Window</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 22:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</guid><description>Friday again, I am already at work for last nine hours(reached around
8ish). Wow! that&amp;rsquo;s lot and time to head towards home soon.
Today, after lots of failure attempt I some how succeeded to capture a
very cute visitor at my window. I have no idea what kind of bird is
this, going to ask one expert for the same. Well, Pamela is working very
hard to upload pictures from Goa and writing trip details – hope this
weekend we upload them.</description></item><item><title>Wordpress Bleeding 2.2 and TAG</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-10-wordpress-bleeding-2-2-and-tag/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2007 15:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-10-wordpress-bleeding-2-2-and-tag/</guid><description>Just upgraded to the latest beta trunk of wordpress 2.2(bleeding) and
found myself with unrecoverable errors. Realized wordpress incorporated
tagging within the core but the old faithful Ultimate Tag Warrior does
not work any more :( Found another bug-hunt has started and hope for tag import from (UTW)
till then …… have to live with out tags Sigh!</description></item><item><title>Mumbaiya Lingo</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 03:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</guid><description>While boarding a train I heard one co-passenger saying to another
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” which astonished me for a fraction of
second as its not at all palatable to an untrained ears. It seems this
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” is considered far more effective while getting
into locals then long winded formal request to the people ahead to make
way.
I was trying hard to relate as it sounds hindi but actually its not.</description></item><item><title>Mera Bharat Jawaan</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 22:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</guid><description>Another funny advertisement which caught my attention Budda Hoga Tera
Baap. This is a soft or hard slang depending on your view - &amp;ldquo;May be
your father is old&amp;rdquo; This new TV series name is &amp;ldquo;Mera Bharat
Jaawan&amp;rdquo; which translates into &amp;ldquo;My India is Young&amp;rdquo;. With one fourth
population under the age of 25 India definitely has young demography.
P.S - In last two months, I have changed theme for wordpress (blog) at
least four times.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine -II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 19:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</guid><description>As I said lots of thoughts were coming
across in spite of
my busy-ness. So first was to ask Pamela to come over at Fort area for
lunch which was denied by her saying that lots of household chores left
to be done. Then again I modified my plan and asked her to join at
evening for dinner when she told me she won’t as without any prior
booking no food will be available at any good restaurant because of that
day- which is in fact quite true.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 18:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</guid><description>Another view of Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s Ballard Pier from my desk. May be I am too busy
between meetings so no time to romance with my valentine. Well, heart
shape balloons floating around our office here and there reminding me of
the special day. Due to meetings and tight schedule I even missed the
chocolate distribution. C&amp;rsquo;est dommage!!! :( . Although enormous
work-pressure but many thoughts are coming across to make evening
better.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Micro$oft Launch @ Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</guid><description>Micro$oft is doing a round of business and technical launch show around
India. The products are Exchange 2007, Office 2007 and Vista. I attended
only a brief session @ Hyatt.
Well, somehow my name was not there even though I registered 10 days
before the event.
And my business card with orange and blue dots did not help much to get
attention from those desk people. Anyway, it was solid 40 minutes of
work for me – replied emails, chat with business contact got updates
from their team – thanks to CDMA mobile card.</description></item><item><title>Zooomr Pro</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-16-zooomr-pro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-16-zooomr-pro/</guid><description>After trying my luck with flickr I figured out that I have to look for
alternative. With Yahoo! there is nothing for free. Almost certainly
they will follow suit when someone else win in their own game like gmail
vs yahoo-mail. So trying my luck for Zooomr pro now.
P.S. I got the pro account :D</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>A dark post</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 02:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</guid><description>Well this post is a dark one-
Aaj fir dil hai kuchh udaas udaasjaane kyun ek mayusi si chhayi haiaaj
fir palkon pe pani haibheer mein hoon fir kyun ye tanhai hai jaane kyun
bebas aur beychain hai dil mera&amp;hellip;.
In simple words, things around me are going crazy&amp;hellip;. restless mind as
there are loved ones who are dealing with the PROBLEM on the ground with
hard reality; facing it more harsh then me who is being updated with
phone calls only.</description></item><item><title>Travel Under Terror</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 00:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</guid><description>There were massive bomb blasts last summer in Mumbai local trains. After
that now there are constant reminders for the commuters to be on alert
and check their surroundings. It is logistical nightmare to manage the
massive number of commuters who takes train every day in Mumbai. In
simple words, “impossible” will be closest word I can pick.
Few months back after lots of planning and public announcement Mumbai
Police conducted a security drill where every passenger was supposed to
pass via metal detector in two Main Terminus in the evening but after
few moments it was clear that police can not handle the stream of
passengers in lakhs and crores as they were heading home and it was
abandoned.</description></item><item><title>New Gadget K790i</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-04-new-gadget-k790i/</guid><description>Well I got
it. After
lots of deliberation I upgraded my choice to K790 from K750. The big
difference is price and features to say in simple words. I heard in
recent time James Bond used this same phone in his last
movie. Not sure what all other
accessories Mr.Q
added for him on the film.
I wanted to buy a camera phone as that will be handy to capture events.</description></item><item><title>Welcoming 2007</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-31-welcoming-2007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2006 05:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-31-welcoming-2007/</guid><description>Well Saddam Hussein is dead so what is next for 2007? May be there will
be very few asking this questions as they start to celebrate New Year
tomorrow. I never ever thought that I will comment upon politics on our
blog. But I think I break that rule today.
Everyone taking stock of year that is almost over. I personally do not
like the week “from Christmas to New Year”, I do not have a solid reason
for the same.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Linen anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid><description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the naming
convention it is Linen
Anniversary we have still
have a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek
(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. After
our wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description></item><item><title>Local trains of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</guid><description>After moving to Mumbai (India) commuting from one place to another was a
big problem (as we didn’t have our own vehicle). It seems Mumbai local
trains are the most efficient one carrying millions of people everyday.
Getting in and out of local trains is one of the hardest tasks
particularly during rush hours which every mumbains has to undergo at
least ones in their life. So, lot of advice was given from Santanu’s
maternal family who are staying here for more than 15 years.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Durga Puja</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-23-durga-puja/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2006 23:23:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-23-durga-puja/</guid><description>Durga Puja is the most important and biggest festival in Bengal for any
Bengali Hindu. Its five days of festivity where this Puja symbolizes
good winning over evil. Maa Durga is considered as daughter of Bengalis.
It is believed that every year she comes to visit her father’s home
(earth) for five days with her four children - Kartik, Ganesh, Saraswati
and Lakshmi- representing respectively the Protector, the Initiator of
the puja, Knowledge and the Provider - signifies the complete
manifestation of the goddess.</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-16-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-16-back-to-work/</guid><description>Well after one and half months of vacation I am back to work today.
Surprisingly, I will be still using my old e-mail (work) well it does
not mean that I am checking my work mails as I write this post. It will
take sometime for the IT guys before they transfer me electronically
from Europe to Asia. I thought it might be a good time to write
something for the blog.</description></item><item><title>Aids Awareness - Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2006 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</guid><description>Can any one guess what this publicity is about? Well, this is 2006 anti
Aids campaign by city hall of Paris (Paris protège l&amp;rsquo;amour means
Paris protects love)
In the photo what we see is sunset on some historical building with moon
at backdrop, but when you take a close look moon is&amp;hellip; a condom. It aims
at promoting the use of condoms among the population i.e., to have safe
sex.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Le vol</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 09:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</guid><description>I am not a person who hates flying to start with as my major air-travel
in recent years was visiting India on holiday from Europe. Like all
other events in life this can be looked at like a coin; on one side the
travel time has reduced significantly while on other side only 20 to 30
kilos of baggage allowed compared to California (65 Kilo).
As we were moving out of Paris we had lot of important things to bring
along with us that we will need till our shipment arrives in next 5
weeks time.</description></item><item><title>Souvenir</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-31-souvenir/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-31-souvenir/</guid><description>As we were leaving Paris it seems our friends (whom we knew for a short
while) has to give something as a memento. Gifts were extravagant and
really worth mentioning as they chose something which we adore.
To start with gift Pamela got from François is very special. I am sure
she can write a new post about the same. I am just going to give you
brief detail on the same.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>Making of Chocolate Charlotte</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</guid><description>Today we have a dinner invitation; spent whole yesterday morning in
thinking what would be good to prepare as I did not want to buy anything
from supermarket. Since we are moving, wanted to clean the fridge
without overstuffing it. So after lot of thought came to conclusion that
charlotte might be best. Learnt this recipe from a friend.
A charlotte is any dessert that&amp;rsquo;s moulded into a container lined
with sponge fingers or boudoir biscuits (purchased at a bakery or
supermarket).</description></item><item><title>Door code</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-door-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 08:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-door-code/</guid><description>This electronic device you are seeing in the picture is nothing but a
door code of our apartment where using a scroll buttons one has to
search and select the name and then press “appel” means “call”
button which will give a ring to the concerned persons apartment and it
is that habitué who will answer that call &amp;amp; unlock the main door.
Certain buildings will have only code with rarely names on front doors
so without “Le code” you won&amp;rsquo;t get past the outer door which usually
leads to a small inner courtyard or a stairway.</description></item><item><title>Pardey key Pichey</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</guid><description>From a good friend of mine I got an offer to help at backstage of Ritu
Beri’s fashion show to be held at Paris on 5th July at Lido. At
first I wanted to deny this proposal but with second thought that it
might be a fun with friends to be there; I nodded my head giving my
approval. Ace fashion designer Ritu Beri is the first Asian to have
joined a French fashion house making a slow transition from Indian Haute
Couture to Prêt-a-porter (ready to wear).</description></item><item><title>Last Week</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-11-last-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 14:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-11-last-week/</guid><description>Watched lots of movies, uploaded some photos to
Running and
walked around Paris last week.
New in gallery - bibs from running . Well you must be wondering what is
that ? For a person like me from whom the activity of sport was taken
away by various pressures at young age it means a lot. The good side of
it is that I am the very few fortunate one to run at this age at various
places but rest remains as silent voice in vast population of India.</description></item><item><title>Swiss-Itenary, TGV and Gizmo</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 09:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</guid><description>Another
Friday, thinking to write something for my blog ;) I think I should have
kept a track of my Friday bloging or changes I made on Friday :D. Well,
this post is not going to be about Friday but it is about our
Switzerland itinerary, experience with TGV etc.
Might have noticed there are lots of posts by Pamela in recent time –
wish she would have done before from our other trips also.</description></item><item><title>Italian aroma…</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Daney Daney Pey likha hain khaney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo;- which
colloquially means each grain has the name of the person who will eat it
(it is the fortune of the person to have certain meal or not). Well the
same with more of spice in Hindi movies &amp;ldquo;goli goli pey likha hain
marney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo; which means in each bullets it is written the
name of the person who will die.</description></item><item><title>Taste of India @ Swiss</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-taste-of-india-swiss/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-taste-of-india-swiss/</guid><description>Although trip to Switzerland is over but yet we can’t stop writing about
it. If you are one of those few regular visitors to our blog you must be
knowing by now how much we liked our one week stay. And must be
wondering what more can be there to write about.
Yes, there are always lot to write about Switzerland when we are
comparing with Paris and when one is seeing through Indian eyes.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Green plate</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-30-green-plate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-30-green-plate/</guid><description>In
my salad days I used to hate many green veggies and I remember when maa
used to scold me for the same. Somehow I didn’t had taste for them at
that point of time but gradually I developed the taste so much so that I
can now survive happily on those green things (cow-food).
From long time Santanu wanted to make a change on our meal as it seems
we both are putting on weight.</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>A must list for swiss</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 19:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</guid><description>Our trip to Switzerland has ended after all those C.B.G (châteaux,
bateaux and gateaux) trips around Europe but indeed it was a different
experience altogether. It is all about the greenery, mountain streams
rushing along, water falls, snow clad mountains, sounds of cow-bells
tickling on the alpine meadows.
I am not sure if every one is happy with their first trip to a new place
or not. But, I am always very happy and excited to go to new places.</description></item><item><title>Shhh …. Silence Please</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</guid><description>Normally, I and Santanu don&amp;rsquo;t talk to each other on bus, train, flight
or whatsoever as we are normally lost in our own world and both try to
respect each others silence. We have books, newspaper, ipod for that
time but this particular evening we happened to talk so much while
returning to Zurich from Luzern. One of the reason maybe that by now we
are kind of used to watching beautiful sceneries from train as it runs
along lakes, rivers and creaking sometimes as it passes by the running
hills unfolding before us.</description></item><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;rdquo; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Relaxing Day - 24th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</guid><description>It meant to be a vacation within vacation today. As we did not have to
catch any train neither any bus nor get up early for any fixed
destination. Relaxingly, we had our self-made breakfast and then headed
towards railway station for renting a cycle to bike. At first, we went
towards the city center of Interlaken where there is a big Casino and
park. From there we biked all the way towards the lake Brienz.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Hiking Mt.Rigi - 22nd June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 14:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</guid><description>Queen of Swiss Mountains From Zurich we went to Mt. Rigi via Arth-Goldau a very short train ride.
From there we took the cogwheel train to the summit at Rigi-Kulm
(1,800m). Incredible vistas, typical Swiss farmhouses, and hundreds of
cows with bells will surprise one throughout the trip. Reward on going
to top is magnificent panorama of Alpine peaks crowding around the
convoluted contours of Lake Lucerne. While going up it was a nice
weather but slowly &amp;amp; slowly it started getting dark.</description></item><item><title>Mount Titlis - 21st June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</guid><description>Staying at Sachin’s place at Zurich was just to save our 3 night’s hotel
expense. After lot of discussion &amp;amp; surfing internet we came to final
decision that on 4th day of our trip we will go to Mount
Titlis via Luzern in order to
make best use of our Swiss flexi pass.
On boarding the train from Luzern to Engelberg we realized that it’s
more of Desi train. From train station, routes are well marked for
heading towards Mount Titlis where one can see all Mr.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Rescued - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</guid><description>By now, seeing the time I was
discussing about hitch hiking to the next big town which was ruled out
by Santanu as it seems not safe. Even I was suggesting him how about
getting into a car of people who does not look that young and suddenly
one car stopped and they asked if we need any lift… looking at their
face we did not take a second to decide and say “YES” in unison (which
came out as if instinct) with big smiling face.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item><item><title>C’est fou - part II !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-12-cest-fou-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 08:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-12-cest-fou-part-ii/</guid><description>Finally, world cup football came to an end where France lost to Italy.
For me France lost but at same time Italy neither win as they just
waited for the final penalty shoot out to happen. I do not like the way
Italian play football in general. They make it dull and boring. Italian
and their relation to non Italian footballer are well known. And this
time the whole nation is waiting for the verdict of match fixing in
Italian league.</description></item><item><title>C’est fou !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</guid><description>Football - the definition for the same may be quite simple but it
certainly does have lots of colors. It is a mutli-billion dollar
business from sporting to TV companies. For some it is as close to their
religion. People can fight or hug with a complete stranger while
ignoring his family or close one when there is a match.
As we live in Europe it is very hard to escape it.</description></item><item><title>Uncertain Voyage</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 19:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</guid><description>After traveling to so many places in Europe in last three years now we
were thinking to travel to some other part of globe which can be easily
reached from Paris within few hours maybe somewhere in North African.
The very thought came was how about going to Morocco or Egypt but none
of them was perfect weather wise to visit. Then also after too much of
thinking we settled for Morocco and started to gather touristic
information.</description></item><item><title>I am sorry when I am wrong but I am furious when I am right</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-15-i-am-sorry-when-i-am-wrong-but-i-am-furious-when-i-am-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2006 11:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-15-i-am-sorry-when-i-am-wrong-but-i-am-furious-when-i-am-right/</guid><description>Well the title say it all</description></item><item><title>Le Marche</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-04-le-marche/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-06-04-le-marche/</guid><description>The open markets in Paris have been
in existence since ages. It&amp;rsquo;s here that you find freshly picked fruit
and vegetables, fresh fish from Brittany and Normandy, meat, flowers,
farmhouses cheeses, breads – you name it &amp;hellip; its there. Food controls
are very strict in France and be assured of their quality and
cleanliness of preparation. French understands the quality in life and
nothing demonstrates this better than the wonderful food markets in
Paris.</description></item><item><title>Bike Route</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-23-bike-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 17:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-23-bike-route/</guid><description>Just uploaded few
pictures from my
bike route as promised in earlier
post. There is a
movie which I tried to shoot while riding with my digital camera (which
is quite old now). Last weekend was very rainy and stormy so being at
home tried MPG4 and QuickTime. MOV version is around 7 MB but the
quality is so so while QuickTime version of the same is big around 26MB
with better quality.</description></item><item><title>Uddan - Flight</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid><description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing its
publicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in the
world. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouraged
us to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar covering
around 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooth
though they were very strict about luggage weight.
In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough leg
room; quality of the food was better than what we had before and was
good with choice of films and music on demand.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>load cpu &amp; memory shell script c program for quick and dirty benchmark</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-18-load-cpu-memory-shell-script-c-program-for-quick-and-dirty-benchmark/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 23:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-18-load-cpu-memory-shell-script-c-program-for-quick-and-dirty-benchmark/</guid><description>This script is a simple empty while loop which will load or increase the
usage of your cpu. a good way to test your cpu check for different monitoring tool
while : &amp;gt; do : &amp;gt; done
/home/sanmisra&amp;gt;more memory.c
main () { while ( 1 ) { malloc (10240) ; } }</description></item><item><title>Friday 12th May</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 15:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</guid><description>Just another weekend of May in Paris. I don&amp;rsquo;t know any other time when
the weather can be so beautiful with clear sky and warm temperature.
Right now, all the horse chestnut
trees along wide
boulevards are full of white flowers. This tree is also known as
Marronier d&amp;rsquo;Inde, thanks to Francois for introducing the same.
Truly, if one cheers up and forgets all the problems round him-it is a
romantic experience in itself.</description></item><item><title>Deja Vu</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 21:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-10-deja-vu/</guid><description>I am not sure if you happened to experience a very low probability
situation or event in life which you can compare with winnnig a
lottery or
getting struck by thunder. Statistically the second one has more chance.
To explain the same I take to you to recent past&amp;hellip;
I had that bizarre experience in the month on December while returning
from work took a
bus.
There was one gentleman very well groomed of dark complexion And I met
the same person next day (Saturday) in a different
bus
while going out.</description></item><item><title>add new administrator and management post for smartdashboard firewall-1</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-add-new-administrator-and-management-post-for-smartdashboard-firewall-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 22:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-add-new-administrator-and-management-post-for-smartdashboard-firewall-1/</guid><description>1.Add the user in the system password file for *nix it will be in
/etc/passwd and /etc/shadow 2. Add his host(PC) to /etc/hosts 3. Use cpconfig ( /opt/CPshrd-53/bin/) in case of Solaris Rest is menu driven</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Back to Mordor</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-04-20-back-to-mordor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 09:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-04-20-back-to-mordor/</guid><description>Well it has been a long time I bloged. I am back to Paris; Pamela will
join me in a month time. The title of the post could not be better as I
am missing the sun after returning from India. I like rain after very
hot summer or sunny days with cool breeze. I really can not take those
dark cloudy days which makes me feel gloomy. As looking out of my window
can&amp;rsquo;t even make out is it 11 AM or 3 PM.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-03-15-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-03-15-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>“India is changing” I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn’t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Tujh bin….</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-03-06-tujh-bin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 16:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-03-06-tujh-bin/</guid><description>Oof !!!! getting mad you know.Its been a while Santanu is trying his
best to make it work but alas no response,no sound&amp;hellip; nothing.Tried his
best as much as he could, took it on his lap, dismantle
everything&amp;hellip;like one of those computer geeks trying to fix that damn
thing but god&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;everything gone in vain.The connections &amp;amp; all
those seems to be fine except that fan which was rotating in such a
speed making hell lot of noise.</description></item><item><title>Vacation on the horizon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid><description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)
when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard of
travelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May be
it is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visit
some country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not at
all interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Paris
cold all the time.</description></item><item><title>French classes came to an end</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-05-french-classes-came-to-an-end/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 19:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-02-05-french-classes-came-to-an-end/</guid><description>Well my French classes came to an end. And I passed the exam :D I would
like to take up the Oscar podium for few seconds and like to thank my
beloved wife Pamela for her support ; my teacher, my colleagues- Stephan
and Fred for their time and effort to make me understand the basics of
French grammar. And I am very satisfied that I didn&amp;rsquo;t let them down as I
scored well in grammar and got all the Passé-compose and
Imparfait (past tense) correct.</description></item><item><title>Joy of baking</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-17-joy-of-baking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2006 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-17-joy-of-baking/</guid><description>With the cold weather and shorter day lights lots of baking is going on
and enjoying the butter and sugar lately. Feeling guilty as cann&amp;rsquo;t
resist and moreover did not do any exercise after my Paris - Versailles
marathon :(
We were invited to one of my colleague’s place for the first time after
almost 3 years in France for ‘Galette des rois’. It was very
memorable and an enjoyable evening.</description></item><item><title>Home Network ADSL-Network-Phone</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</guid><description>I just wanted to share my home network. It is not a state of
technologies with the latest &amp;amp; greatest wireless or wired network with
complex router and switches. I did it in old school way with a single
long CAT5 Ethernet Cable. I have a FreeBox which is an ADSL2 router
connecting to the main phone jack. The output from the
FreeBox connects my PC, Television and
Phone. Now all these components are connected with the single wire as
I mentioned before.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Thank God its Friday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-16-thank-god-its-friday/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2005 09:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-16-thank-god-its-friday/</guid><description>It has been a while I wrote any post. Well, after quite a long time I
met with Tapas
a good old friend from Bay Area. The meeting was short while having
dinner at our place; got some updates on other friends in Bay Area.
Yesterday, was last French class before 2 week vacations so we went out
for drinks after the class. I never had this kind of social events where
you have to speak in French and you are not ashamed of your mistakes.</description></item><item><title>Metro in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</guid><description>Living in Paris and not travelling in Metro has lots of demerits. Like
usual I am going to start with the traffic jams, one way roads,
unavailability of parking, high parking tickets and very unusual sense
of Parisian driving skills.
These only list if you have a car and travelling of your own. But what
about those who are taking other mode of smart transports like Bus,
Tram, Bicycle, Rollerblade or just walk to work or work from home?</description></item><item><title>create typewriter effect with ming php for flash (swf) movie</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-25-create-typewriter-effect-with-ming-php-for-flash-swf-movie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2005 11:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-25-create-typewriter-effect-with-ming-php-for-flash-swf-movie/</guid><description>This is nice and simple code it creates the simple effect which you
might have seen in lots of web sites. As it is PHP you can use the same
from your own news reader to database.
setBackground(0x00,0x00,0x00);// SM
This is very important as it set sets the speed of the movie// SM -
Higher the number faster the typing will
appear$movie-&amp;gt;setRate(3);// SM - This one will depends upon
you$movie-&amp;gt;setDimension(600,40);$movie-&amp;gt;setFrames(31);$movie-&amp;gt;nextFrame();//
Define your String here $str = &amp;lsquo;Miing Typewriter Effect&amp;rsquo;; /* SM - As
you note The space between character if not fixed SM - due to font
width so you have to figure out your own SM - Now we split our string
and make an array with the same */ $chars = preg_split('//', $str,
-1, PREG_SPLIT_NO_EMPTY);// print_r($chars);$inc = 0
;for($i=0;$isetFont($myFont); $myText-&amp;gt;setColor(255,255,255);
$myText-&amp;gt;SetHeight(30); $myText-&amp;gt;addString($chars[$i]); echo
(&amp;ldquo;$chars[$i] \n&amp;rdquo;) ; $firstText=$movie-&amp;gt;add($myText);
$firstText-&amp;gt;moveTo($inc,30); $inc = $inc + 18; // SM - this is very
critical as you need to add this extra frame to make this effect of
some typewriter $movie-&amp;gt;nextframe(); // SM - This helps to
determine the width of the movie // SM - turn only if you need the
same // echo &amp;ldquo;inc is $inc \n&amp;rdquo; ; } // SM - we do not want to loop this
movie// $movie-&amp;gt;add(new SWFAction(&amp;ldquo;stop();&amp;quot;)); // SM - Save the
movie $movie-&amp;gt;save(&amp;quot;/tmp/banner.</description></item><item><title>Create Banner with mirror effect by ImageMagick</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-18-create-banner-with-mirror-effect-by-imagemagick/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-18-create-banner-with-mirror-effect-by-imagemagick/</guid><description>A simple way to create a text image which will have mirror effects. The
best part of this you do not have to use any fancy imging software and
it takes only few seconds to create the same. The code a single line to
make it easier for Windows
convert
-size 460x130 xc:white -font forte -pointsize 72 -fill &amp;ldquo;#cccccc&amp;rdquo;
-annotate 0x180+12+80 &amp;ldquo;Banner Mirror&amp;rdquo; -gaussian 0x2 -stroke black
-strokewidth 1 -fill &amp;ldquo;#80904F&amp;rdquo; -stroke black -strokewidth 1 -annotate
0x0+12+55 &amp;ldquo;Banner Mirror&amp;rdquo; -draw &amp;ldquo;line 0,68 430,68&amp;rdquo;
Banner-Mirror-Imagemagick.</description></item><item><title>Reached 10K and folding</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-16-reached-10k-and-folding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 13:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-16-reached-10k-and-folding/</guid><description>Folding @ Home is a Stanford University project of understating protein
folding. It is distributed computing where small tasks are sent to
Personal Computers (PC) across the world and it uses those CPU power to
calculate. The results are sent back to the main computer. It is a very
safe program and probably you will not notice any performance change for
your computer.
There are similar projects for understanding Genome to AIDS which uses
more or less similar technology of distributed computing.</description></item><item><title>Orsay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-14-orsay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2005 09:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-14-orsay-revisited/</guid><description>To my greatest surprise I found failure in implementing a perfect backup
system for my digital images. Somehow I lost all the pictures from Orsay
museum. May be I just deleted them(by mistake)!!! Yes I know the trouble
of digital memories they are very easy to capture but most difficult to
save. There are lists of problem that can happen to your golden past;
starting with the media card to Hard Drive not to mention virus problems
or accidental deletion of files</description></item><item><title>Diwali at Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-10-diwali-at-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2005 10:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-10-diwali-at-paris/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Are you safe out there?&amp;rdquo; This was typical question to which I have been
answering to my friends and relatives after the riots at Paris suburbs.
I myself was keeping updated with news only. &amp;ldquo;Thank God&amp;rdquo; it looks like
getting better now. I would not like to make any comments and express my
view on the same as it seems to be very complex matter.
We celebrated Diwali quite well this year.</description></item><item><title>Part -2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-part-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 02:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-part-2/</guid><description>create individual pages for each image dirty way with php [code] &amp;lt;?php //$image_files=[] ; $type = &amp;ldquo;jpg&amp;rdquo;; $abspath_folder = &amp;ldquo;/home/santm/public_html/PamelasCreation/images&amp;rdquo; ; if ( is_dir ( $abspath_folder ) ) { if ( $handle = opendir( $abspath_folder ) ) { while (false !== ( $file = readdir($handle ) ) ) { if ( $file != &amp;lsquo;.&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file != &amp;lsquo;..&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file != &amp;lsquo;CVS&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file !=
&amp;lsquo;index.html&amp;rsquo; ) { //santm echo &amp;ldquo;FILE is $file \n&amp;rdquo; ; $the_array[] = $file; } } } } closedir( $handle ); // end of reading the directory // santm print_r ( $the_array ); // making sure the array only has our jpg image starting with a number foreach ( $the_array as $img ) { if ( !</description></item><item><title>photo album : imagemagick (part -1)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-photo-album-imagemagick-part-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 02:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-photo-album-imagemagick-part-1/</guid><description>Quick and dirty way of creating photo album with imagemagick, creating
images with black border as it looks good for all
#!/bin/cshset files = `echo [0-9]*.jpg`echo $filesforeach file ( $files )set w = `identify -format &amp;quot;%w&amp;quot; $file`set h = `identify -format &amp;quot;%h&amp;quot; $file`if ($w &amp;gt; $h) then convert $file -thumbnail 500X -bordercolor black -border 1 /tmp/foo100/$fileelse convert $file -thumbnail X500 -bordercolor black -border 1 /tmp/foo100/$fileendifend</description></item><item><title>Place de la Concorde</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-30-place-de-la-concorde/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2005 21:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-30-place-de-la-concorde/</guid><description>After a long time I was able to
capture the fountain of Place de la Concordein a very beautiful sunny morning. It is
so amazing that we still take pictures of Paris like tourist on their
first day. When we left home it was cloudy and we were questioning
ourselves why we are carrying the camera with us. But luckily it was
worth to do so. Then from there we took a small promenade at the garden
of Elysee.</description></item><item><title>Tibx Shoe Laces</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</guid><description>Yes these are my dirty shoes. Not very sure about the origin of those
shoe laces, I got them when my old office was getting closed. Missing
the TIBX bus and shares I got those laces :( (People got nice race cars
and big houses in Bay Area a dream come true in this materialistic world
and what I got for boarding the train late. Well I have another pair of
these laces….</description></item><item><title>Migrating rrd database between different architecture</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-11-migrating-rrd-database-between-different-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 20:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-11-migrating-rrd-database-between-different-architecture/</guid><description>This script you run on the source host from the same directory where all
those rrd files are there. I found this very helpful while migrating
between Linux and Solaris.
#/bin/csh
set all_files=`echo *.rrd`
echo $all_files
foreach file ( $all_files )
set base = `basename $file .rrd`
/bin/rrdtool dump $file &amp;gt; /tmp/new1/$base.xml
end
The do a `tar` with `gzip` as that will save lots of space and time
while transferring data between machines.</description></item><item><title>French class</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-05-french-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2005 17:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-10-05-french-class/</guid><description>After all these months, I prefer not to use years yet :) I started
formal French class. I am not sure how it will end up as it keeps me
reminding about my Spanish class which I dropped out after 2 months. But
for those 2 months I went on time to Foothill community college every
morning at 8AM. It was different as medium of instruction was English
now everything is French.</description></item><item><title>Gallery2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-29-gallery2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2005 20:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-29-gallery2/</guid><description>Well I am having lots of trouble with a simple gallery2 installation
with 15 pictures for my wife&amp;rsquo;s hobby pictures. While I am running a 1600
picture gallery on the same server with out any problem touch wood. The
back on the main one not there.
And i am having wonderful tech support from dot5 hosting to say the
least. The guy does not even know what is Unix he replies it is
FreeBSD.</description></item><item><title>Running Paris Versailles</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-26-running-paris-versailles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2005 00:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-26-running-paris-versailles/</guid><description>Almost after one and half year I was
running in any event. The weather was very grey but it was very pleasant
for running. Temperature was around 16 degree Celsius. The race was 17KM
long starting from bottom of Eiffel Tower to Château de
Versailles.For the first time, Pamela accompanied me to the starting point of the
course so as to take a photo of mine with Eiffel Tower. The first part
of the run was along River Seine and then it goes to Forest of Meudon;
this was the most crucial part as it has a steep climb (approx.</description></item><item><title>New look to web site</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2005 03:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</guid><description>Migrated to Wordpress along with
Gallery2, the choice for the same was not
easy. As for a long time Mambo and custom
home grown Photo Album was doing the job fine. In fact the template I
used for the same was appreciated by friends. But as days passed and
numbers of pictures are growing it was getting difficult to manage the
same with custom gallery. But the idea to grab Wordpress and dropping
Mambo is a personal one.</description></item><item><title>banner with imagemgick convert</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-11-banner-with-imagemgick-convert/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2005 01:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-11-banner-with-imagemgick-convert/</guid><description>To create a banner with mirror effect!!
convert -size 600x130 xc:transparent -font forte -pointsize 72 -fill
&amp;ldquo;#cccccc&amp;rdquo; -annotate 0x180+12+80 &amp;ldquo;Pamela&amp;rsquo;s Gallery&amp;rdquo; -gaussian 0x2
-stroke black -strokewidth 1 -fill &amp;ldquo;#ff3600&amp;rdquo; -stroke black -strokewidth
1 -annotate 0x0+12+55 &amp;ldquo;Pamela&amp;rsquo;s Gallery&amp;rdquo; -draw &amp;ldquo;line 0,68 570,68&amp;rdquo;
banner.png</description></item><item><title>ssh and scp</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-11-ssh-and-scp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2005 00:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-11-ssh-and-scp/</guid><description>Via tunnel
scp -P 2222 font_slewed.gif santm@localhost:/tmp/banner.gif ssh -p 2222 santm@localhost
nomally :</description></item><item><title>[How To] Puttygen Puttssh for ssh</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-05-how-to-puttygen-puttssh-for-ssh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 19:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-08-05-how-to-puttygen-puttssh-for-ssh/</guid><description>1. Run PuttyKeyGen 1.a Make sure you choose SSH2DSA at the bottom 1.b Click on Generate 1.c Move Mouse as mentioned.
Once the key is generated 2.a Put proper comment for Key username and hostname 2.b Type your Password please try to choose a proper password i.e. with
number, special character, upper case hard to guess 2.c Save the public and private key I saved in C:\Documents and Settings\santanu.misra</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 18:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</guid><description>When I was on my vacation last week in Spain and Portugal, was thinking
about to write down all that we had experienced there - the places we
visted and food we tasted and others. But back to work it is such a
Dilbert place that I can not explain with my logic.
Also I need to find a cheap solution to restore pictures from Smart
Media. It looks like there is a well suited option commercial for 40
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Lost Pictures Recovered</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 18:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</guid><description>After discovering that one of the SmartMedia Card from my Camera not
working at Seville we were really very heart broken and anxious. It had
pictures from our first three days of our trip. And in those first three
days we traveled from Madrid to Granada. We had captured lots of evening
pictures in Madrid and sunset view of Alhambra at Granada.
But we kept our nerve cool and continued with other media cards and
tried our best not to remember about the same.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Train Lisbon to Madrid</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</guid><description>We
were at the very last phase of our vacation. We took train back to
Madrid tonight as from there we had our flight back to Paris.
We booked the train ticket long back; I went in-person to get the same
from Spanish Railway ticket office based in Paris. The office is kind of
hidden by all the stores near to Boulevard Haussmann; ever busy shopping
place.
Being Indian it was a really something new although we had experienced
few other different night trains in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Cordoba – Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid><description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought of
Cordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggested
visiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reach
the train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. The
fair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costs
almost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Alhambra - Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</guid><description>We did not book our tickets for Alhambra before coming to Granada. There
can be 8,000 visitors inside Alhambra in a given day. Out of those 8,000
around 6,500 are sold over internet &amp;amp; phone. So for us, it meant getting
up early and queuing up in the morning. As it was Monday and not peak of
tourist season&amp;hellip; we were lucky.
Alhambra has main 4 sites to visit.
The main attraction is of course &amp;ldquo;Palacios Nazaries&amp;rdquo; the best preserved
Moorish Palace in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2005 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</guid><description>The temperature in Spain was quite hot compared to Paris. It was around
37° C when we reached Granada in the afternoon. The bus station for
intercity is not at the city center but there is a good connection of
public transport for the same. Our hotel was at the center - Plaza
Royal.
Around 5 PM, we headed out from hotel, it was still very hot and bright.
We walked towards Plaza Nueva.</description></item><item><title>Madrid - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-21-madrid-spain/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2005 18:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-21-madrid-spain/</guid><description>We were on our way to spring break; we planned to visit Spain and Lisbon
for 10 days. We started our trip with flight from Paris to Madrid on
Saturday 21st May 2005.
We reached Charles de Gaulle Airport on time and the checking was smooth
but after boarding the plane we were in ground for almost one hour
before taking off. The cost cutting measures with European state
carriers are all alike now, so there is no free snacks &amp;amp; drinks in the
short flight.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Bonjour</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</guid><description>After a long time I changed the theme of my web site; hope the color
combination looks good. The two templates are &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;zen&amp;rsquo;.
There are now more than 1300 pictures to checkout in the Photo Album
section. Most of them come from last 3 years as that is how old my
digital camera is. And a big section comes from Europe. After moving to
Paris, we used this opportunity to visit maximum countries possible
which are part of Schengen visa.</description></item><item><title>New PC</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-04-15-new-pc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2005 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-04-15-new-pc/</guid><description>After months of checking web sites for prices reading forums for review
and always thinking about moving out Paris I got my new PC. It was not
an easy choice as all these years I wanted a Mac from Apple. And
Mini-Mac was a real contender for long time.
But at the end I went for mini-PC because of the money and choice of
flexibility I have with the same.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2004 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</guid><description>Happy Holidays!!! Well year 2004 is almost over; wish you all the best for the year 2005
and next. This year we did not traveled like last year. But we did
traveled to Italy and Greece for one week each, other than some of few
short trips. You will find them in pictures for 2004.
In the month of November we framed few pictures and cross-stitch work of
Pamela. Here are the pictures of the same.</description></item><item><title>Loire Valley</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-11-22-loire-valley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2004 20:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-11-22-loire-valley/</guid><description>River Loire is one of the four major rivers of France. It had always
major importance to France. In the Medieval time or the best time of
French civilization French Rules and noble men of that time had built
lot of Chateau (castles) along this river. It is very close to Paris,
which is one of the reasons to built their weekend home for hunting and
relaxation here.
We only visited three castles that Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Chateau de Versailles</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-11-12-chateau-de-versailles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2004 10:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-11-12-chateau-de-versailles/</guid><description>I have a fascination for the colour of autumn, mat be the reason is I
never experienced them before while in India and California. You can
enjoy the same in Paris where trees along the big boulevards changes it
colour. Around Paris particularly the Bois de Boulogne is very nice that
time. We went to Versailles just to take pictures. It was not a very
sunny day that Sunday, sun was playing around clouds.</description></item><item><title>Greece</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-10-18-greece/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2004 19:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-10-18-greece/</guid><description>After coming back from Italy we were looking for a week long vacation
and the obvious choice was Greece but waited till Olympics 2004 to
finish. We figured out from all the guidebooks and Internet that all the
major historical sites are quite far from each others. As we had no plan
for renting and driving we opted a guided tour for the main attractions.
We were very skeptical initially but at the end it turned to be very
good meeting new people and quality of service was very good.</description></item><item><title>Opera - Alcina</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-26-opera-alcina/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2004 05:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-26-opera-alcina/</guid><description>Going to opera for the first time was a very eye-opening experience. It
was really fabulous and all the thanks goes to Francois for the same. He
gave us the recording in CD and printed storyline before. That really
helped us to enjoy and understand the musical drama. We went to the
Opera Garnier the old one in Paris. He got us one of the best seats in
the beautiful opera house as the TV camera was in our next box.</description></item><item><title>Paris in night mode</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 20:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</guid><description>I wanted to take pictures of Paris famous landmarks in the twilight with
a tripod. We started with Sacre-coeur Basilica. And the picture we got
from there was really great as we were there on the right time. The sky
color was perfect for the camera and it was just lighted.
From there we went to Moulin-Rouge; the famous cabaret of Paris then to
Assembly National the French Parliament. We crossed Seine and came to
Concord.</description></item><item><title>DisneyLand - Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-17-disneyland-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2004 05:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-17-disneyland-paris/</guid><description>This place which is most visited by tourist in Paris. I really didnot
wanted to visit this one as I have been to Disney land twice in
California. Pamela wanted to visit this place last summer but some how I
was able to save myself from that trip. This year I could not escape.
OK, enough of cursing and all. At end I have to say, that I did enjoyed
my time there like every other time at Disneyland.</description></item><item><title>Musee Guimet</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-12-musee-guimet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2004 09:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-12-musee-guimet/</guid><description>This Museum is an extension of Louvre Museum-collection of objects from
Asia. Mostly the objects are from south Asia and far east Asia, if you
been to London British Museum and visited Asian sections you will feel
deja vu. It is located in 16th arrondissement of Paris next to Metro
Station of Iena.
We visited the same with Francois; it was only Francois who told us
about this museum. He had been here before few times.</description></item><item><title>Itlay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 12:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</guid><description>We have been to Rome for 4 days in 2003 but we wanted to visit the other
parts of Italy but could not do that due to time constrain. We were
planning for trip to Florence, Venice etc old classic route for long
time.
Krovi and Vidya went to Italy on their paper honeymoon which was 3
weeks earlier than us and they did provided us with lots of good tips.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item><item><title>LA HOLLANDE, ALLEZ-Y MAINTENANT!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-08-la-hollande-allez-y-maintenant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2004 22:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-08-la-hollande-allez-y-maintenant/</guid><description>Seeing one of friend&amp;rsquo;s photographs we were so excited to visit that
place. That, in our last trip to Amsterdam (May 2003) we tried to visit
that - but alas! Local people told us that Tulip season is already over.
But deep down in our heart we wanted to visit that place particularly
Keukenhof thinking -maybe next year.
Then we were in touch with Holland tourism in-order to know more about
Keukenhof.</description></item><item><title>Got an IPOD</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2004 21:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</guid><description>Requested my brother to send me one I-pod from USA with Hitesh as he was
coming to Paris on a business trip. It was very nice to catch up with
Hitesh, Neetu and Simran after moving out of CA. We met them at their
hotel in Latin quarter and had dinner with them. It was almost 2 in the
morning when we returned home in the cold night of February.</description></item><item><title>A year in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2004 04:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved to Paris almost a year back from US. We try to travel around at
least once a month outside of Paris. This year so far we have been to
Zurich, Mt. Saint Michel and Barcelona.
I like Paris but some time French system and people makes me mad. I am
going to run Paris Half marathon in March first week. Now a days I am
trying to run more regularly.</description></item><item><title>St. Michel</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-14-st-michel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2004 22:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-14-st-michel/</guid><description>Perched on a rocky islet in the midst of vast sandbanks exposed to
powerful tides between Normandy and Brittany (on the north coast of
France) stand the &amp;lsquo;Wonder of the West&amp;rsquo;, a Gothic-style abbey dedicated
to the Archangel St Michael
It was built in 8thcentury, the buildings of Mont St. Michel
were constructed of granite which were carried from near-by island but
some limestone were also used in the cloister.</description></item><item><title>Back from vacation</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 04:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</guid><description>Back to Paris after a nice and quick vacation of 4 weeks from India. The
days passed by very quickly between meals and sleep. Our vacation got
split between my parents and in-law&amp;rsquo;s house. But it was great to spent
time with family. Will post some new pictures and others later. Paris is
very beautifully decorated for holidays, it is a great sight to see all
those big trees along the road being lighted up, as they don&amp;rsquo;t have any
leaf now.</description></item><item><title>Paper Anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid><description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventful
for both of us. On this day we went to Ramkrishna
Mission.The
hour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fall
color.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Pooja
and Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went to
Salon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description></item><item><title>Rome (Sep 5th-7th)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 09:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</guid><description>We wanted to visit all the top attractions of Italy in one trip but due
to vacation time (for Parisians) and taking off from work and with
Pamela&amp;rsquo;s school we could not do. So, we planned for only Rome. We
flew with Alitalia from CDG this time in early morning. It was much
better than Ryan Airlines in terms of access to the airport. But the
initial fun started when just before checking-in we have to run 3
terminals to collect our tickets from Air Traffic office.</description></item><item><title>Stockholm (Aug 14th - 17th)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2003 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</guid><description>While browsing through web sites for summer travel deals I found there
was a very attractive deal by Ryan Air to Stockholm.We went there middle
of August when Paris was burning with summer heat. It was a great escape
to Scandinavia. Stockholm was very clean and very beautiful. Although,
the weather was not at its best as it rained for first two days.
We stayed in the centre of Stockholm (Drottninggatan) one side of this
pedestrian street with full of shops.</description></item><item><title>London 5days (July 29th - Aug 3rd)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2003 23:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</guid><description>We went to London the proper Bilayet (Foreign land -as mentioned by
S.Rushdie ) for five days. We stayed as guest of Sampath, at his home
bit outside of London. The trip would not have been so pleasant and
memorable without his help and warm hospitality.
We reached around noon at Waterloo station by Eurostar. After keeping
our luggage at cloak room we went straight to London Eye. It was a
nice start to see all the monuments of London from birds view.</description></item><item><title>Heat wave of August</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-08-heat-wave-of-august/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2003 22:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-08-heat-wave-of-august/</guid><description>Oh! summer, it reached 40 degree cel. or 100+ F this week at Paris.The
global pollution is taking its effect may be? 20 years back it used to
snow a lot in Paris but now it does not snow any more. The houses,
metro&amp;rsquo;s are not designed for this kind of hot weather which makes it
more unbearable. We are surviving with Pedestal Fan but it is still far
from a rain.</description></item><item><title>Cantal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-07-18-cantal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2003 10:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-07-18-cantal/</guid><description>The first trip to France countryside was to Cantal -central region for 3
days with Murali &amp;amp; Joydeep on July 14th. Cantal, in France&amp;rsquo;s Massif
Central, is the largest volcanic edifice in Europe. We went by car,
Murali did a wonderful job by seating at the back of steering wheel &amp;amp;
Joydeep at navigator’s seat while we two were enjoying sleeping (from
time to time) at back seat. We enjoyed a natural landscape which was
really worth seeing through own eyes- rolling hills, lush green
farmlands, small mountains, forests &amp;amp; valleys.</description></item><item><title>Trip to Amsterdam (June 7th-9th)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-09-trip-to-amsterdam-june-7th-9th/</guid><description>Our first trip in Europe, I decided about Amsterdam because of two
reason Van Gogh and people of Amsterdam. To our delight it was really
great and was a great escape from noise and crowd of Paris.The city is
not so big compared to Paris but very clean and friendly. As most
tourist books suggest Dutch people has unique and very efficient
solution to their day-to-day problem. The streets are not crowded with
car.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item><item><title>Music @ Cite Universitaire</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-25-music-cite-universitaire/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-25-music-cite-universitaire/</guid><description>It was great that we just went there without any plan. Various kinds of
musical instruments &amp;amp; on different themes were played by young student
musicians. A nice place for free concert and music if you are around
Paris. We spent quite a long time. But, we could not attend the final
grand Jazz program, as it was already around 9 PM.
http://www.ciup.fr/</description></item><item><title>Purbayan and Satyajit</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-18-purbayan-and-satyajit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-18-purbayan-and-satyajit/</guid><description>Jaya(my cousin sister) and her hubby Purbayan visited us along with
Satyajit on very rainy Sunday. They came to Paris for their own private
concert. They were on a tour to Europe and playing Indian classical
music. Purbayan(sitar) and Satyajit (tabla) are very talented in their
own field.It was our great pleasure to have them as guest. Due to rain
we reached the concert bit late but it was a great performance.</description></item><item><title>Metro on Strike</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</guid><description>It started on Tuesday the 13th. My manager gave me a lift to work. On
the way back I walked, it was long but nice walk through Bois de
BoulogneWednesday, the strike was supposed to end; but it continued in
a French way. So, I have to work hard to fix my bike and went by bike to
work. In that process I got an ache on to my shoulder, which did not
allow me to sleep for a whole week.</description></item><item><title>Second Titre De Sejour</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-10-second-titre-de-sejour/</guid><description>On the 9th of April we were supposed to collect our new Titre De
Sejour (Long term VISA) from Cite Prefecture de Police. The interview
was fixed almost 3 months ago and we reached there before our scheduled
time to be make sure this time there is no big problem. But our turn
came around 4o&amp;rsquo;clock which is almost one hour behind our scheduled time.
And after checking all our paper she says oh!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Paris an unofficial guide by Malc</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2003 20:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</guid><description>Here is a set of stuff about flat hunting, contributed from many
sources. One note. Most of this is for finding a flat on your own.Don&amp;rsquo;t
go near
Hestia.fr (many a tale of woe has originated
from here) Get your &amp;lsquo;dossier&amp;rsquo; together straight away. Needs
photocopy of
Present employment contract
Last 3 pay slips
Last 3 rent receipts (or in my case my 1 year mortgage statement from
the UK)</description></item><item><title>Picnic with Ritu</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</guid><description>It has been a long time we were exchanging e-mails and phone calls with
Ritu, but could not meet her in-person. She is a friend of Akiko&amp;rsquo;s Paris
friend. A long chain; but a start to make social contacts in new place.
I am personally not that social to make friends at party or other social
gatherings that is one reason holding me to join local Expats club.Ritu
arranged a great picnic and was very nice to meet all other expaticians.</description></item><item><title>Louvre</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-04-02-louvre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-04-02-louvre/</guid><description>After figuring out, lots of museum have free entry on first Sunday of
every month we started with our museum tour with Louvre. Oh!! It is
a museum in itself. I am sure all of you know some thing or other about
it. We started our tour with Egyptian section last month. We are still
visiting &amp;amp; we think we only covered 1/3rd so far after two Sundays. God
knows how many sundays it will take to complete this whole museum.</description></item><item><title>Visit to Ram Krishna Mission</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</guid><description>Ramkrishana Mission or center of Vendantic Society as we know it,
commonly is situated out side of Paris. A great place just to go and
spend some time in peace. It was birth anniversary of Ramkrishana when
we went there first time. We were very unsure how to reach the Center.
But it was a miracle we found some one speaking English at the station
to guide us. This center is quite big area-wise compared to San
Francisco and Berkeley one that we visited.</description></item><item><title>Terry and Greg in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-20-terry-and-greg-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-20-terry-and-greg-in-paris/</guid><description>Terry &amp;ldquo;long hair&amp;rdquo; or that Canadian came to Paris from Palo Alto. It was
nice of Terry, Jaroline (Wife of Terry) and Greg to spend two evenings
with us. It was a great as for the first time we had some friends while
dining. The big surprise was Terry got a nice hair cut in Paris at end
of his trip which was a big change. But,I am sorry I did not have a
camera to capture the same.</description></item><item><title>Moving to Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-18-moving-to-apartment/</guid><description>OK, we moved to our own apartment after all. This whole week was very
busy and hectic.Monday: It started with getting informed that my
checkout from hotel was the very same day. But I was not informed about
this before. And hotel people informed Pamela and disconnected
telephone; a real mess. We could not connect each other and convey what
was happening at two ends. I must have to admit the HR practice is worse
here.</description></item><item><title>Signing the Lease</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-04-signing-the-lease/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-03-04-signing-the-lease/</guid><description>First time we went to sign the lease. They asked me to write cheque of
almost 3000. Oh!!but I didn&amp;rsquo;t had French cheque book yet &amp;amp; there was no
money in the account either. What a shame!!! No one told me. So I went
back to work and found I will be paid only once a month here. Need to
wait till month end.So after a week I came with the cheques and got the
keys of the apartment.</description></item><item><title>Visting top sights</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-23-visting-top-sights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-23-visting-top-sights/</guid><description>Another nice weekend in the month of March and we are trying to see all
the top sights on our guidebook. We must admit this book is indeed a
very good and very nice gift from Akiko and others. A highly recommended
guidebook on Paris by Avant Guide.This time we started with St.
Chappell at Heart of Paris. Wonderful craftsmanship on glass windows,
which tells the story of Bible. Next to it is high court of France.</description></item><item><title>Tour Effiel</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-16-tour-effiel/</guid><description>It was a bright and bleak winter day, we headed straight to the number
one attraction of Paris or Europe as you might say. A great view; this
picture was taken by a Japanese tourist. There were lots of people from
Indian sub-continent selling momento of Eiffel Tower for cheap. But we
left after a while, as it was too cold and windy that day to go at the
top of tower.</description></item><item><title>Finding Apartment</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-12-finding-apartment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-12-finding-apartment/</guid><description>It was now time to find a roof in Paris . But this day was the first day
we really went out in Paris. We were only 5 days old in Paris and the
relocation lady started with a very very bad apartment and kept on
showing till we found a one of our budget with lots of discomfort.
however,Pamela was very skeptical about this place but somehow we agreed
on this after doing lots of calculations.</description></item><item><title>OMI and Prefecture</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-07-omi-and-prefecture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-07-omi-and-prefecture/</guid><description>After getting over with jetlag went to OMI for my medical visit next
morning. It was OK. Tried Metro for the first time (Parlez vous Anglais)
worked. BTW this medical vist is must before any one starts working in
French. But all that good time was so short lived as we reached Cite
Police Prefecture. A very big old building in front of Notre Dame in
center Paris. This is the H.</description></item><item><title>Moved to Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</guid><description>After basking last 4 years in Bay Area we moved to Paris. The weather
was bleak cold which almost blew me off as we were getting in to the
TAXI at the airport. Reached hotel without problem, had a Chinese female
driver speaking English. Exhausted and tired to reach work which looked
like a 5 minutes walk from hotel on map. But, got lost in concrete
jungle of La Defense which is one of the unique place with
concentrated modern high-rise buildings in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Shan &amp; Pam-The Perfect Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2002 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</guid><description>It was the 27thApril 02 &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:green;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;evening,
Every thing was geared up for the Mumbai &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;meeting,
Our “Rosy” flower, made “&amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#ff9900;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;Shan” like a bee &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993300;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;humming,
Not showing outside, Pam thought it was her prince &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993366;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;charming,
Santanu was convinced it was the end of his &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:fuchsia;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;findings,
Gandhiji was nervously smiling,
Shan’s mother in law thought it was perfectly &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;matching,
Pam’s mother and father in law were unable to hide the &amp;lt;span</description></item><item><title>Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-11-08-wedding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2002 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-11-08-wedding/</guid><description>It all started around very early 2002. After few correspondences between
our parents I was asked to come to India in April. After doing some
travelling around, on very last day I met Pamela in-person at Bombay on
27th April. It did not took much time for deciding about the biggest
step of our life.After phone calls and emails for next six months, we
got married on 8th November at Calcutta.</description></item><item><title>Summer 2002</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-08-10-summer-2002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2002 13:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-08-10-summer-2002/</guid><description>Summer of 2002 was a great summer. I did lots of travelling. Thanks to
Tanujoy and Atul for the same. With Atul and I went to Utah for 4 day
trip in July, it was just great!. We visited four national parks and
travelled through very scenic highways.
I went to Yosemite few times for hiking and climbing with members of
PGVIP and with other friends as well.</description></item><item><title>Cameras,Rolls,Photos and Albums</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2002-05-21-cameras-rolls-photos-and-albums/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2002 14:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2002-05-21-cameras-rolls-photos-and-albums/</guid><description>Most of my Web Site is dedicated to photography. In fact, the very
thought of sharing pictures has changed with internet. I like to see
pictures in-print myself. But when you have friends half way accross the
globe, internet is your best friend.The pictures in these albums are
taken by three different cameras. The first camera I had a Pentax. Now I
have a Nikon N-80 and recently bought a Digital camera from Olympus.</description></item></channel></rss>