<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tamilnadu on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/tamilnadu/</link><description>Recent content in Tamilnadu on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 19:03:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/tamilnadu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coonoor - Acre Wild</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-12-21-coonoor-acre-wild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 19:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-12-21-coonoor-acre-wild/</guid><description>We followed road suggested by Mr. Vijay to reach Coonoor, which was
quite deserted except few local people we were the only one on that
road. This road goes via tea gardens and gives a treat to your eyes.
Once we reached Coonoor we parked next to the bus stand and had a quick
thali lunch in nearby busy restaurant. After that we headed towards our
Farmstay - Wild Acre. The direction given by Mr.</description></item><item><title>A magical gateway called - RedHill</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-09-26-a-magical-gateway-called-redhill/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 22:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-09-26-a-magical-gateway-called-redhill/</guid><description>The drive to Ooty was thrilling with those 36 hairpin turns. We reached
the outskirt of the city and asked for direction to Emerald/Avalanche
and reached bypassing central Ooty town. We passed Ooty lake on Lake
Road and crossed Good Shepherd School, Fern Hill Road and at last drove
on Avalanche Road. The place ‘Avalanche’ gets its name as there was a
massive land slide in early 1800. From Emerald (after the bridge) we
took a left and the road condition continued to degrade as we crossed
Avalanche Lake.</description></item><item><title>Masinagudi</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-09-14-masinagudi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-09-14-masinagudi/</guid><description>The long waited Summer Vacation of 2012 ; earlier we used to escape the
peak season madness now we are in the madness since both Aarush and
Pamela are now part of active school. And we are going to be like this
for years to come with no other choice. With that said, still wanted to
avoid the crowded destinations. We wanted to visit ‘ Nilgiris’ the
number uno summer destination of South India and picked Mudumalai,
Ooty(Red Hills) and Connoor.</description></item><item><title>South Trip</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-22-south-trip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 18:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-22-south-trip/</guid><description>Our trip to South was one for which we hardly planned meticulously.
Moreover, my son got fractured elbow but then also our spirit was on
high although bit dampened that whether we will enjoy or not; kind of
excitement mixed with anxiety, hope and happiness. I still remember the
moment we sat in the car and started for the trip which was going to be
one of the longest drive with Aarush.</description></item><item><title>Kanyakumari : Where the Seas Meet</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-02-kanyakumari-where-the-seas-meet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 16:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-08-02-kanyakumari-where-the-seas-meet/</guid><description>Continuing from Madurai
(2010-December); we setup the alarm clock to ensure we do not miss the
sunrise. But to our surprise we were awaken early by anxiety and
whispers from the corridors. We went to see if the Sun was rising soon
but the horizon was dark and there was faint rays of light. We let
Aarush sleep and went to the rooftop where we saw every hotel rooftop is
full of people as all are waiting for the Sun-rise.</description></item><item><title>Yercaud - March'12</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-07-30-yercaud-march12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 17:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-07-30-yercaud-march12/</guid><description>Yercaud is mentioned as poor man&amp;rsquo;s Ooty in 52 weekends
gateway
but the article also mention it is a smart choice compared to Ooty. We
were supposed to visit Yercaud in 2011 September but after wonderful
vacation of
Munnar
and just before Gujarat we cancelled the booking as it was becoming too
much travelling in short span. I strongly believe in the words of
Tagore that good things in life needs to scared or they will become
mediocre :-)</description></item><item><title>Rameshwaram</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-02-24-rameshwaram/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 16:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-02-24-rameshwaram/</guid><description>After complete rest and rainy night we woke up to find a perfect morning
in Madurai. Breakfast at the hotel was quite elaborate and we did a good
one before starting for Rameshwaram. The hotel guys were kind enough
to give us elaborate maps which really helped us to exit Madurai without
asking for any direction. One thing we noticed in Tamil-Nadu the
direction boards are mostly in Tamil and less of English compared to
Karnataka.</description></item><item><title>Madurai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-05-04-madurai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 17:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-05-04-madurai/</guid><description>Started very early morning around 5.45 from our parking lot and with one
stop at A2B restaurant at Krishnagiri reached Madurai exactly by
11.30AM. Then took some time to find out decent hotel two friends
recommended “Royal
Court”
near Madurai railway station. The hotel is clean and neat the management
was great to upgrade our room to executive suite as the original room
smelt cigarettes.
After settling we had a vegetarian south Indian lunch at market area.</description></item><item><title>Auroville</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-10-18-auroville/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 04:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-10-18-auroville/</guid><description>Almost
after one and half year we went for a long weekend out of Bangalore; our
very first road trip of 2010. We were looking for something near to
beach and thought of heading towards Pondichery but due to
unavailability of any sea facing hotel we opted of Auroville.
Certain thing really happens for good. The road was Bangalore -&amp;gt; Krishnagiri -&amp;gt;
Tiruvanamalli -&amp;gt;Tindivanam-&amp;gt; Auroville.As usual Santanu had production outage @ work and went to sleep around 2
AM thanks to ‘new era new tool’ at work.</description></item><item><title>Yelagiri</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-06-19-yelagiri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 00:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-06-19-yelagiri/</guid><description>Really do not recollect how I came first time to
Team-BHP web site, specifically their
forum. And from then on is kind of hooked though not a car freak myself
with limited understanding for these electro-mechanical wonders. What
fascinates me is travelogue section of this forum. It is great to find
so many passionate souls sharing their trips and tricks. Last November
got an unexpected mail about a meet-up @ Yelagiri for Bangalore
team-bhpean; was not sure to join or not.</description></item></channel></rss>