<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anniversary on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/anniversary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anniversary on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 06:15:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/anniversary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>As time flies...</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 06:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-11-13-as-time-flies/</guid>
      <description>We feel elated to celebrate our sixth year of togetherness @ IndiJoe. Ajourney full of sweet, bitter, sour, spicy and many more&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; flavours.After all soft items like paper, linen etc finally we reachedanniversary which is represented by metal -&amp;ldquo;IronAnniversary&amp;rdquo;.
This year&amp;rsquo;s anniversary is extra special because we were given a veryprecious gift from God, our son Aarush, and now we&amp;rsquo;ve moved on from&amp;ldquo;couple&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;small family&amp;rdquo;, and it feels amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiv Jayanti</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid>
      <description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night oflord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindumythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birthanniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17thcentury fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He wasnamed Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabaihad prayed for a son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Krishna!!!</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock featherin his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts andplaying pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony calleddahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day oron the second day of Janmashtami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linen anniversary</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the namingconvention it is LinenAnniversary we have stillhave a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. Afterour wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventfulfor both of us. On this day we went to RamkrishnaMission.Thehour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fallcolor.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Poojaand Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went toSalon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit to Ram Krishna Mission</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-03-30-visit-to-ram-krishna-mission/</guid>
      <description>Ramkrishana Mission or center of Vendantic Society as we know it,commonly is situated out side of Paris. A great place just to go andspend some time in peace. It was birth anniversary of Ramkrishana whenwe went there first time. We were very unsure how to reach the Center.But it was a miracle we found some one speaking English at the stationto guide us. This center is quite big area-wise compared to SanFrancisco and Berkeley one that we visited.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>