<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Badami on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/badami/</link><description>Recent content in Badami on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 01:43:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/badami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Badami and Bijapur</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 01:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</guid><description>Day-4, Morning we woke up early and headed towards to Bansankari
Temple to start our day. Bansankari has lady idol with eight hands which
is worshiped meticulously around. We saw one lady rolling herself around
the whole temple periphery with wet cloth which signifies she just took
a bath in the nearby holy-pond. We got a good darshan of the devi idol
as there was not much crowd in the morning.</description></item><item><title>Aihole and Patadkal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 01:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</guid><description>Day-3, post breakfast we hit the road, this time we followed the GPS
voice of Pamela’s Lumia more attentively and with ease we head out of
Hospet and join the highway. The highway NH-13 between Hospet and
Bijapur is recently widen to 4 lane. It was a pleasure driving, the road
was not at all crowded and surprisingly the trucks maintained the left
lane. Was driving around 110/120 KMph without any trouble and soon
reached Hungund.</description></item><item><title>Road trip - October 2012</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</guid><description>Visiting the northern part of Karnataka for its historic and artistic
monuments were long due. We thought of doing it two years back during
15th August long weekend but postponed the same due to late rain and
high water level at Tungabhadra Rivers. This year we started to plan
early and consulted two avid travelers and their guidance in setting up
the itinerary. It was planned that we would use the 2 weeks school
vacation for this trip, but then I personally felt it would be a great
miss Durga pooja twice in a row.</description></item></channel></rss>