<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>interlaken on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/interlaken/</link><description>Recent content in interlaken on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/interlaken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;quot; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Relaxing Day - 24th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</guid><description>It meant to be a vacation within vacation today. As we did not have to
catch any train neither any bus nor get up early for any fixed
destination. Relaxingly, we had our self-made breakfast and then headed
towards railway station for renting a cycle to bike. At first, we went
towards the city center of Interlaken where there is a big Casino and
park. From there we biked all the way towards the lake Brienz.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item></channel></rss>