<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chocolate on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/chocolate/</link><description>Recent content in chocolate on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/chocolate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>chocolate Banana Muffins</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-12-05-chocolate-banana-muffins/</guid><description>First weekend of December past with lots of activities - a trip to
commercial street, malls and office. On Saturday Aarush forced me to
leave bed early - deprived me of extended sleeping on the weekend. After
that I was busy with him mostly for breakfast. Nowadays he has developed
a nasty habit of prolonged (around an hour or more) eating times be it
breakfast, lunch or dinner. After that he played for while but soon he
was sleepy for nap.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Belgium</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</guid><description>While categorizing our old travelogs I found there was no post on
Belgium
which values a lot for me. As I go down the memory lane&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;year 2003,
within 2 ½ months of marriage we have to move to Paris from US which was
a big change for me. Apart from the cultural shock, language was immense
barrier for day today life as well to mingle up with people around. Not
only that, in Indian arrange marriage, it takes time to understand each
other with each one&amp;rsquo;s weaknesses and failings.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 18:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</guid><description>Another view of Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s Ballard Pier from my desk. May be I am too busy
between meetings so no time to romance with my valentine. Well, heart
shape balloons floating around our office here and there reminding me of
the special day. Due to meetings and tight schedule I even missed the
chocolate distribution. C&amp;rsquo;est dommage!!! :( . Although enormous
work-pressure but many thoughts are coming across to make evening
better.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Making of Chocolate Charlotte</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</guid><description>Today we have a dinner invitation; spent whole yesterday morning in
thinking what would be good to prepare as I did not want to buy anything
from supermarket. Since we are moving, wanted to clean the fridge
without overstuffing it. So after lot of thought came to conclusion that
charlotte might be best. Learnt this recipe from a friend.
A charlotte is any dessert that&amp;rsquo;s moulded into a container lined
with sponge fingers or boudoir biscuits (purchased at a bakery or
supermarket).</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>Paper Anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid><description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventful
for both of us. On this day we went to Ramkrishna
Mission.The
hour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fall
color.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Pooja
and Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went to
Salon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item></channel></rss>