<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Featured on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/featured/</link><description>Recent content in Featured on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 20:58:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visit to hungry tide- Sunderban</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 20:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-02-04-visit-to-hungry-tide-sunderban/</guid><description>For the first time in my life I spent more than 2 nights in a row at
Calcutta. The initial plan was to attend Papai’s wedding reception and
travel to some where around like Digha and back to Bangalore. We got our
Bangalore – Calcutta ticket booked. Going was by train to save money and
return was on flight so that we save time &amp;amp; energy before getting back
to our daily routine.</description></item><item><title>Tonsuring my baby’s head: Tirupati</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 13:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-11-14-tonsuring-my-babys-head-tirupati/</guid><description>Ever since from childhood heard about Tirupati but never had a chance
till date or never understood why people use to grumble till they had
darshan. May be god wanted me to experience the same. Few days back
Santanu suddenly decided to visit before his upcoming hectic weeks at
office. So it was kind of planned-unplanned trip. Why unplanned
knowingly was&amp;hellip;.we didn&amp;rsquo;t had any ticket in hands before starting the
journey nor we had any references to make use of.</description></item><item><title>My baby shower</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 15:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</guid><description>My
baby shower was done in the Bengali traditional way which is called as
Saadh in Bengali. It is meant mostly to pamper the first-time mother
to be and cheer her up as she accumulates courage to face the most
testing time in her life which will soon change her life in and out.
Normally, held in the seventh or ninth month of pregnancy on a
specified day when mother-in-law will organize this ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Bhat Suar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid><description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”
(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my college
days. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of same
state 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similar
to an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”
and second part “suar which means pig”.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
A brief about Paris:Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Paris an unofficial guide by Malc</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2003 20:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-06-welcome-to-paris-an-unofficial-guide-by-malc/</guid><description>Here is a set of stuff about flat hunting, contributed from many
sources. One note. Most of this is for finding a flat on your own.Don&amp;rsquo;t
go near
Hestia.fr (many a tale of woe has originated
from here) Get your &amp;lsquo;dossier&amp;rsquo; together straight away. Needs
photocopy of
Present employment contract
Last 3 pay slips
Last 3 rent receipts (or in my case my 1 year mortgage statement from
the UK)</description></item></channel></rss>