<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>market on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/market/</link><description>Recent content in market on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Whatz FRESH about Reliance Fresh ?</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 04:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-07-23-whatz-fresh-about-reliance-fresh/</guid><description>As we are new to Bangalore trying to explore all nearby hypermarket,
supermarket and open markets as we settle in. This is also giving us as
chance to explore places around. The first one we tried and explored was
BIG-BAZAR on Old Madras road. As it is just near to one of our
office address in Bangalore I knew how to reach there without being
lost. Then weekend after we tried SPAR at Kormongala followed by
Nilgiris.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Tomato Soup</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 20:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</guid><description>Till far only soup ever tried to make was carrot soup in Paris that too
in bleak winter. Big thanks to my French Teacher for sharing the
recipe en Français. Recently, went to local vegetable market; seeing
tomato got so tempted that without thinking bought two kilos. Then I
brainstormed a bit to think and idea of soup came as an escape. Here is
my 2 cents recipe. If craving for something sweet and sour at the
same time just have a bowl of creamy tomato soup to satisfy your desire
as an appetizer.</description></item><item><title>Sunsets in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 21:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Sunset with blue sky of late October seems “magnifique” along with open
space of Navi Mumbai as viewed from local train (picture taken through
window)
This one I clicked last Saturday when I was stuck in middle of JJ
Flyover - the longest flyover in Mumbai (2.3 KM). It is constructed like
a snake, which makes its way through labyrinth of old buildings on
either side; basically you bypass the busy, crowded market underneath.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</guid><description>This picture was taken from my phone camera when I went to do our weekly
vegetable shopping in APMC [Agro Product Market] close to Vashi.
Prices for every vegetables went up. Due to lack of infrastructure it
was a shame to see so much wastage due to heavy rain. From the posture
of the seller it was quite clear he was not looking for lot of customers
as he stretches his back.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid><description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperative
if you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedom
but can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggled
at least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activa
for Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get good
price). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim to
visit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Souvenir</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-31-souvenir/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-31-souvenir/</guid><description>As we were leaving Paris it seems our friends (whom we knew for a short
while) has to give something as a memento. Gifts were extravagant and
really worth mentioning as they chose something which we adore.
To start with gift Pamela got from François is very special. I am sure
she can write a new post about the same. I am just going to give you
brief detail on the same.</description></item><item><title>Making of Chocolate Charlotte</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</guid><description>Today we have a dinner invitation; spent whole yesterday morning in
thinking what would be good to prepare as I did not want to buy anything
from supermarket. Since we are moving, wanted to clean the fridge
without overstuffing it. So after lot of thought came to conclusion that
charlotte might be best. Learnt this recipe from a friend.
A charlotte is any dessert that&amp;rsquo;s moulded into a container lined
with sponge fingers or boudoir biscuits (purchased at a bakery or
supermarket).</description></item><item><title>Green plate</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</guid><description>In
my salad days I used to hate many green veggies and I remember when maa
used to scold me for the same. Somehow I didn’t had taste for them at
that point of time but gradually I developed the taste so much so that I
can now survive happily on those green things (cow-food).
From long time Santanu wanted to make a change on our meal as it seems
we both are putting on weight.</description></item><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Le Marche</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-04-le-marche/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-04-le-marche/</guid><description>The open markets in Paris have been
in existence since ages. It&amp;rsquo;s here that you find freshly picked fruit
and vegetables, fresh fish from Brittany and Normandy, meat, flowers,
farmhouses cheeses, breads – you name it &amp;hellip; its there. Food controls
are very strict in France and be assured of their quality and
cleanliness of preparation. French understands the quality in life and
nothing demonstrates this better than the wonderful food markets in
Paris.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Reached 10K and folding</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-11-16-reached-10k-and-folding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 13:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-11-16-reached-10k-and-folding/</guid><description>Folding @ Home is a Stanford University project of understating protein
folding. It is distributed computing where small tasks are sent to
Personal Computers (PC) across the world and it uses those CPU power to
calculate. The results are sent back to the main computer. It is a very
safe program and probably you will not notice any performance change for
your computer.
There are similar projects for understanding Genome to AIDS which uses
more or less similar technology of distributed computing.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item></channel></rss>