<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nap on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/nap/</link><description>Recent content in nap on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:43:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/nap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Our sleeping beauty</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</guid><description>Aarush never likes to sleep when ever we tried to tuck his hands&amp;hellip;.I
mean with buritto wrap. If wrapped he keeps on moving his hands in
discomfort until he is unwrapped. He always loves to have his hands
free, outstretched in upward direction. This series of pictures which
were taken during half an hour cat&amp;rsquo;s nap. So many positions for two
little hands :D</description></item><item><title>An announcement</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 01:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</guid><description>This announcement was long due on our blog. Though this breaking news
was shared on d-day instantly with friends and families from Hospital
via SMS and emails. I specifically carried my camera, laptop and
wireless data card for the same.
I created two announcement cards one in pink and other in blue with two
names (for girl and boy) and kept them ready. We never disclosed this
big-news in last few months in our blog in-fact it was kept secret to
many except close family members and few friends.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary- Potsdam</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</guid><description>Today sun and clouds chase each other across the skies along the shores
of Berlin as it glides past. We decided to visit Potsdam city situated
on southwest of Berlin known for Sanssouci (without worries) palace;
reached there by train.
As we were short of time having our return ticket to Paris same evening
we opted for sight-seeing guided tour bus available right outside the
train station. So along with other tourists we visited new palace, old
town hall, Fortunaportal and Nikolaikirche at Alter Markt, Schloss
Cecilienhof, Potsdam’s Brandenburg gate, Dutch colony, Russian colony
Alexandrowka providing flair of a city steeped in European tradition.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Venice at leisure</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid><description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after two
days of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s
Square. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was too
crowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out of
time and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.
Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear end
which is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>An afteroon at Pisa</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2007 20:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-23-an-afteroon-at-pisa/</guid><description>Being exhausted from last evening we got up bit late and had very good
breakfast before hitting the road. According to our itinerary, distance
to be covered was long one as our hotel was booked at Florence.
We took train to La Spezia, it was a crowded, got packed with each
passing stations of Cinque Terre but became empty as soon as we
crossed Riomaggiore. We had to wait a bit at La Spezia as train was
coming from north was late.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Thread of love</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</guid><description>It is a celebration of unconditional love between brother and sister in
Hindu culture. This age old celebration tries to remind us of the
beautiful and unique relationship between brother and sister celebrated
since time immemorial. Sisters tie sacred threads on brothers wrist
asking for longer &amp;amp; healthy life of brother and brothers in-turn vow to
protect (to save her- Raksha) their sisters from any unpleasant
situations of life on this day.</description></item><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Bombay International Airport</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid><description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far as
my International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is getting
better and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the pictures
for the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictures
looks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may be
not …quality wise.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-20-celebrations/</guid><description>Looking at those plastic chairs brought back my memories of
Anandamela (a Bengali
children magazine - published fortnight. They used to have picture of
common objects in obscure way and you have to identify the same. I know
this picture is a far cry from those -any way some sweet memories to
reflect upon from fourth floor while taking this picture.
In India celebration is part of life whether big or small ones.</description></item><item><title>Cart in city road</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 21:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</guid><description>While coming to work this morning oxen (castrated male) cart
carrying sugar canes caught my attention. It is not a common site to see
a bullock cart or hand pulled cart (pulled or pushed by a man) at the
heart of Mumbai city next to VT Station.
They are not allowed in the main roads of the city but can only move in
the peripheral roads of the city. These kinds of slow moving objects
cause most notorious traffic jam in India.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</guid><description>This picture was taken from my phone camera when I went to do our weekly
vegetable shopping in APMC [Agro Product Market] close to Vashi.
Prices for every vegetables went up. Due to lack of infrastructure it
was a shame to see so much wastage due to heavy rain. From the posture
of the seller it was quite clear he was not looking for lot of customers
as he stretches his back.</description></item><item><title>China rose</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid><description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soul
into. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit if
they fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,
the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No one
wants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid><description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arranged
for two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. We
opted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in a
non-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary included
Dona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilica
and se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurga
dedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit to
Ancestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description></item><item><title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid><description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I got
opportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, I
couldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarried
Indian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as an
escort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered like
friend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description></item><item><title>Little Visitor at Office Window</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 22:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-13-little-visitor-at-office-window/</guid><description>Friday again, I am already at work for last nine hours(reached around
8ish). Wow! that&amp;rsquo;s lot and time to head towards home soon.
Today, after lots of failure attempt I some how succeeded to capture a
very cute visitor at my window. I have no idea what kind of bird is
this, going to ask one expert for the same. Well, Pamela is working very
hard to upload pictures from Goa and writing trip details – hope this
weekend we upload them.</description></item><item><title>Mera Bharat Jawaan</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 22:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-04-mera-bharat-jawaan/</guid><description>Another funny advertisement which caught my attention Budda Hoga Tera
Baap. This is a soft or hard slang depending on your view - &amp;ldquo;May be
your father is old&amp;rdquo; This new TV series name is &amp;ldquo;Mera Bharat
Jaawan&amp;rdquo; which translates into &amp;ldquo;My India is Young&amp;rdquo;. With one fourth
population under the age of 25 India definitely has young demography.
P.S - In last two months, I have changed theme for wordpress (blog) at
least four times.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine -II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 19:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</guid><description>As I said lots of thoughts were coming
across in spite of
my busy-ness. So first was to ask Pamela to come over at Fort area for
lunch which was denied by her saying that lots of household chores left
to be done. Then again I modified my plan and asked her to join at
evening for dinner when she told me she won’t as without any prior
booking no food will be available at any good restaurant because of that
day- which is in fact quite true.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 18:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-14-saint-valentine/</guid><description>Another view of Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s Ballard Pier from my desk. May be I am too busy
between meetings so no time to romance with my valentine. Well, heart
shape balloons floating around our office here and there reminding me of
the special day. Due to meetings and tight schedule I even missed the
chocolate distribution. C&amp;rsquo;est dommage!!! :( . Although enormous
work-pressure but many thoughts are coming across to make evening
better.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Micro$oft Launch @ Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-21-micro-oft-launch-mumbai/</guid><description>Micro$oft is doing a round of business and technical launch show around
India. The products are Exchange 2007, Office 2007 and Vista. I attended
only a brief session @ Hyatt.
Well, somehow my name was not there even though I registered 10 days
before the event.
And my business card with orange and blue dots did not help much to get
attention from those desk people. Anyway, it was solid 40 minutes of
work for me – replied emails, chat with business contact got updates
from their team – thanks to CDMA mobile card.</description></item><item><title>Zooomr Pro</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-16-zooomr-pro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2007 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-16-zooomr-pro/</guid><description>After trying my luck with flickr I figured out that I have to look for
alternative. With Yahoo! there is nothing for free. Almost certainly
they will follow suit when someone else win in their own game like gmail
vs yahoo-mail. So trying my luck for Zooomr pro now.
P.S. I got the pro account :D</description></item><item><title>Another weekend</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2007 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-13-another-weekend/</guid><description>Well another day! Some techie note ; upgraded the web site to the latest
beta release of Wordpress. And I found some strange behaviour. This is
what I put forward to the mailing list. But with few minute of research
found the root cause.
WP is adding [code]
[/code] as extra inside in my [code]
[/code]This was one example.[code]
[/code]
It was happening due to &amp;ldquo;wp-include/formatting.php&amp;rdquo;. I use plain
text mode while doing copy-paste between text-editor from my PC to
Wordpress Editor.</description></item><item><title>Travel Under Terror</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 00:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-01-06-travel-under-terror/</guid><description>There were massive bomb blasts last summer in Mumbai local trains. After
that now there are constant reminders for the commuters to be on alert
and check their surroundings. It is logistical nightmare to manage the
massive number of commuters who takes train every day in Mumbai. In
simple words, “impossible” will be closest word I can pick.
Few months back after lots of planning and public announcement Mumbai
Police conducted a security drill where every passenger was supposed to
pass via metal detector in two Main Terminus in the evening but after
few moments it was clear that police can not handle the stream of
passengers in lakhs and crores as they were heading home and it was
abandoned.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item><item><title>Friday 12th May</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 15:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</guid><description>Just another weekend of May in Paris. I don&amp;rsquo;t know any other time when
the weather can be so beautiful with clear sky and warm temperature.
Right now, all the horse chestnut
trees along wide
boulevards are full of white flowers. This tree is also known as
Marronier d&amp;rsquo;Inde, thanks to Francois for introducing the same.
Truly, if one cheers up and forgets all the problems round him-it is a
romantic experience in itself.</description></item><item><title>Home Network ADSL-Network-Phone</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</guid><description>I just wanted to share my home network. It is not a state of
technologies with the latest &amp;amp; greatest wireless or wired network with
complex router and switches. I did it in old school way with a single
long CAT5 Ethernet Cable. I have a FreeBox which is an ADSL2 router
connecting to the main phone jack. The output from the
FreeBox connects my PC, Television and
Phone. Now all these components are connected with the single wire as
I mentioned before.</description></item><item><title>Paris in night mode</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 20:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</guid><description>I wanted to take pictures of Paris famous landmarks in the twilight with
a tripod. We started with Sacre-coeur Basilica. And the picture we got
from there was really great as we were there on the right time. The sky
color was perfect for the camera and it was just lighted.
From there we went to Moulin-Rouge; the famous cabaret of Paris then to
Assembly National the French Parliament. We crossed Seine and came to
Concord.</description></item></channel></rss>