<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>running on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/running/</link><description>Recent content in running on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 19:38:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/running/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2016 Planning</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2016-01-13-2016-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 19:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2016-01-13-2016-planning/</guid><description>Some Runs/Race I would like to do in 2016.
14-Feb-2016 Auroville Marathon 06-Mar-2016 IDBI Kolkata Marathon ( can not go but listing ) 19-Mar-2016 Nirbhaya Midnight Marathon (Bangalore) 12-Jun-2016 Run Your First Half or Full Marathon (Jaynagar Jaguar
date not confirmed) 17-Jul-2016 The Cherrapunjee Marathon 28-Aug-2016 Airtel Hyderabad Marathon 11-Sep-2016 Chennai Trail Marathon 16-Oct-2016 Bengaluru Marathon</description></item><item><title>Cochin Full Marathon 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 15:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-11-25-cochin-full-marathon-2015/</guid><description>Pre-Race Day
The day started early, we get out Cochin Club today and part our our
ways for some time. While Pamela &amp;amp; Aarush goes back to Bangalore on
Saturday itself I stay back for the big run on Sunday.
They had a train to catch around 9 from ERS. There was not a single auto
around so had to walk and get one from Ferry station and as usual the
price asked and agreed is way more than normal,</description></item><item><title>Satara HM 2015</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-09-23-satara-hm-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 11:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-09-23-satara-hm-2015/</guid><description>Satara is located in Maharashtra not very far from Pune,
Mahabaleshwar located
in western ghat. PaceMakers decided to run this HM instead of Hyderabad
beginning of the year and booked a complete hotel in February itself.
That caused a uproar in Indian armature running community. The
registration for Satara HM for out station also got closed as there is a
limited hotel accommodation in this town. Personally I was not very
keen to run to it given the remote location and no direct train and
flight.</description></item><item><title>43 seconds and counting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 10:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-08-31-43-seconds-and-counting/</guid><description>Third year in a row ran Airtel Hyderabad half
marathon yesterday. There was many
things which were different from 2013. Looking back 2013 was my second
outstation race with PaceMakers. We
traveled in train and return journey was not a great one as we had to
travel in sleeper class. The fun was most of us did not had bed linen as
we forgot how it was to travel in sleeper class.</description></item><item><title>What a Saturday</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-07-what-a-saturday/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 12:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-07-what-a-saturday/</guid><description>Woke up at 4:25 AM ; it was supposed it be a a long day for me as I try
to run 39 KM practice run in a easy pace. Though I am not going to
participate in the upcoming SCMM (Standard Chartered Mumbai Marathon)
2015 I decided to stick with the full marathoner group to see how
grueling their preparation can be. Assembled at 4:45 in front of the NCBS gate and met an ultra marathoner
from our running group who already covered 23KM starting from 02:30 AM.</description></item><item><title>Sharat - when rains give way to the early autumn with blue skies, mid-August to mid-October.</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-12-03-sharat-when-rains-give-way-to-the-early-autumn-with-blue-skies-mid-august-to-mid-october/</guid><description>Month of September 2014 was a unique one. It started like just another
month of the year.
Honestly it has 17th September which is most times ‘Bishwakarma Puja’
and Pamela’s B’day and that is how I remember it. From childhood
Bishwakarma puja has a special mention growing up in Tripura. After
Saraswati puja in January/February there was no major festival till
Bishwakarma Puja. And there used to pandals and people going out in the
evening to visit those pandals.</description></item><item><title>Airtel Hyderabad Half Marathon 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-09-02-airtel-hyderabad-half-marathon-2014/</guid><description>After Chennai DRHM event the event I signed up for was Airtel Hyderabad
Half Marathon. This run is little special to me as received my first
ever finisher T-shirt last year as a proof of my improvement in running.
Also there is the big culinary charm of Dine-hill and Karachi biscuits
as post run celebration.
Booked myself a return flight as soon as the dates for AHM 2014 was out.</description></item><item><title>DRHM Chennai 2014</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-07-03-drhm-chennai-2014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 14:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-07-03-drhm-chennai-2014/</guid><description>Enough is enough I said to myself before I started to write down my
experience with 2014 Chennai Dream Runners Half marathon. After waiting
for weeks and getting constant update on social media that my friends
are being tagged in various albums I could not found a single picture of
myself what a pity when everyone was clicking with those super sharp
DSLRs and smart phones.
Like last year we travelled to Chennai in Shatabdi Express on Saturday
starting early morning from Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Mysore Half Marathon 2013</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</guid><description>This was Mysore Celebration Run 2013 ; well there was BIG celebration at
Pacemakers running group. Coach was brand ambassador of the run, we had
a promo run in Bangalore for the same. Few runners from group also got
featured in Life is Calling&amp;rsquo;s web
site.
Initially I was against this run as I rescheduled my Mother&amp;rsquo;s return
flight from Bangalore to Siliguri on the same Sunday :(. But big thanks
to Maa and Pamela as they supported to run me this event.</description></item><item><title>Blessed</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-28-blessed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 03:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-28-blessed/</guid><description>Blessing is a simple word, but yesterday night (Monday) just before
sleeping I was thinking about the same again and again. Wished for a
gadget to record my thought as I was too tired to use any keyboard or
voice recorder. At times we wonder and sometime make fun of those award
ceremonies where people on the stage keep on thanking people around him
or her and sometimes even their dogs.</description></item><item><title>Chennai DRHM</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</guid><description>Chennai DRHM ( Dream Runners Half
Marathon) was on
1st Sunday of July i.e. 7thJuly 2013. It was the first run
out of Bangalore for me. Last time I registered for Mumbai Standard
Chartered was in 2008 and was gifted with Aarush just few days before
the race :D Well Aarush is the reason why I can not run on weekdays
morning but he is the catalyst who introduced me to The Pacemakers
running group of Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Running Paris Versailles</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-26-running-paris-versailles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2005 00:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-26-running-paris-versailles/</guid><description>Almost after one and half year I was
running in any event. The weather was very grey but it was very pleasant
for running. Temperature was around 16 degree Celsius. The race was 17KM
long starting from bottom of Eiffel Tower to Château de
Versailles.For the first time, Pamela accompanied me to the starting point of the
course so as to take a photo of mine with Eiffel Tower. The first part
of the run was along River Seine and then it goes to Forest of Meudon;
this was the most crucial part as it has a steep climb (approx.</description></item></channel></rss>