<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lake shore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/lake-shore/</link><description>Recent content in lake shore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/lake-shore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Relaxing Day - 24th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</guid><description>It meant to be a vacation within vacation today. As we did not have to
catch any train neither any bus nor get up early for any fixed
destination. Relaxingly, we had our self-made breakfast and then headed
towards railway station for renting a cycle to bike. At first, we went
towards the city center of Interlaken where there is a big Casino and
park. From there we biked all the way towards the lake Brienz.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item></channel></rss>