<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Berlin on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/berlin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Berlin on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/berlin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Diary- Potsdam</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</guid>
      <description>Today sun and clouds chase each other across the skies along the shoresof Berlin as it glides past. We decided to visit Potsdam city situatedon southwest of Berlin known for Sanssouci (without worries) palace;reached there by train.
As we were short of time having our return ticket to Paris same eveningwe opted for sight-seeing guided tour bus available right outside thetrain station. So along with other tourists we visited new palace, oldtown hall, Fortunaportal and Nikolaikirche at Alter Markt, SchlossCecilienhof, Potsdam’s Brandenburg gate, Dutch colony, Russian colonyAlexandrowka providing flair of a city steeped in European tradition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Diary II</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid>
      <description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past ofGermany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee atStarbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point betweenEast and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash throughour mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition ofBerlin wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Diary</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid>
      <description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet anothertrip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. Atrip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend whensky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’tdeter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>