<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>moon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/moon/</link><description>Recent content in moon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 04:12:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/moon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sweet potato dessert</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</guid><description>Sweet potato dessert (Ranga Alur Puli) is an age old Bengali dessert - a
sweet lover&amp;rsquo;s delight for sure. Its crispy outer layer mesmerizes
gastronomic senses. As for its availability, it is more of a
traditional sweet, prepared in households. These days some sweet shops
are starting to include this in their repertoire to cater to the
time-constrained generation.
My hubby being born with a sweet tooth, do enjoy sweet of any kind.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid><description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I got
opportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, I
couldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarried
Indian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as an
escort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered like
friend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description></item><item><title>Mumbaiya Lingo</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 03:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-06-mumbaiya-lingo/</guid><description>While boarding a train I heard one co-passenger saying to another
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” which astonished me for a fraction of
second as its not at all palatable to an untrained ears. It seems this
“Tabadtod andar jaane ka” is considered far more effective while getting
into locals then long winded formal request to the people ahead to make
way.
I was trying hard to relate as it sounds hindi but actually its not.</description></item><item><title>Aids Awareness - Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2006 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</guid><description>Can any one guess what this publicity is about? Well, this is 2006 anti
Aids campaign by city hall of Paris (Paris protège l&amp;rsquo;amour means
Paris protects love)
In the photo what we see is sunset on some historical building with moon
at backdrop, but when you take a close look moon is&amp;hellip; a condom. It aims
at promoting the use of condoms among the population i.e., to have safe
sex.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>Itlay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 12:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</guid><description>We have been to Rome for 4 days in 2003 but we wanted to visit the other
parts of Italy but could not do that due to time constrain. We were
planning for trip to Florence, Venice etc old classic route for long
time.
Krovi and Vidya went to Italy on their paper honeymoon which was 3
weeks earlier than us and they did provided us with lots of good tips.</description></item></channel></rss>