<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>India on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/india/</link><description>Recent content in India on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Day - 2 Dehradun &amp; Haridwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 15:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-09-13-day-2-dehradun-haridwar/</guid><description>We
work up fresh after a good sleep. But soon we realized we are in a place
which we are very not fond off. May be the Mussoorie did not blink with
us. After taking shower and getting ready for the day we went up to the
restaurant for breakfast. But looked like we were an early riser as
there were no one else and the place was not cleaned up for the day.</description></item><item><title>Uttarakhand - prelude</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2017-05-31-uttarakhand-prelude/</guid><description>*It
has been such a long time that we posted something we almost forgot how
to type long paragraphs. Maybe all due to Facebook and WhatsApp which is
instant but then in when you look back you have no way to figure out
what all the noise was about. Well enough of rant now let me
type….*Beginning
of 2017 we were very much looking for a vacation and Pamela was
interested in Uttarakhand.</description></item><item><title>Indian Mobile scene and future ....</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2014-07-17-indian-mobile-scene-and-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 15:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2014-07-17-indian-mobile-scene-and-future/</guid><description>As you know the growth of mobile is one of BIG discussion point of any
technology seminar or talk show you attend today. Everybody already
predicting more and more people will use mobile to access
internet/information/e-commerce compared to traditional desktop or
laptop. And in a country like India there will be lots of users who will
be &amp;ldquo;on-line&amp;rdquo; for the first time and they will directly use a smart
phone bypassing key-board and mice altogether, in numbers they might be
larger than some European country.</description></item><item><title>Puri – Konark</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-10-03-puri-konark/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 21:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-10-03-puri-konark/</guid><description>We had to extend our planned holidays as we
got a last minute invitation for my cousin&amp;rsquo;s marriage now both marriages
were only 6 days apart. Personally was quite unhappy about the whole
situation of attending two marriages; instead of voicing opinions, kept
cribbing and ranting. Confronting such family matters does not work as
no one is right. Anyways, at times you are forced to go along with such
decision whether you like it or not.</description></item><item><title>Lavazza in India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 18:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-10-lavazza-in-india/</guid><description>Just saw this advertisement on BBC website while checking my morning
dose of news. I was quite fascinated by this ad. Immediately started to
think “Oh this is great!!” now I can get a great coffee to start my
day at home by pressing a button.
If you are not familiar with this machine or not a coffee person this
machine uses special coffee capsules to dispense coffee. There are
varieties of flavor to choose from and trust me it really makes great
coffee.</description></item><item><title>Vacation on the horizon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid><description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)
when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard of
travelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May be
it is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visit
some country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not at
all interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Paris
cold all the time.</description></item></channel></rss>