<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>France on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/france/</link><description>Recent content in France on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yum……..</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 19:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-26-yum/</guid><description>Normally
Santanu has a tendency of encroaching cuisine area particularly on
weekend or on his official holidays depending on his mood. In a way,
it’s good as I get 2 days off.
We were just back from Switzerland and went for picnic at
St.-Germain-en-Laye with few colleagues of Santanu. And Santanu promised
he is going to prepare all by himself -simple vegetable-rice and Date
walnut brownies.
Lately I borrowed one book on vegetarian by Nicolas Graimes from one
friend which includes light meals, main courses, tarts, salads, desserts
etc.</description></item><item><title>C’est fou !</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</guid><description>Football - the definition for the same may be quite simple but it
certainly does have lots of colors. It is a mutli-billion dollar
business from sporting to TV companies. For some it is as close to their
religion. People can fight or hug with a complete stranger while
ignoring his family or close one when there is a match.
As we live in Europe it is very hard to escape it.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>St. Michel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2004 22:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</guid><description>Perched on a rocky islet in the midst of vast sandbanks exposed to
powerful tides between Normandy and Brittany (on the north coast of
France) stand the &amp;lsquo;Wonder of the West&amp;rsquo;, a Gothic-style abbey dedicated
to the Archangel St Michael
It was built in 8thcentury, the buildings of Mont St. Michel
were constructed of granite which were carried from near-by island but
some limestone were also used in the cloister.</description></item><item><title>Cantal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2003 10:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</guid><description>The first trip to France countryside was to Cantal -central region for 3
days with Murali &amp;amp; Joydeep on July 14th. Cantal, in France&amp;rsquo;s Massif
Central, is the largest volcanic edifice in Europe. We went by car,
Murali did a wonderful job by seating at the back of steering wheel &amp;amp;
Joydeep at navigator’s seat while we two were enjoying sleeping (from
time to time) at back seat. We enjoyed a natural landscape which was
really worth seeing through own eyes- rolling hills, lush green
farmlands, small mountains, forests &amp;amp; valleys.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item></channel></rss>