<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>airport on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/airport/</link>
    <description>Recent content in airport on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/airport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebbal Lake</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress onconstruction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as atwork things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is anice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes ahappy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in nextmonth this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that isgoing to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from trip</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stayin Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did notvisit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather whichever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: thispicture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bombay International Airport</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid>
      <description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far asmy International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is gettingbetter and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the picturesfor the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictureslooks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may benot …quality wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid>
      <description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperativeif you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedombut can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggledat least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activafor Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get goodprice). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim tovisit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid>
      <description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I gotopportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, Icouldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarriedIndian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as anescort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered likefriend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le vol</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 09:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</guid>
      <description>I am not a person who hates flying to start with as my major air-travelin recent years was visiting India on holiday from Europe. Like allother events in life this can be looked at like a coin; on one side thetravel time has reduced significantly while on other side only 20 to 30kilos of baggage allowed compared to California (65 Kilo).
As we were moving out of Paris we had lot of important things to bringalong with us that we will need till our shipment arrives in next 5weeks time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uddan - Flight</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid>
      <description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing itspublicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in theworld. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouragedus to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar coveringaround 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooththough they were very strict about luggage weight.

In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough legroom; quality of the food was better than what we had before and wasgood with choice of films and music on demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cordoba – Spain</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid>
      <description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought ofCordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggestedvisiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reachthe train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. Thefair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costsalmost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vienna - Austria</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid>
      <description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. Itwas a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outsideof city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” andwe preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for ourtrips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentionedit has Metro next to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rome (Sep 5th-7th)</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 09:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-09-15-rome-sep-5th-7th/</guid>
      <description>We wanted to visit all the top attractions of Italy in one trip but dueto vacation time (for Parisians) and taking off from work and withPamela&amp;rsquo;s school we could not do. So, we planned for only Rome. Weflew with Alitalia from CDG this time in early morning. It was muchbetter than Ryan Airlines in terms of access to the airport. But theinitial fun started when just before checking-in we have to run 3terminals to collect our tickets from Air Traffic office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockholm (Aug 14th - 17th)</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2003 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</guid>
      <description>While browsing through web sites for summer travel deals I found therewas a very attractive deal by Ryan Air to Stockholm.We went there middleof August when Paris was burning with summer heat. It was a great escapeto Scandinavia. Stockholm was very clean and very beautiful. Although,the weather was not at its best as it rained for first two days.
We stayed in the centre of Stockholm (Drottninggatan) one side of thispedestrian street with full of shops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved to Paris</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</guid>
      <description>After basking last 4 years in Bay Area we moved to Paris. The weatherwas bleak cold which almost blew me off as we were getting in to theTAXI at the airport. Reached hotel without problem, had a Chinese femaledriver speaking English. Exhausted and tired to reach work which lookedlike a 5 minutes walk from hotel on map. But, got lost in concretejungle of La Defense which is one of the unique place withconcentrated modern high-rise buildings in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>