<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transport on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/transport/</link><description>Recent content in transport on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bhat Suar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid><description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”
(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my college
days. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of same
state 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similar
to an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”
and second part “suar which means pig”.</description></item><item><title>Hebbal Lake</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid><description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress on
construction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as at
work things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is a
nice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes a
happy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in next
month this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that is
going to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>Cart in city road</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 21:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</guid><description>While coming to work this morning oxen (castrated male) cart
carrying sugar canes caught my attention. It is not a common site to see
a bullock cart or hand pulled cart (pulled or pushed by a man) at the
heart of Mumbai city next to VT Station.
They are not allowed in the main roads of the city but can only move in
the peripheral roads of the city. These kinds of slow moving objects
cause most notorious traffic jam in India.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Metro in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-29-metro-in-paris/</guid><description>Living in Paris and not travelling in Metro has lots of demerits. Like
usual I am going to start with the traffic jams, one way roads,
unavailability of parking, high parking tickets and very unusual sense
of Parisian driving skills.
These only list if you have a car and travelling of your own. But what
about those who are taking other mode of smart transports like Bus,
Tram, Bicycle, Rollerblade or just walk to work or work from home?</description></item><item><title>Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2005 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</guid><description>The temperature in Spain was quite hot compared to Paris. It was around
37° C when we reached Granada in the afternoon. The bus station for
intercity is not at the city center but there is a good connection of
public transport for the same. Our hotel was at the center - Plaza
Royal.
Around 5 PM, we headed out from hotel, it was still very hot and bright.
We walked towards Plaza Nueva.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item><item><title>A year in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2004 04:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-02-20-a-year-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved to Paris almost a year back from US. We try to travel around at
least once a month outside of Paris. This year so far we have been to
Zurich, Mt. Saint Michel and Barcelona.
I like Paris but some time French system and people makes me mad. I am
going to run Paris Half marathon in March first week. Now a days I am
trying to run more regularly.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item><item><title>Metro on Strike</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</guid><description>It started on Tuesday the 13th. My manager gave me a lift to work. On
the way back I walked, it was long but nice walk through Bois de
BoulogneWednesday, the strike was supposed to end; but it continued in
a French way. So, I have to work hard to fix my bike and went by bike to
work. In that process I got an ache on to my shoulder, which did not
allow me to sleep for a whole week.</description></item></channel></rss>