<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>monsoon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/monsoon/</link><description>Recent content in monsoon on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/monsoon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>Rainy Sunday</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 05:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-26-rainy-sunday/</guid><description>This picture was taken from my phone camera when I went to do our weekly
vegetable shopping in APMC [Agro Product Market] close to Vashi.
Prices for every vegetables went up. Due to lack of infrastructure it
was a shame to see so much wastage due to heavy rain. From the posture
of the seller it was quite clear he was not looking for lot of customers
as he stretches his back.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item></channel></rss>