<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>food on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/food/</link><description>Recent content in food on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Venice at leisure</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid><description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after two
days of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s
Square. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was too
crowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out of
time and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.
Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear end
which is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description></item><item><title>Cinqueterre – Mediterranean nirvana</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-22-cinqueterre-mediterranean-nirvana/</guid><description>We got up early had a quick breakfast and dragged our bags to Milan
Central Station; bought our ticket for next destination
“Cinqueterre” - refers to five small villages (Corniglia,
Manarola, Monterosso al Mare, Riomaggiore and Vernazza) - cling to
the rugged mountains along Mediterranean coastline with breath taking
view.
This UNSECO heritage site is not on the main train line or motor-way
that connects Milan to Rome. To get there, we have to cross the mountain
to reach the western side of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Belgium</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 05:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-17-remembering-belgium/</guid><description>While categorizing our old travelogs I found there was no post on
Belgium
which values a lot for me. As I go down the memory lane&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;year 2003,
within 2 ½ months of marriage we have to move to Paris from US which was
a big change for me. Apart from the cultural shock, language was immense
barrier for day today life as well to mingle up with people around. Not
only that, in Indian arrange marriage, it takes time to understand each
other with each one&amp;rsquo;s weaknesses and failings.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sweet teeth</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-04-sweet-teeth/</guid><description>From this Monday I moved to a corner desk as I put a new pair of shoes
at work. The desk is nice but I lost my view from the
window.
Well, this post is not about my office and work.
Our boss is sailing Far-East and we had a dinner at Marine Plaza
Hotel honoring him. The location of
the hotel is great and as we were a big group we got a hall to ourself
facing Black Bay and Marine-Drive of Mumbai.</description></item><item><title>Udupi Thali</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 05:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-04-udupi-thali/</guid><description>This thali is named after a small town of South western coast of India
Udupi near to Mangalore. It is famous for Krishna temple where
from udupi (also called udipi) cuisine got originated. It is basically
delicious vegetarian cuisine with no onion, garlic as commonly found
in rich north Indian cuisine. Udupi cuisine comprises dishes made from
grains, beans, vegetables. The variety and range of dishes are wide and
a hallmark of this cuisine is the use of locally available
ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Hearty Healthy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 03:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-30-hearty-healthy/</guid><description>It’s too hot and humid with power failure I was sweating like a hell.
Though just few minutes before I took my shower. Having my last portion
of lunch I was searching desperately for something in my fridge but
actually I forgot to buy one. My all time favourite item which I can
even take truckload if needed in any form. It is generally considered to
cool the body in tropical climates.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid><description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arranged
for two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. We
opted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in a
non-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary included
Dona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilica
and se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurga
dedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit to
Ancestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Saint Valentine -II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 19:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-14-saint-valentine-ii/</guid><description>As I said lots of thoughts were coming
across in spite of
my busy-ness. So first was to ask Pamela to come over at Fort area for
lunch which was denied by her saying that lots of household chores left
to be done. Then again I modified my plan and asked her to join at
evening for dinner when she told me she won’t as without any prior
booking no food will be available at any good restaurant because of that
day- which is in fact quite true.</description></item><item><title>Britania - Irani Restaurant</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2007 20:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-27-britania-irani-restaurant/</guid><description>Ballard Estate is old corporate park in Mumbai where most of the
buildings have high ceiling and windows a left-over from British Raj. I
feel very fortunate as my workplace is on this street and moreover when
I get bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of Mumbai from my desk.
For lunch, I have walked past Britannia before but for some or other
reason I did not entered. It is one of Bombay&amp;rsquo;s famous old Irani
(Persian) restaurants situated at Ballard Estate.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Making of Chocolate Charlotte</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-28-making-of-chocolate-charlotte/</guid><description>Today we have a dinner invitation; spent whole yesterday morning in
thinking what would be good to prepare as I did not want to buy anything
from supermarket. Since we are moving, wanted to clean the fridge
without overstuffing it. So after lot of thought came to conclusion that
charlotte might be best. Learnt this recipe from a friend.
A charlotte is any dessert that&amp;rsquo;s moulded into a container lined
with sponge fingers or boudoir biscuits (purchased at a bakery or
supermarket).</description></item><item><title>Italian aroma…</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 16:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-01-italian-aroma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Daney Daney Pey likha hain khaney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo;- which
colloquially means each grain has the name of the person who will eat it
(it is the fortune of the person to have certain meal or not). Well the
same with more of spice in Hindi movies &amp;ldquo;goli goli pey likha hain
marney waley kaa naam&amp;rdquo; which means in each bullets it is written the
name of the person who will die.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Green plate</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 20:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-30-green-plate/</guid><description>In
my salad days I used to hate many green veggies and I remember when maa
used to scold me for the same. Somehow I didn’t had taste for them at
that point of time but gradually I developed the taste so much so that I
can now survive happily on those green things (cow-food).
From long time Santanu wanted to make a change on our meal as it seems
we both are putting on weight.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Le Marche</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-04-le-marche/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-04-le-marche/</guid><description>The open markets in Paris have been
in existence since ages. It&amp;rsquo;s here that you find freshly picked fruit
and vegetables, fresh fish from Brittany and Normandy, meat, flowers,
farmhouses cheeses, breads – you name it &amp;hellip; its there. Food controls
are very strict in France and be assured of their quality and
cleanliness of preparation. French understands the quality in life and
nothing demonstrates this better than the wonderful food markets in
Paris.</description></item><item><title>Uddan - Flight</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid><description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing its
publicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in the
world. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouraged
us to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar covering
around 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooth
though they were very strict about luggage weight.
In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough leg
room; quality of the food was better than what we had before and was
good with choice of films and music on demand.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 18:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</guid><description>When I was on my vacation last week in Spain and Portugal, was thinking
about to write down all that we had experienced there - the places we
visted and food we tasted and others. But back to work it is such a
Dilbert place that I can not explain with my logic.
Also I need to find a cheap solution to restore pictures from Smart
Media. It looks like there is a well suited option commercial for 40
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Alhambra - Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</guid><description>We did not book our tickets for Alhambra before coming to Granada. There
can be 8,000 visitors inside Alhambra in a given day. Out of those 8,000
around 6,500 are sold over internet &amp;amp; phone. So for us, it meant getting
up early and queuing up in the morning. As it was Monday and not peak of
tourist season&amp;hellip; we were lucky.
Alhambra has main 4 sites to visit.
The main attraction is of course &amp;ldquo;Palacios Nazaries&amp;rdquo; the best preserved
Moorish Palace in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>Cantal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2003 10:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</guid><description>The first trip to France countryside was to Cantal -central region for 3
days with Murali &amp;amp; Joydeep on July 14th. Cantal, in France&amp;rsquo;s Massif
Central, is the largest volcanic edifice in Europe. We went by car,
Murali did a wonderful job by seating at the back of steering wheel &amp;amp;
Joydeep at navigator’s seat while we two were enjoying sleeping (from
time to time) at back seat. We enjoyed a natural landscape which was
really worth seeing through own eyes- rolling hills, lush green
farmlands, small mountains, forests &amp;amp; valleys.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
A brief about Paris:Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item><item><title>Picnic with Ritu</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-04-19-picnic-with-ritu/</guid><description>It has been a long time we were exchanging e-mails and phone calls with
Ritu, but could not meet her in-person. She is a friend of Akiko&amp;rsquo;s Paris
friend. A long chain; but a start to make social contacts in new place.
I am personally not that social to make friends at party or other social
gatherings that is one reason holding me to join local Expats club.Ritu
arranged a great picnic and was very nice to meet all other expaticians.</description></item></channel></rss>