<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>festival on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/festival/</link><description>Recent content in festival on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 18:50:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/festival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Festival of lights</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</guid><description>Today as we celebrate India’s grand festival of Light signaling triumph
over evil after a protracted fight which is marked by lighting of oil
based traditional earthen or clay lamps as they shine brightly in each
and every home - Be it lowly or mightily from the hut of the poor to the
mansion of the rich when good with all its might, leads us from darkness
to light. A day when old and young indulge in royal feast on this
festival of snacks and sweet.</description></item><item><title>Festivity begins</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-16-festivity-begins/</guid><description>Monsoon is about to end. So begins the celebrations and festivals across
India. Any Indian festival is incomplete without the typical Indian
festivities, the gatherings, celebrations, exchange of sweets and gifts,
lots of noise, singing and dancing. Festivals are the celebration of
not only togetherness but also being part of the family.
In India, monsoon follows FIFO (first in first out) model so the
festivals. As the fields look brilliant with a bountiful harvest; the
beautiful landscape of greenery can be seen in its full radiance at this
time.</description></item><item><title>O Krishna!!!</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 02:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-04-o-krishna/</guid><description>Celebrating the birth anniversary of blue boy with peacock feather
in his wreath, flute in one hand and making efforts to steal pots of butter,
butter-milk or dahi (curd); well known for his mischievous acts and
playing pranks on gopis (cow herding girls).
Based on his stealing efforts there is a very popular ceremony called
dahi-handi celebrated with lot of enthusiasm and glee on this day or
on the second day of Janmashtami.</description></item><item><title>Thread of love</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-28-thread-of-love/</guid><description>It is a celebration of unconditional love between brother and sister in
Hindu culture. This age old celebration tries to remind us of the
beautiful and unique relationship between brother and sister celebrated
since time immemorial. Sisters tie sacred threads on brothers wrist
asking for longer &amp;amp; healthy life of brother and brothers in-turn vow to
protect (to save her- Raksha) their sisters from any unpleasant
situations of life on this day.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-20-celebrations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-20-celebrations/</guid><description>Looking at those plastic chairs brought back my memories of
Anandamela (a Bengali
children magazine - published fortnight. They used to have picture of
common objects in obscure way and you have to identify the same. I know
this picture is a far cry from those -any way some sweet memories to
reflect upon from fourth floor while taking this picture.
In India celebration is part of life whether big or small ones.</description></item><item><title>W questions of Indian life</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</guid><description>In India, life of middle class is different compared to occidental
culture. There is a vast population of middle class in India and within
middle class there are three distinct sub-divisions - “lower
middleclass”, “middle middleclass” and “higher middleclass”.
Comprehending the complexities of Indian society is not that easy.
Though there are variations in socio-economic life within these three
but one thing is common between all of them - everyone is curious to
know whatz happening in others life despite of their own busy life.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>London 5days (July 29th - Aug 3rd)</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2003 23:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-08-11-london-5days-july-29th-aug-3rd/</guid><description>We went to London the proper Bilayet (Foreign land -as mentioned by
S.Rushdie ) for five days. We stayed as guest of Sampath, at his home
bit outside of London. The trip would not have been so pleasant and
memorable without his help and warm hospitality.
We reached around noon at Waterloo station by Eurostar. After keeping
our luggage at cloak room we went straight to London Eye. It was a
nice start to see all the monuments of London from birds view.</description></item></channel></rss>