<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>India on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/categories/india/</link><description>Recent content in India on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:03:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/categories/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Drive Bangalore to Durg</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2021-02-22-drive-bangalore-2-durg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2021-02-22-drive-bangalore-2-durg/</guid><description>This is the longest drive we did so far and truly this was a memorable one with 1300+ KM. The planning for the trip started almost a month back. It involved looking at Google maps multiple times and talking to few friends who are roadies. We knew the road till Hyderabad would be good as we been on this highway almost 2 years back. Beyond Hyderabad was a complete unknown. Also posted my naïve query to TEAM-BHP.</description></item><item><title>Onakona Temple</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2021-02-22-onakona-chhattisgarh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2021-02-22-onakona-chhattisgarh/</guid><description>Proluge
Somewhere sometime Pamela wrote down two places to explore in Chhattisgarh which were not that well known. And one of them was Onakona. She being from there, it intrigued us with the beutiful pictures. After a week in Durg we were looking for a small break, the week was hectic and top of it the whole Diwali weekend was super busy as domestic helps were on vacation for days.</description></item><item><title>Birding at Durg</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2021-01-17-birding-at-durg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 22:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2021-01-17-birding-at-durg/</guid><description>2½ months at in-laws' place just went like that, my longest stay away from home. Just realised yesterday when discussing with my son that I did not even stay that long at my parent’s home. Yes it is a blessing in this difficult time.
As many of you know my MIL had a bad fall during lockdown and had to go through major operation. We could not arrange a travel pass at that time so when the opportunity came we decided to come to Durg/Bhilai around November 1st week and stay as much we can.</description></item><item><title>Majuli Part-I, Day-10 Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-20-majuli-day-1-april-2018/</guid><description>Somewhere on the internet once read the need for a vacation within a vacation. I know it sounds oxymoron but trust me when you are on the road for some time you need a day or two just doing nothing. Majuli was supposed to a magical place for us.
As we drove back west from Sivsagar we took the diversion to Nematighat, the boat embarkation point (ferry ghat) to go to Majuli.</description></item><item><title>Sivasagar, Day-9 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-04-sivasagar-unexplored-ahom-kingdoms-finest/</guid><description>When I was planning this long trip to Assam I always wanted to drive all the way up to Dibrugarh where I studied till class 5. Later, in the final planning stage realized it was too long of a drive. Covering Guwahati, Shillong &amp;amp; Dibrugarh was getting too much in one trip so saved it for a later day. Sivasagar remained in the itinerary for a night stay with a condition if we finish Gibbon-Hollongapar and still have time to explore the ancient capital of the Ahom kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Hoollongapar Gibbon, Day-8 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-a-morning-at-hoollongapar-gibbon-sanctuary/</guid><description>Our trip to Hollong was one of the most challenging and memorable ones. Still, after so many months, it remains clear like yesterday. We slept early knowing we have to leave early. So when the alarm went off at 4 AM the whole place was quiet and dark. We hauled all our luggage from the room to the rented car. It was a bit of a task given that we were staying backside of the property.</description></item><item><title>Gibbon Hollongapar Wildlife - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</guid><description>Hollongapar GIBBON WILDLIFE SANCTUARY Hollong - the state tree of Aaasm. The story goes back like this when the British came and saw these long trees, they asked How Long? And it became Hollong Tree.
Just like &amp;ldquo;there is a brown crow&amp;rdquo; was a way to say Darwazabandh Karo (close the door in Hindi &amp;ndash; from Satyajit Ray&amp;rsquo;s Feludaa
It is only 20 sq KM of Sanctuary. Actually, it is the oldest miscellaneous plantation having Dipterocarpus and Mesua as dominant species It was declared a Reserve by the British way back in 1881, (53years after the advent of British rule) The original forests used to extend to the foothills of the Patkai mountain range.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga Part-II, Day-7 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-second-day-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>Our hotel Wild Grass was next to Central Zone. For the second day in Kaziranga, we supposed to have Elephants Safari in the morning. Now there are 2 places where you can have elephant safari. The central zone is very popular, is difficult to get, The counter opens at 7 PM in the evening prior and people line up for long, there is a priority to foreign tourist. Our hotel arranged for the Western Zone.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</guid><description>Kaziranga is one of the bigger National Park of India. It has three prominent zones - Central, Western and Eastern.
Central Range This drive covers the central region of the park. It is an ideal introduction to the park and its ecology as the route passes through the entire spectrum of habitat types prevalent in the Kaziranga area. (though Brahmaputra view is not available, a stretch of the route goes by the tributary river Difloo) There is a possibility of sighting elephants as well as the other big animals especially the swamp buffalo and of course the rhino.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga Part-I, Day-6 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 15:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2019-02-20-day-1-in-kaziranga-april-2018/</guid><description>After a good night sleep with thunders and rain, the morning was clear of rain but the sky had overcast. Without much delay, we put all our stuff in the car and head out of the resort for Kaziranga. The best thing about the resort for us its proximity to the highway. We drive on the straight highway going east. The road was divided four lanes and there was not much traffic and was cruising around 100KM/Hr.</description></item><item><title>Sohra-Cherrapunjee, Day-5 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</guid><description>As usual, the sun went up early as we are the Eastern part of India, so after a good breakfast and settling our bills we left towards Cherrpunjee. The sky was cloudy but not raining. The 16KM drive is a long one from the resort we stayed and the road of first 8 KM closer to the resort was really bad.
We started with Thangkharang Park which looked farthest on the map.</description></item><item><title>Double Decker Bridge, Day-4 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</guid><description>Today we got up pretty late compared to other days. Had breakfast and left the hotel around 9 AM. There are some journeys in life which are hard to forget. Our trek to the much talked about Double Decker Root Bridge was one such journey for me. Staying at Cheerapunji Holiday resort has one advantage that it is hardly 7 km away from double-decker root bridge. We went 5 KM till Tyrna village where we parked our car and then 3KMs of hiking we were told by hotel people.</description></item><item><title>Driving Khasi Hills, Day-3 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</guid><description>Last night could not have proper sleep as in the middle of the night there was a sudden storm, followed by rain and finally power cut off. We got up around 6 AM and moved out of the place before 7 AM so as to avoid school traffic. We headed towards Elephant caves which come on the way to Cherrapunji, before that we saw the sign for Shillong Peak. And the sun was perfect to see the entire Shillong from the peak but as we approached near the turning and asked one passer-by whether it will be open.</description></item><item><title>Shillong, Day-2 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</guid><description>We started early morning with a drive to pick-up point of our rented car. This place was in such an area where proper roads were not there….it was full of potholes and filled with rainwater from previous rains. One thing is there Guwahati inner roads are not great and even city is not that clean&amp;hellip;full of plastics. Anyways we zoomed out from that place without much wastage of time and hit the highway.</description></item><item><title>Guwahati, Day-1 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 19:36:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-19-day-1-maa-kamakhya-here-we-come/</guid><description>Guwahati Kamakhya The flight to Guwahati was too early in the morning from Bangalore and we decided upon that on landing we will go directly to Kamakhya temple before starting our trip. Kamakhya Temple is around 14KM from the airport and our relatives stay on the other side of the city. It makes sense to start the trip in an auspicious way and we tried to strike 2 birds with one.</description></item></channel></rss>