<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Swiss on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/swiss/</link><description>Recent content in Swiss on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/swiss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goodbye – Mumbai – a quick update</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</guid><description>I
did not want to use a title like “Welcome to Bangalore” or “Here I
come to Bangaloru” on purpose as need some time before I can call this
my new home. From long time we were knowing that we have to move to
Banglore but on personal grounds I had to postpone it which was readily
accepted by my company. In recent months, I was waiting for that green
signal from my company that I have to move in any case.</description></item><item><title>Swiss-Itenary, TGV and Gizmo</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 09:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-08-04-swiss-itenary-tgv-and-gizmo/</guid><description>Another
Friday, thinking to write something for my blog ;) I think I should have
kept a track of my Friday bloging or changes I made on Friday :D. Well,
this post is not going to be about Friday but it is about our
Switzerland itinerary, experience with TGV etc.
Might have noticed there are lots of posts by Pamela in recent time –
wish she would have done before from our other trips also.</description></item><item><title>Taste of India @ Swiss</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-taste-of-india-swiss/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-31-taste-of-india-swiss/</guid><description>Although trip to Switzerland is over but yet we can’t stop writing about
it. If you are one of those few regular visitors to our blog you must be
knowing by now how much we liked our one week stay. And must be
wondering what more can be there to write about.
Yes, there are always lot to write about Switzerland when we are
comparing with Paris and when one is seeing through Indian eyes.</description></item><item><title>A must list for swiss</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 19:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</guid><description>Our trip to Switzerland has ended after all those C.B.G (châteaux,
bateaux and gateaux) trips around Europe but indeed it was a different
experience altogether. It is all about the greenery, mountain streams
rushing along, water falls, snow clad mountains, sounds of cow-bells
tickling on the alpine meadows.
I am not sure if every one is happy with their first trip to a new place
or not. But, I am always very happy and excited to go to new places.</description></item><item><title>Shhh …. Silence Please</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-19-shhh-silence-please/</guid><description>Normally, I and Santanu don&amp;rsquo;t talk to each other on bus, train, flight
or whatsoever as we are normally lost in our own world and both try to
respect each others silence. We have books, newspaper, ipod for that
time but this particular evening we happened to talk so much while
returning to Zurich from Luzern. One of the reason maybe that by now we
are kind of used to watching beautiful sceneries from train as it runs
along lakes, rivers and creaking sometimes as it passes by the running
hills unfolding before us.</description></item><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;quot; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Relaxing Day - 24th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</guid><description>It meant to be a vacation within vacation today. As we did not have to
catch any train neither any bus nor get up early for any fixed
destination. Relaxingly, we had our self-made breakfast and then headed
towards railway station for renting a cycle to bike. At first, we went
towards the city center of Interlaken where there is a big Casino and
park. From there we biked all the way towards the lake Brienz.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Hiking Mt.Rigi - 22nd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 14:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-hiking-mt-rigi-22nd-june/</guid><description>Queen of Swiss Mountains From Zurich we went to Mt. Rigi via Arth-Goldau a very short train ride.
From there we took the cogwheel train to the summit at Rigi-Kulm
(1,800m). Incredible vistas, typical Swiss farmhouses, and hundreds of
cows with bells will surprise one throughout the trip. Reward on going
to top is magnificent panorama of Alpine peaks crowding around the
convoluted contours of Lake Lucerne. While going up it was a nice
weather but slowly &amp;amp; slowly it started getting dark.</description></item><item><title>Mount Titlis - 21st June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</guid><description>Staying at Sachin’s place at Zurich was just to save our 3 night’s hotel
expense. After lot of discussion &amp;amp; surfing internet we came to final
decision that on 4th day of our trip we will go to Mount
Titlis via Luzern in order to
make best use of our Swiss flexi pass.
On boarding the train from Luzern to Engelberg we realized that it’s
more of Desi train. From train station, routes are well marked for
heading towards Mount Titlis where one can see all Mr.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Rescued - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-rescued-19th-june/</guid><description>By now, seeing the time I was
discussing about hitch hiking to the next big town which was ruled out
by Santanu as it seems not safe. Even I was suggesting him how about
getting into a car of people who does not look that young and suddenly
one car stopped and they asked if we need any lift… looking at their
face we did not take a second to decide and say “YES” in unison (which
came out as if instinct) with big smiling face.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item></channel></rss>