<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jaipur on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/jaipur/</link><description>Recent content in Jaipur on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:18:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/jaipur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chokhi Dhani- Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-19-chokhi-dhani-jaipur/</guid><description>Last day at Jaipur, today we have kept ourselves more or less free for
shopping. Had breakfast at hotel lawn for the first time. The buffet
breakfast at Hotel Madhuvan worth only when you have time to enjoy
it. We met one Indian family who were travelling from Gujrat for the
Diwali weekend to Jaipur and wanted to join us at Chokhi Dhani later in
the evening. Around 10 we left for shopping with Mr.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-02-01-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 02:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-02-01-jaipur/</guid><description>We woke around 7ish and left by the same Cab with Mr. Singh (who took us
to Shekhawati) around 8:30 from hotel. As Mr. Singh said jokingly lets
start the day in auspicious way – which mean Birla Temple was first
on the list and we reached the parking lot at dot 9. The journey took us
trough the posh residential area of Jaipur with huge bungalows which
have similarities with the Lutyens’ Delhi but a rarity in modern India.</description></item><item><title>Shekhawati - Open Air Art Gallery</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 17:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-11-19-shekhawati-open-air-art-gallery/</guid><description>29th Oct - We took SpiceJet flight to Jaipur but unfortunately could
not make it within time due to technical problems and traffic congestion
we were made to wait for 3 hrs inside flight. We reached around 22:00 to
our pre-booked Hotel Madhuban by prepaid taxi.
On reaching hotel driver says &amp;ldquo;kya bekar hotel liya hain sir&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;.ughh.
Lump in my throat as all booking was done by me. It was a laborious,
monotonous job going through website after website, jotting down details
regarding price.</description></item></channel></rss>