<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ranting on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/ranting/</link><description>Recent content in ranting on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/ranting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>W questions of Indian life</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</guid><description>In India, life of middle class is different compared to occidental
culture. There is a vast population of middle class in India and within
middle class there are three distinct sub-divisions - “lower
middleclass”, “middle middleclass” and “higher middleclass”.
Comprehending the complexities of Indian society is not that easy.
Though there are variations in socio-economic life within these three
but one thing is common between all of them - everyone is curious to
know whatz happening in others life despite of their own busy life.</description></item></channel></rss>