<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Information on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/categories/information/</link><description>Recent content in Information on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/categories/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gibbon Hollongapar Wildlife - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-gibbon-wildlife-things-to-know-before-vising/</guid><description>Hollongapar GIBBON WILDLIFE SANCTUARY Hollong - the state tree of Aaasm. The story goes back like this when the British came and saw these long trees, they asked How Long? And it became Hollong Tree.
Just like &amp;ldquo;there is a brown crow&amp;rdquo; was a way to say Darwazabandh Karo (close the door in Hindi &amp;ndash; from Satyajit Ray&amp;rsquo;s Feludaa
It is only 20 sq KM of Sanctuary. Actually, it is the oldest miscellaneous plantation having Dipterocarpus and Mesua as dominant species It was declared a Reserve by the British way back in 1881, (53years after the advent of British rule) The original forests used to extend to the foothills of the Patkai mountain range.</description></item><item><title>Kaziranga - Information to know before visiting</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2020-01-03-kaziranga-information-you-need-to-know-before-visiting/</guid><description>Kaziranga is one of the bigger National Park of India. It has three prominent zones - Central, Western and Eastern.
Central Range This drive covers the central region of the park. It is an ideal introduction to the park and its ecology as the route passes through the entire spectrum of habitat types prevalent in the Kaziranga area. (though Brahmaputra view is not available, a stretch of the route goes by the tributary river Difloo) There is a possibility of sighting elephants as well as the other big animals especially the swamp buffalo and of course the rhino.</description></item></channel></rss>