<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sky on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/sky/</link><description>Recent content in sky on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/sky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Berlin Diary- Potsdam</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-22-berlin-diary-potsdam/</guid><description>Today sun and clouds chase each other across the skies along the shores
of Berlin as it glides past. We decided to visit Potsdam city situated
on southwest of Berlin known for Sanssouci (without worries) palace;
reached there by train.
As we were short of time having our return ticket to Paris same evening
we opted for sight-seeing guided tour bus available right outside the
train station. So along with other tourists we visited new palace, old
town hall, Fortunaportal and Nikolaikirche at Alter Markt, Schloss
Cecilienhof, Potsdam’s Brandenburg gate, Dutch colony, Russian colony
Alexandrowka providing flair of a city steeped in European tradition.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 15:53:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-07-berlin-diary-ii/</guid><description>Freshened up to kick start our day and decided to go through past of
Germany. Took metro and got off at Potsdamer platz. Had coffee at
Starbucks just outside the metro exit as it was too cold.
From here we walked to Checkpoint Charlie - a crossing point between
East and West Germany during the Cold War and Berlin Wall Memorial.
The scenes blur as present dissolves into the past. Images flash through
our mind of 1989 when news flashed with headlines of demolition of
Berlin wall.</description></item><item><title>Berlin Diary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-12-06-berlin-diary/</guid><description>Today while leafing through the pages of our album found yet another
trip waiting to be jotted down before it gets erased from our memory. A
trip to Berlin where present and past are in sync once again.
We went there for 3days- 2 nights stay by train on Easter weekend when
sky was gloomy and mercury dropped to almost freezing point but didn’t
deter our enthu to explore city as much possible.</description></item><item><title>Venice at leisure</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid><description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after two
days of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s
Square. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was too
crowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out of
time and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.
Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear end
which is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description></item><item><title>Sunsets in Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 21:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-10-29-sunsets-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Sunset with blue sky of late October seems “magnifique” along with open
space of Navi Mumbai as viewed from local train (picture taken through
window)
This one I clicked last Saturday when I was stuck in middle of JJ
Flyover - the longest flyover in Mumbai (2.3 KM). It is constructed like
a snake, which makes its way through labyrinth of old buildings on
either side; basically you bypass the busy, crowded market underneath.</description></item><item><title>Le Ciel</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 03:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-23-le-ciel/</guid><description>[](/image_article/gammon-big.jpg &amp;ldquo;Blue sky with moon at dusk&amp;rdquo;)While rain still continues in South Asian countries; People from Karachi
to Dhaka are facing this year after monsoon-effects with this heavy
downpour. This monsoon is considered to be most well-known and potent.
So, I thought to put a picture with blue evening sky to cheer up ;). BTW
this is Gammon House situated at Prabhadevi next to Sidhi Vinayak
Temple.</description></item><item><title>Hue of the sky</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid><description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city of
North Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.
It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,
mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road and
rail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan and
Bangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperature
but weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description></item><item><title>A day break - Harihareshwar</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 03:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-18-a-day-break-harihareshwar/</guid><description>After moving from Paris, we had been planning to take a trip somewhere
out of Mumbai. We even bought a Travel book on India to explore more our
own motherland. But with time and circumstances our plan didn’t got
executed. At last, after longtime we took a day break on last weekend
when Santanu came to know at last moment about his holiday on Maha
Shivratri. Since it was last moment plan we could only make for one
night stay.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>A must list for swiss</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 19:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-19-a-must-list-for-swiss/</guid><description>Our trip to Switzerland has ended after all those C.B.G (châteaux,
bateaux and gateaux) trips around Europe but indeed it was a different
experience altogether. It is all about the greenery, mountain streams
rushing along, water falls, snow clad mountains, sounds of cow-bells
tickling on the alpine meadows.
I am not sure if every one is happy with their first trip to a new place
or not. But, I am always very happy and excited to go to new places.</description></item><item><title>Mount Titlis - 21st June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</guid><description>Staying at Sachin’s place at Zurich was just to save our 3 night’s hotel
expense. After lot of discussion &amp;amp; surfing internet we came to final
decision that on 4th day of our trip we will go to Mount
Titlis via Luzern in order to
make best use of our Swiss flexi pass.
On boarding the train from Luzern to Engelberg we realized that it’s
more of Desi train. From train station, routes are well marked for
heading towards Mount Titlis where one can see all Mr.</description></item><item><title>C’est fou !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-02-cest-fou/</guid><description>Football - the definition for the same may be quite simple but it
certainly does have lots of colors. It is a mutli-billion dollar
business from sporting to TV companies. For some it is as close to their
religion. People can fight or hug with a complete stranger while
ignoring his family or close one when there is a match.
As we live in Europe it is very hard to escape it.</description></item><item><title>Friday 12th May</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 15:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-12-friday-12th-may/</guid><description>Just another weekend of May in Paris. I don&amp;rsquo;t know any other time when
the weather can be so beautiful with clear sky and warm temperature.
Right now, all the horse chestnut
trees along wide
boulevards are full of white flowers. This tree is also known as
Marronier d&amp;rsquo;Inde, thanks to Francois for introducing the same.
Truly, if one cheers up and forgets all the problems round him-it is a
romantic experience in itself.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Paris in night mode</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 20:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</guid><description>I wanted to take pictures of Paris famous landmarks in the twilight with
a tripod. We started with Sacre-coeur Basilica. And the picture we got
from there was really great as we were there on the right time. The sky
color was perfect for the camera and it was just lighted.
From there we went to Moulin-Rouge; the famous cabaret of Paris then to
Assembly National the French Parliament. We crossed Seine and came to
Concord.</description></item><item><title>Stockholm (Aug 14th - 17th)</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2003 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-08-15-stockholm-aug-14th-17th/</guid><description>While browsing through web sites for summer travel deals I found there
was a very attractive deal by Ryan Air to Stockholm.We went there middle
of August when Paris was burning with summer heat. It was a great escape
to Scandinavia. Stockholm was very clean and very beautiful. Although,
the weather was not at its best as it rained for first two days.
We stayed in the centre of Stockholm (Drottninggatan) one side of this
pedestrian street with full of shops.</description></item></channel></rss>