<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cart on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/cart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cart on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/cart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhat Suar</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid>
      <description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my collegedays. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of samestate 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similarto an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”and second part “suar which means pig”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cart in city road</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 21:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-16-cart-in-city-road/</guid>
      <description>While coming to work this morning oxen (castrated male) cartcarrying sugar canes caught my attention. It is not a common site to seea bullock cart or hand pulled cart (pulled or pushed by a man) at theheart of Mumbai city next to VT Station.
They are not allowed in the main roads of the city but can only move inthe peripheral roads of the city. These kinds of slow moving objectscause most notorious traffic jam in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Few books</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid>
      <description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lotsof free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain andheat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books inlast 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘DigitalFortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story lineis similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing face of India</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. Butthere are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;tnotice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Anychanges are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place orperson after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grewup but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growingvertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>