<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>meghalaya on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/meghalaya/</link><description>Recent content in meghalaya on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:32:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/meghalaya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sohra-Cherrapunjee, Day-5 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-27-sight-seeing-sohra-cherrapunjee/</guid><description>As usual, the sun went up early as we are the Eastern part of India, so after a good breakfast and settling our bills we left towards Cherrpunjee. The sky was cloudy but not raining. The 16KM drive is a long one from the resort we stayed and the road of first 8 KM closer to the resort was really bad.
We started with Thangkharang Park which looked farthest on the map.</description></item><item><title>Double Decker Bridge, Day-4 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-tiring-yet-happy-day-double-decker-root-bridge/</guid><description>Today we got up pretty late compared to other days. Had breakfast and left the hotel around 9 AM. There are some journeys in life which are hard to forget. Our trek to the much talked about Double Decker Root Bridge was one such journey for me. Staying at Cheerapunji Holiday resort has one advantage that it is hardly 7 km away from double-decker root bridge. We went 5 KM till Tyrna village where we parked our car and then 3KMs of hiking we were told by hotel people.</description></item><item><title>Driving Khasi Hills, Day-3 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-12-17-day-3-long-day-long-drive-crazy-one-meghalaya/</guid><description>Last night could not have proper sleep as in the middle of the night there was a sudden storm, followed by rain and finally power cut off. We got up around 6 AM and moved out of the place before 7 AM so as to avoid school traffic. We headed towards Elephant caves which come on the way to Cherrapunji, before that we saw the sign for Shillong Peak. And the sun was perfect to see the entire Shillong from the peak but as we approached near the turning and asked one passer-by whether it will be open.</description></item><item><title>Shillong, Day-2 -- Assam &amp; Meghalaya Trip 2018</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-21-day-2-shillong/</guid><description>We started early morning with a drive to pick-up point of our rented car. This place was in such an area where proper roads were not there….it was full of potholes and filled with rainwater from previous rains. One thing is there Guwahati inner roads are not great and even city is not that clean&amp;hellip;full of plastics. Anyways we zoomed out from that place without much wastage of time and hit the highway.</description></item><item><title>North East 2018 planning</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-05-18-north-east-2018-planning/</guid><description>Long prologue … someone once said&amp;hellip;
Happiness is to plan a trip to somewhere new with your loved one.
One best friend from Santanu’s engineering college got transferred from Bangalore to Shillong last year. In his send-off party, everyone committed that they would like to visit that part of the country. The friend in question is serving our country and he promised to be our host there while we visit Shillong, the Scotland of East and British summer capital of North East.</description></item></channel></rss>