<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goa on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/goa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Goa on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 12:37:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/goa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Goa  ...  beach and x-mas</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 12:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2014-01-17-goa-beach-and-x-mas/</guid>
      <description>In 2013 we had very little family vacation time. I personally travelledhere and there for single nights few times due to running and otherpersonal work. The worst was to spend a week in Calcutta just afterDurga Pooja and not able to accomplish anything there. So when Decembervacation time was only few days away I booked for Goa for 4 nightswithout much thinking. Personally felt quite happy with the booking asgot a decent price for Goa just before X-mas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Adios</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 05:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</guid>
      <description>[](http://www.santm.com/gallery3/index.php/2007/goa/mixed/reflexation-nerul-river)![](../images/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios-mirror-view.jpg)
Last day, woke up very early in the morning to visit Candolim, Sinquerimbeach- Just to avoid scorching heat of sun. The shimmering sea stretchesto the horizon. Spent some time to savour the view then headed to FortAguada. Fort Agauda crowns the rocky flattened headland at the end ofthe beach. Constructed in 1612 to protect the northern shores of Mandoviestuary from Dutch and Maratha raiders. It was a reference point for thevessels coming from Europe at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid>
      <description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bikeand move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxilocally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or forshort distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellowmudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a singlepillion rider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Day 3</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 02:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-16-viva-goa-day-3/</guid>
      <description>We opted for package tour with our hotel stay, so our hotel had arrangedfor two day sightseeing South Goa with river cruise and North Goa. Weopted for South Goa to start with.
Left hotel around 9 at Indian Stretchable Time after breakfast in anon-AC bus accompanied by one local guide. The itinerary includedDona-Paula (bypass Miramar beach). Old Goa churches-Bom Jesus Basilicaand se cathedral along with two temples Mangueshi and shantadurgadedicated to Shiva and shantadurga (goddess of Peace), visit toAncestral Goa/old Portuguese house and Colva beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid>
      <description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperativeif you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedombut can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggledat least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activafor Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get goodprice). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim tovisit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva GOA - Preamble</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-preamble/</guid>
      <description>Trip to Goa was long due may-be you can say from 2001 when I gotopportunity as a teacher with my school children. But unfortunately, Icouldn’t make as I was supposed to behave as good girl. Good unmarriedIndian girls don’t go anywhere without an escort. To qualify as anescort there are lots of criteria to be checked and considered likefriend’s brother, acquaintance from neighborhood etc. is a BIG NO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>