<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Singapore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/singapore/</link><description>Recent content in Singapore on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 21:07:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thursday - Arab Street</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-19-thursday-arab-street/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 21:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-19-thursday-arab-street/</guid><description>Today was last day at Singapore. Packed everything night before so that
after breakfast we can check-out without much wasting of time.It was
holiday at Singapore as of some Muslim festival. My plan was to go to
Arab Street. This area has beautiful old shop houses that line the
streets. 
The highlight of the area is the grand Sultan Mosque, which was
crowded as people were coming out after prayers.</description></item><item><title>Wedneday- Visit to China town</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-wedneday-visit-to-china-town/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 17:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-wedneday-visit-to-china-town/</guid><description>It was the day to visit china town and particularly Buddha tooth
relic temple. The day was very bright with little could in the sky.
This is the view from our hotel room looking central Singapore Business
District.
After a good breakfast headed out of hotel. Got down by MRT at China
town &amp;amp; took exit to Pagoda street. One can&amp;rsquo;t miss the colorful row of
shop-houses along that street, with baby blue and yellow flowers painted
all over.</description></item><item><title>Hectic Tuesday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-hectic-tuesday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 14:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-04-03-hectic-tuesday/</guid><description>We woke up bit early; had heavy breakfast as usual. For today I have
already decided to go to Botanical garden in first half of the day.
So took a cab from hotel and I figured it was very nearby. This
botanical garden is must if you want to see the greenery and variety of
plants and flowers they have. Excellent maintenance, people come here
for jogging, picnic and touristy purpose.</description></item><item><title>Sleepy Monday</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 11:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-23-sleepy-monday/</guid><description>Monday morning mother-son woke up pretty late. Santanu already left for
office while we were in sleep. Around noon we went out of hotel to
nearby mall. Today I was not much interested in exploring rather looking
for kids activities. Spent almost half day at Toys R Us play area in
Paragon mall where Aarush enjoyed to fullest. He did not want to
give-up the car and was seating there for hours.</description></item><item><title>Jurong bird park</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-22-jurong-bird-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 18:47:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-02-22-jurong-bird-park/</guid><description>After a full day @ Santosa on Sunday we woke up pretty late. We decided
to go for Jurong bird park and offbeat track -Kong Meng San Phor
Kark See Monastery, is the largest monastery in Singapore.
We had breakfast at ChatterBox as the normal breakfast side was packed.
The menu was quite different from the normal side as we had lots of
traditional dishes to choose from. As usual Pamela had lots of dim-sum
and I preferred the usual cereal and fruits.</description></item><item><title>Day-3 Sentosa visit</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-11-day-3-sentosa-visit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2010-01-11-day-3-sentosa-visit/</guid><description>Saturday, we planned for Sentosa Island – Sentosa is the top tourist
attraction if you ask any Singaporean tourist information or locals.
Sentosa has it all – beach, corporate team building activities,
aquarium, great food and entertainment and soon there will be Casio and
entertainment park with roller coaster rides. We planned for complete
day-trip; as usual after heavy breakfast we went by metro to Harbour
Front MRT station. From there took Sentosa Express (Monorail train)
from Vivocity mall’s top floor.</description></item><item><title>Friday - Black Peper Crab</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 04:19:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-27-friday-black-peper-crab/</guid><description>On Friday we woke up early; had
breakfast- an elaborate one. Me and Aarush after shower around 11am left
our hotel room. Today again we walked on other side of Orchard
Streettill Dhoby Ghat Station. Now
a days; I too feel sick like my hubby when too much time spent at malls
… am I growing old ? :D It was good to be in mall when it is raining.</description></item><item><title>First day @ Singapore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-21-first-day-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 05:18:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-12-21-first-day-singapore/</guid><description>Viewing Singapore through a lens of mother of 22 months old baby was not
fun all the time but enjoyed our stay there for 9 days. Actually this
journey is because of Santanu who went almost every year after returning
to India. Each time after his official trip he use to complain about his
loneliness and etc. So this time we made sure to accompany him. But what
a luck! he was damn busy in his office.</description></item><item><title>Cost cutting Travel and more</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 07:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2009-08-06-cost-cutting-travel-and-more/</guid><description>My last week trip to Singapore was a hectic one. Too many meetings and
meetings at work; best part is now a new Starbucks at Science Park
Drive is opened close to work; was very lucky where every other day got
pampered by my host with a coffee.
The flight from Bangalore was a nightmare I never experienced such
horrible service from any airline in my travel history. For Airlines
each seats are perishable commodities, which is lost as soon as the
flight takes off and it is a dream come true for Airline Company when
they have one.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Tomato Soup</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 20:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-19-fresh-tomato-soup/</guid><description>Till far only soup ever tried to make was carrot soup in Paris that too
in bleak winter. Big thanks to my French Teacher for sharing the
recipe en Français. Recently, went to local vegetable market; seeing
tomato got so tempted that without thinking bought two kilos. Then I
brainstormed a bit to think and idea of soup came as an escape. Here is
my 2 cents recipe. If craving for something sweet and sour at the
same time just have a bowl of creamy tomato soup to satisfy your desire
as an appetizer.</description></item><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>Exploring…bits n bites II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 16:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-14-exploring-bits-n-bites-ii/</guid><description>Continuing from my last post I like to share a great experience I had.
It was a sudden plan and I was tagged along with my instructor who
in-turn was invited by a local Singaporean colleague after work for
dinner. It was buffet for a fixed price at Marina Bay Shopping Mall.
The crowd was very young far-eastern or North-Asians. Sorry guys, I
could not figure out who is Chinese, Japanese, Koreans or just
Singaporeans…as they all looked alike and age-wise they looked like high
school or college students to me.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Arrived Singapore</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-23-arrived-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 20:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-23-arrived-singapore/</guid><description>Reached Singapore on a business trip for about 26 days. Will try to
post more often as I explore Singapore from my angle.</description></item><item><title>Bombay International Airport</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-22-bombay-international-airport/</guid><description>Bombay International Airport is always under construction as far as
my International travels are concerned. Good news is that it is getting
better and the completion date is getting closer. Here, are the pictures
for the same as I waited for my flight to Singapore.Though the pictures
looks quite world class construction work; but on the ground it may be
not …quality wise.</description></item></channel></rss>