<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bikes on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/bikes/</link><description>Recent content in bikes on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/bikes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Baking Bread</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 16:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-31-baking-bread/</guid><description>For quite a long was thinking to prepare bread at home which I would
have never thought of in my wildest dream if I was in India. But staying
at Paris it just clicked why not to try once on experimental basis as it
is there staple food. It’s like an icon of France. This is why French
people visit the local &amp;ldquo;Boulangerie&amp;rdquo; (hot bread shop) at least once
a day and this shop is there at least at every street corner.</description></item><item><title>Relaxing Day - 24th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-relaxing-day-24th-june/</guid><description>It meant to be a vacation within vacation today. As we did not have to
catch any train neither any bus nor get up early for any fixed
destination. Relaxingly, we had our self-made breakfast and then headed
towards railway station for renting a cycle to bike. At first, we went
towards the city center of Interlaken where there is a big Casino and
park. From there we biked all the way towards the lake Brienz.</description></item></channel></rss>