<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>siliguri on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/siliguri/</link>
    <description>Recent content in siliguri on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 03:09:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/siliguri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurseong</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 03:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2013-10-25-kurseong/</guid>
      <description>Thefirst-daywegot little suspicious with the transport rates being quoted by KanchanView Hotel Manager. We reportedthat back to Calcutta the tour operator Mr. D. Ghosh. But once you areaway from home and you have limited option to negotiate a bargain. TheHotel person by now have charged us 2500 for the first day covering onlyTagore Smritivan , monastery and forest bungalow. For the second day wepaid 2500 to cover 5/6 places but the distance was more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Sikkim - Hee Bermiok</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2013-09-19-west-sikkim-hee-bermiok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2013-09-19-west-sikkim-hee-bermiok/</guid>
      <description>We initially planned to visit Bhutan during summer vacation of ’13.Somehow during the planning phase we found it was overshooting ourbudget. And moreover, was advised against it during late April &amp;amp; EarlyMay as there is a high chances of rain during that time. So we had noplan and no places to visit while we are going to be in Siliguri for10/12 days.
We called one travel agent in Calcutta from train and told him about ourrequirement and he said he would be able to put an itinerary of 6 nights( 2nights Sikkim, 2 Kursuang and 2 in Darjeeling).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet potato dessert</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-09-11-sweet-potato-dessert/</guid>
      <description>Sweet potato dessert (Ranga Alur Puli) is an age old Bengali dessert - asweet lover&amp;rsquo;s delight for sure. Its crispy outer layer mesmerizesgastronomic senses. As for its availability, it is more of atraditional sweet, prepared in households. These days some sweet shopsare starting to include this in their repertoire to cater to thetime-constrained generation.
My hubby being born with a sweet tooth, do enjoy sweet of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hue of the sky</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 03:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-06-20-hue-of-the-sky/</guid>
      <description>Siliguri is gateway to the North East of India. It is commercial city ofNorth Bengal where tea, timber and transport are the main business.It is a base point to head towards Darjeeling, Sikkim, kalimpong,mirik etc. Besides, it is also the transit point for air, road andrail traffic to the neighboring countries of Nepal, Bhutan andBangladesh.
Situated at foot of Eastern Himalayas it has very pleasant temperaturebut weather is very unpredictable as it gets shower any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China rose</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 01:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-05-16-china-rose/</guid>
      <description>Flowers are the sweetest things God ever made and forgot to put a soulinto. - Henry Ward Beecher.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know really why I love to picture flowers. Wherever visit ifthey fascinate me, try to make them my subject.
My dad loves garden; for him it is most sociable of hobbies.Truly said,the very nature of one&amp;rsquo;s field of activities demands an audience. No onewants flowers to blush unseen or waste their sweetness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid>
      <description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may notbe the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the mostimportant city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographicallocation. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway toseven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just startedmy career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation on the horizon</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid>
      <description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard oftravelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May beit is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visitsome country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not atall interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Pariscold all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shan &amp; Pam-The Perfect Wedding</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2002 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</guid>
      <description>It was the 27thApril 02 &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:green;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;evening,
Every thing was geared up for the Mumbai &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;meeting,
Our “Rosy” flower, made “&amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#ff9900;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;Shan” like a bee &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993300;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;humming,
Not showing outside, Pam thought it was her prince &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993366;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;charming,
Santanu was convinced it was the end of his &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:fuchsia;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;findings,
Gandhiji was nervously smiling,
Shan’s mother in law thought it was perfectly &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;matching,
Pam’s mother and father in law were unable to hide the &amp;lt;span</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2002-11-08-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2002 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2002-11-08-wedding/</guid>
      <description>It all started around very early 2002. After few correspondences betweenour parents I was asked to come to India in April. After doing sometravelling around, on very last day I met Pamela in-person at Bombay on27th April. It did not took much time for deciding about the biggeststep of our life.After phone calls and emails for next six months, wegot married on 8th November at Calcutta.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>