<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>calcutta on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/calcutta/</link><description>Recent content in calcutta on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/calcutta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Back from trip</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 15:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-20-back-from-trip/</guid><description>Well, I am back to Bombay from my official visit after four weeks stay
in Singapore. There are lots of pictures from the trip, but as I did not
visit any vista-points or sight-seeing points as tourist rather which
ever crossed my path got snapped. Will post them soon. Note: this
picture is not from Mumbai Airport but from Kolkata(Calcutta)</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Vacation on the horizon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid><description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)
when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard of
travelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May be
it is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visit
some country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not at
all interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Paris
cold all the time.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2002 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</guid><description>It all started around very early 2002. After few correspondences between
our parents I was asked to come to India in April. After doing some
travelling around, on very last day I met Pamela in-person at Bombay on
27th April. It did not took much time for deciding about the biggest
step of our life.After phone calls and emails for next six months, we
got married on 8th November at Calcutta.</description></item></channel></rss>