<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Diary on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/my-diary/</link><description>Recent content in My Diary on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 18:51:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/my-diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mysore Half Marathon 2013</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 18:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-09-30-mysore-half-marathon-2013/</guid><description>This was Mysore Celebration Run 2013 ; well there was BIG celebration at
Pacemakers running group. Coach was brand ambassador of the run, we had
a promo run in Bangalore for the same. Few runners from group also got
featured in Life is Calling&amp;rsquo;s web
site.
Initially I was against this run as I rescheduled my Mother&amp;rsquo;s return
flight from Bangalore to Siliguri on the same Sunday :(. But big thanks
to Maa and Pamela as they supported to run me this event.</description></item><item><title>Blessed</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-28-blessed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 03:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-28-blessed/</guid><description>Blessing is a simple word, but yesterday night (Monday) just before
sleeping I was thinking about the same again and again. Wished for a
gadget to record my thought as I was too tired to use any keyboard or
voice recorder. At times we wonder and sometime make fun of those award
ceremonies where people on the stage keep on thanking people around him
or her and sometimes even their dogs.</description></item><item><title>Pipeline Road Run</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-04-pipeline-road-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 23:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-08-04-pipeline-road-run/</guid><description>There was a discussion in the running group to practice hill-run before
upcoming Hyderabad run which I am trying to be a regular member.
Normally the &amp;ldquo;numero uno&amp;rdquo; destination for hill training around Bangalore
is Nandi Hill ; which is 60KM north of the city. Have already run Nandi
hills few times and yes Nandi is grueling specially the last 3 KM. Nandi
run is 15KM in total where you go 7.</description></item><item><title>Chennai DRHM</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-07-12-chennai-drhm/</guid><description>Chennai DRHM ( Dream Runners Half
Marathon) was on
1st Sunday of July i.e. 7thJuly 2013. It was the first run
out of Bangalore for me. Last time I registered for Mumbai Standard
Chartered was in 2008 and was gifted with Aarush just few days before
the race :D Well Aarush is the reason why I can not run on weekdays
morning but he is the catalyst who introduced me to The Pacemakers
running group of Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>BookShelf</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-06-04-bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 02:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-06-04-bookshelf/</guid><description>This was complete DYI project. Theses books are not going to be touched
soon.</description></item><item><title>Opinion - does it really matter ?</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-04-09-opinion-does-it-really-matter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 20:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-04-09-opinion-does-it-really-matter/</guid><description>Opinion – a simple word everyone has one. Thanks to new social media
which makes it so easy to spread it. They express it say it is personal
(me included). Does it really personal once expressed ? I am not a
social science expert but there are some opinions heard, read in recent
time wondered what to do with them. Tried argue with few at the
beginning but at the end ignored them all.</description></item><item><title>A small nano but long wait</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-09-23-a-small-nano-but-long-wait/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 18:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-09-23-a-small-nano-but-long-wait/</guid><description>Beginning of this year sold our Indica and bought Swift-Dzire(ZDI) which
we found very practical and perfect for our Indian need. And we did not
thought of booking any new car in recent time. Suddenly things got
changed when Pamela started a new job in May. We were quite happy with
single car and personally opted for BIAS (Bangalore International
Airport - Volvo) as I commute from Hebbal to Old Airport read every day
around 20KM one way.</description></item><item><title>A quick post</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 22:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-07-14-a-quick-post/</guid><description>Reading old newspaper clipping fascinate me; an article which earns a
good amount space on that day and most likely people read and forgot.
and here I am reading it after days with a fresh eye. And most times it
turns out to be a great story to read with eagerness.
This one was bit special which caught my eyes today was &amp;ldquo;Chaturanan
Mishra
passed away&amp;rdquo;; now there are few things which made me to write this quick
post.</description></item><item><title>Father Day - Thank you Aarush</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 19:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-06-28-father-day-thank-you-aarush/</guid><description>During month of May there were some sudden turn of events happened that
changed the course of my life as father. Well I am quite positive on
this sudden turn of event that this happened for good. Pamela suddenly
jackpot a teaching Job with one of the premier institute of Bangalore.
And they asked her to join immediately. The first week was in training
in Kormangala was OK OK as Aarush had his summer camp in his old
school.</description></item><item><title>Another Move</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-11-15-another-move/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 20:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-11-15-another-move/</guid><description>A few more week we will move from our current address; this time within
Bangalore. So compared to last moves it is going to be a very small
one. In 2003, we crossed Atlantic (California to Paris), in 2006 we
crossed Indian ocean (Paris to Mumbai) and in 2008 we moved within India
(Mumbai to Bangalore). Now this is just 20 Km move within Bangalore
city.
The painters from Asian Paint Home Solutions are doing the paint job and
they are supposed to finish by 25th November.</description></item><item><title>Coffee – makes me happy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 17:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-07-12-coffee-makes-me-happy/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is not new and there are few
posts on the same subject
in past. The culture of having a good time with a cup of coffee is
catching up in India. Café Coffee Day aka CCD is expanding its
footprints in rapid speed from past few years; people close to the
business speculate they are just spending money and expanding in hope
for a bought over by some FDI like Starbucks if the later enter
Indian market.</description></item><item><title>IKEA - made in India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2010-04-23-ikea-made-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 01:44:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2010-04-23-ikea-made-in-india/</guid><description>It is no secret that I am a big fan
of IKEA&amp;rsquo;s clean cut design. And now every time I go outside of India try to pick something from there. Wished we got the whole modular
kitchen, beds, chest of drawers, leather sofa while moving back from
Paris. This time I visited IKEA store was next to Newark Airport(EWR,
NJ) and picked some small stuff for Aarush. When a neighbour looked at
the &amp;ldquo;Made in India&amp;rdquo; level asked from which store we picked up?</description></item><item><title>Another year passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 14:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-26-another-year-passed-by/</guid><description>Another year passed and more grey hairs to take care now. Well this time
I cut the cake at office with my team. Cake came off course from Cake
Walk. Well I never had any no birthday resolution there was no
difference this year as well. Big thanks to those who wished me on time
or belated. For others this post is few weeks old in itself.</description></item><item><title>Madras Filter Coffee</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 18:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-10-15-madras-filter-coffee/</guid><description>My addiction to coffee is old an old one. My morning does not start
without coffee on weekdays. I am not quite human still have my
morning coffee will probably describe it best. In India coffee is very
different from West. I came to know recently that Indian Coffee Board
is head quartered in Bangalore. The main coffee producing region of
India(hills of Coorg, Niligiris and Wayanad&amp;gt;) are not very far off
Bangalore.</description></item><item><title>Happy Durga Puja</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-09-22-happy-durga-puja/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 06:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-09-22-happy-durga-puja/</guid><description>Hello everyone, happy festivity it is time of celebration in India
specially north and east where it is NavaRatri in North and Durga Puja
in East. Pamela and Arush left on Sunday for Durg. It will be almost
after 8 years Pamela will be at her mother house to celebrate Durga
Puja. For Bengali&amp;rsquo;s it is the most special occasion in the whole
calender. According to mythological believe Goddess Durga is a daughter
of every Bengali and she visit her parents with her four children.</description></item><item><title>Depuis Longtemps</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-21-depuis-longtemps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-21-depuis-longtemps/</guid><description>In recent time, there is no post in our blog. Few days back, newspaper
mentioned popular blogs are drying as &amp;ldquo;twitter or facebook&amp;rdquo; becomes
popular ways to communicate with readers. Many bloggers started to
update about themselves in social-site or micro-blogging using SMS and
original blog surffers. For us nothing as such happened; we just got
super busy from busy.
We were very happy that my younger brother and his wife took the pain to
come over to Bangalore (10-13thJuly).</description></item><item><title>Playing football</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-04-playing-football/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 06:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-07-04-playing-football/</guid><description>Aarush having nice time in green patch of IIM Bangalore Campus. Color of
ball and his T-shirt coincidently matched and isn&amp;rsquo;t that look nice on
green background? I took Pamela and Aarush to show them the southern
part of Bangalore which I am visiting quite often this year on academic
purpose. A great place to escape from routine life and bring back
memories of &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Purani Jeans Aur Guitar&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; days.</description></item><item><title>IPL 2.0</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-23-ipl-2-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 23:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-03-23-ipl-2-0/</guid><description>IPL – Indian Premier League goes out of India. You do not need to be a
cricket fan to follow this news as it is every where. I am literally out
raged with this news can you think suddenly British (Barclay)
premiership moves to Spain as cold winter stormed as swapped across
Britain. Mr.Lalit Modi is a big favorite be it media or those franchisee
owners but certainly things will be different after this summer.</description></item><item><title>My baby shower</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 15:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-05-my-baby-shower/</guid><description>My
baby shower was done in the Bengali traditional way which is called as
Saadh in Bengali. It is meant mostly to pamper the first-time mother
to be and cheer her up as she accumulates courage to face the most
testing time in her life which will soon change her life in and out.
Normally, held in the seventh or ninth month of pregnancy on a
specified day when mother-in-law will organize this ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Journey to Motherhood</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-04-journey-to-motherhood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 15:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-04-journey-to-motherhood/</guid><description>Remembering my journey to motherhood as Aarush turns one year old. After
4 years of marriage and lot of traveling around Europe Santanu decided
to move back to India to find a better professional career. Life as
couple was not full of hip and happening but we were happy and carefree
about the same. I use to scorn at people whenever brought up kids in
topic; balked at elders. After getting back to India this pressure was
getting on me.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 17:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-03-happy-new-year/</guid><description>**Happy New Year everyone!!!**. Wish
you all the best for next 361 days; already late by two days to post the
first one of &amp;lsquo;09.Only one resolution we take &amp;ndash; that is to update our blog often and
complete the list of posts we are supposed to for long time; there are
some of travelogue too to complete. Keep coming back and put your
comments that really makes us going.</description></item><item><title>2008 - mixed bag</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 17:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-01-01-2008-mixed-bag/</guid><description>Thinking of 2008&amp;hellip; it was an eventful year. We started by adding a new
member to our family after going through lot of apprehension. Now our
new world started to revolve around baby with umpteen number of diaper
changes and sleepless nights, his cries, bowel movement and what
not&amp;hellip;..
Pamela&amp;rsquo;s parents were at Mumbai to help us in our happily tough times.
Even before completing two months Aarush left Mumbai for Pamela&amp;rsquo;s
hometown.</description></item><item><title>Wear the red Ribbon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-01-wear-the-red-ribbon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 23:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-12-01-wear-the-red-ribbon/</guid><description>December 1st 2008- World AIDS Day - today, AIDS is one of the main
causes of mortality on the planet. 33 million people are HIV-positive in
the world, but 90 % of them ignore it. Given the numbers, there is a
definite need to increase the awareness levels about the disastrous
effects of this incurable disease.
I am sure there are plenty online about the same which can be accessed
quickly but the main problem remains in uneducated rural areas where it
is not even mentioned forget about a healthy discussion.</description></item><item><title>Change</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-11-21-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 19:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-11-21-change/</guid><description>In last 20 months “change” was one of most used word thanks to new
President elect Obama. I admire the way he delivers speeches and uses
words. Most reporters must be missing those malapropian phrases used in
last 8 years.
I took this picture in February at Mumbai Airport; personally I too was
thinking about the change and transition I was going trough at work and
home at that time.</description></item><item><title>Long Time no see ...</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-10-29-long-time-no-see/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 07:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-10-29-long-time-no-see/</guid><description>Well we are still connected to internet just not having enough time to
spare to post. There are few posts which are long overdue. Only time we
can type in peace when Aarush is sleeping but by that time we are so
tired that we retire quickly. Do not worry will post more often as we
try to get back into a more strict routine. BTW I just registered myself
in Facebook after lots of deliberation.</description></item><item><title>Wish Pamela</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-09-17-wish-pamela/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 23:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-09-17-wish-pamela/</guid><description>If you are reading this post on 17th September please call up, e-mail if
you have not done so yet.
Well why I am writing this post &amp;ndash; I am stuck in a business trip and
missing her and Aarush for last 3 weeks. Sometime I wish I just could
dump my current job and spend some quality time with Family. But with
Financial commitment I don’t think I can do that soon :(.</description></item><item><title>Rejuvenating old I-Pod</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-08-07-rejuvenating-old-i-pod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 21:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-08-07-rejuvenating-old-i-pod/</guid><description>Our old faithful I-pod’s
battery died last year; nothing to complain about the same. We have used
it enough and did not have any complain. Only thing that happened is the
battery started to loose charge more often and at the end it stopped
charging altogether. Just after I got this I-Pod, Apple had to settle a
lawsuit for low
quality batteries. That way I must say I am happy to survive for 3 years
with one battery.</description></item><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Bhat Suar</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 07:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-23-bhat-suar/</guid><description>Every time I visit my in-laws and see one of these “Bhat Suar”
(three-wheeler cart) on the road it brings back memories of my college
days. Durg(in-law’s place) and Bhopal(college day) were part of same
state 6 years back; although politically divided they are very similar
to an outsider like me on social and geographical terms.
First part of the name comes from the sound they make “Bhat-Bhat”
and second part “suar which means pig”.</description></item><item><title>Hebbal Lake</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 21:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-24-hebbal-lake/</guid><description>Last weekend I was in Bangalore and was checking progress on
construction site. Well will this be a view if we move there; but as at
work things are not yet crystal clear for the upcoming move. It is a
nice view to have from kitchen they say a happy person always makes a
happy meal. With new Bangalore airport going to be operational in next
month this side of town is going to see lots of traffic and that is
going to add more worries for already worried Bangaloreans.</description></item><item><title>An announcement</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 01:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-01-29-an-announcement/</guid><description>This announcement was long due on our blog. Though this breaking news
was shared on d-day instantly with friends and families from Hospital
via SMS and emails. I specifically carried my camera, laptop and
wireless data card for the same.
I created two announcement cards one in pink and other in blue with two
names (for girl and boy) and kept them ready. We never disclosed this
big-news in last few months in our blog in-fact it was kept secret to
many except close family members and few friends.</description></item><item><title>Calamity of Mid life &amp; middle class</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 16:38:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-10-17-calamity-of-mid-life-middle-class/</guid><description>It is impossible not to eavesdrop when people are having a loud
conversation on phone in Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s life line - local train.
Unlike other days today morning, was special one which is worth
describing.
A guy gets in; stands next to me and elbows me to make his room and
starts chatting over mobile (so how it goes&amp;hellip;.).
“Sorry yaar (friend) had to switch off the mobile as train was coming
in; you know how much rush is there nowadays.</description></item><item><title>36th week as passed by</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 15:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-07-36th-week-as-passed-by/</guid><description>Looking at Ballard Pier at south Bombay from my office window. Bombay
port is one of the busiest port in India if not the most. I am sure
looking at the picture you can figure out it is a old picture as the
weather is still gloomy with dark clouds here. It is one of the very
first pictures from our Canon G7 camera. I really like the way light and
shadow on the tree brunch, it is quite well center balanced shoot to me.</description></item><item><title>W questions of Indian life</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 01:03:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-05-02-w-questions-of-indian-life/</guid><description>In India, life of middle class is different compared to occidental
culture. There is a vast population of middle class in India and within
middle class there are three distinct sub-divisions - “lower
middleclass”, “middle middleclass” and “higher middleclass”.
Comprehending the complexities of Indian society is not that easy.
Though there are variations in socio-economic life within these three
but one thing is common between all of them - everyone is curious to
know whatz happening in others life despite of their own busy life.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>A dark post</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 02:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</guid><description>Well this post is a dark one-
Aaj fir dil hai kuchh udaas udaasjaane kyun ek mayusi si chhayi haiaaj
fir palkon pe pani haibheer mein hoon fir kyun ye tanhai hai jaane kyun
bebas aur beychain hai dil mera&amp;hellip;.
In simple words, things around me are going crazy&amp;hellip;. restless mind as
there are loved ones who are dealing with the PROBLEM on the ground with
hard reality; facing it more harsh then me who is being updated with
phone calls only.</description></item><item><title>Welcoming 2007</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-31-welcoming-2007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2006 05:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-31-welcoming-2007/</guid><description>Well Saddam Hussein is dead so what is next for 2007? May be there will
be very few asking this questions as they start to celebrate New Year
tomorrow. I never ever thought that I will comment upon politics on our
blog. But I think I break that rule today.
Everyone taking stock of year that is almost over. I personally do not
like the week “from Christmas to New Year”, I do not have a solid reason
for the same.</description></item><item><title>Linen anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-04-linen-anniversary/</guid><description>It is four years that we got married :D and according to the naming
convention it is Linen
Anniversary we have still
have a long way to go before it will be any precious or strong material.
This day is special in another way as it is birthday of Prateek
(maternal cousin of mine). Now we stay above floor from Prateek. After
our wedding this is the first time that we three are together.</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-16-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-16-back-to-work/</guid><description>Well after one and half months of vacation I am back to work today.
Surprisingly, I will be still using my old e-mail (work) well it does
not mean that I am checking my work mails as I write this post. It will
take sometime for the IT guys before they transfer me electronically
from Europe to Asia. I thought it might be a good time to write
something for the blog.</description></item><item><title>Aids Awareness - Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2006 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-10-aids-awareness-paris/</guid><description>Can any one guess what this publicity is about? Well, this is 2006 anti
Aids campaign by city hall of Paris (Paris protège l&amp;rsquo;amour means
Paris protects love)
In the photo what we see is sunset on some historical building with moon
at backdrop, but when you take a close look moon is&amp;hellip; a condom. It aims
at promoting the use of condoms among the population i.e., to have safe
sex.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>I am sorry when I am wrong but I am furious when I am right</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-15-i-am-sorry-when-i-am-wrong-but-i-am-furious-when-i-am-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2006 11:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-15-i-am-sorry-when-i-am-wrong-but-i-am-furious-when-i-am-right/</guid><description>Well the title say it all</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 13:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-04-25-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;India is changing&amp;rdquo; I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn&amp;rsquo;t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Changing face of India</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-03-15-changing-face-of-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-03-15-changing-face-of-india/</guid><description>“India is changing” I am sure this is not a new topic to talk about. But
there are few things which got changed in India which my RADAR didn’t
notice before. I am not going to debate on their pros and cons. Any
changes are more noticeable when we encounter the same old place or
person after a break. Like you meet up an old friend with whom you grew
up but that time probably you did not noticed he or she was growing
vertically and your mid- aged relatives were growing horizontally.</description></item><item><title>Tujh bin….</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-03-06-tujh-bin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 16:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-03-06-tujh-bin/</guid><description>Oof !!!! getting mad you know.Its been a while Santanu is trying his
best to make it work but alas no response,no sound&amp;hellip; nothing.Tried his
best as much as he could, took it on his lap, dismantle
everything&amp;hellip;like one of those computer geeks trying to fix that damn
thing but god&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;everything gone in vain.The connections &amp;amp; all
those seems to be fine except that fan which was rotating in such a
speed making hell lot of noise.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Tibx Shoe Laces</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-10-20-tibx-shoe-laces/</guid><description>Yes these are my dirty shoes. Not very sure about the origin of those
shoe laces, I got them when my old office was getting closed. Missing
the TIBX bus and shares I got those laces :( (People got nice race cars
and big houses in Bay Area a dream come true in this materialistic world
and what I got for boarding the train late. Well I have another pair of
these laces….</description></item><item><title>New look to web site</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2005 03:49:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-09-16-new-look-to-web-site/</guid><description>Migrated to Wordpress along with
Gallery2, the choice for the same was not
easy. As for a long time Mambo and custom
home grown Photo Album was doing the job fine. In fact the template I
used for the same was appreciated by friends. But as days passed and
numbers of pictures are growing it was getting difficult to manage the
same with custom gallery. But the idea to grab Wordpress and dropping
Mambo is a personal one.</description></item><item><title>Lost Pictures Recovered</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 18:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-31-lost-pictures-recovered/</guid><description>After discovering that one of the SmartMedia Card from my Camera not
working at Seville we were really very heart broken and anxious. It had
pictures from our first three days of our trip. And in those first three
days we traveled from Madrid to Granada. We had captured lots of evening
pictures in Madrid and sunset view of Alhambra at Granada.
But we kept our nerve cool and continued with other media cards and
tried our best not to remember about the same.</description></item><item><title>Bonjour</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-17-bonjour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-17-bonjour/</guid><description>After a long time I changed the theme of my web site; hope the color
combination looks good. The two templates are &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;zen&amp;rsquo;.
There are now more than 1300 pictures to checkout in the Photo Album
section. Most of them come from last 3 years as that is how old my
digital camera is. And a big section comes from Europe. After moving to
Paris, we used this opportunity to visit maximum countries possible
which are part of Schengen visa.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2004 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-12-18-happy-holidays/</guid><description>Happy Holidays!!! Well year 2004 is almost over; wish you all the best for the year 2005
and next. This year we did not traveled like last year. But we did
traveled to Italy and Greece for one week each, other than some of few
short trips. You will find them in pictures for 2004.
In the month of November we framed few pictures and cross-stitch work of
Pamela. Here are the pictures of the same.</description></item><item><title>Got an IPOD</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2004 21:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-03-08-got-an-ipod/</guid><description>Requested my brother to send me one I-pod from USA with Hitesh as he was
coming to Paris on a business trip. It was very nice to catch up with
Hitesh, Neetu and Simran after moving out of CA. We met them at their
hotel in Latin quarter and had dinner with them. It was almost 2 in the
morning when we returned home in the cold night of February.</description></item><item><title>Back from vacation</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 04:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</guid><description>Back to Paris after a nice and quick vacation of 4 weeks from India. The
days passed by very quickly between meals and sleep. Our vacation got
split between my parents and in-law&amp;rsquo;s house. But it was great to spent
time with family. Will post some new pictures and others later. Paris is
very beautifully decorated for holidays, it is a great sight to see all
those big trees along the road being lighted up, as they don&amp;rsquo;t have any
leaf now.</description></item><item><title>Paper Anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid><description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventful
for both of us. On this day we went to Ramkrishna
Mission.The
hour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fall
color.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Pooja
and Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went to
Salon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description></item><item><title>Shan &amp; Pam-The Perfect Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2002 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2002-12-10-shan-pam-the-perfect-wedding/</guid><description>It was the 27thApril 02 &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:green;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;evening,
Every thing was geared up for the Mumbai &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;meeting,
Our “Rosy” flower, made “&amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#ff9900;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;Shan” like a bee &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993300;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;humming,
Not showing outside, Pam thought it was her prince &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:#993366;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;charming,
Santanu was convinced it was the end of his &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:fuchsia;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;findings,
Gandhiji was nervously smiling,
Shan’s mother in law thought it was perfectly &amp;lt;span
style=&amp;quot;color:blue;&amp;ldquo;&amp;gt;matching,
Pam’s mother and father in law were unable to hide the &amp;lt;span</description></item><item><title>Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2002 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</guid><description>It all started around very early 2002. After few correspondences between
our parents I was asked to come to India in April. After doing some
travelling around, on very last day I met Pamela in-person at Bombay on
27th April. It did not took much time for deciding about the biggest
step of our life.After phone calls and emails for next six months, we
got married on 8th November at Calcutta.</description></item></channel></rss>