<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spain on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/spain/</link><description>Recent content in Spain on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nouvelle in market</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid><description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metro
suburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weight
Wal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance is
now trying to negotiate with france based global retail major
Carrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores are
small and right around the corner competing with family owned generation
old style grocery store.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Back to Work</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 18:13:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-06-02-back-to-work/</guid><description>When I was on my vacation last week in Spain and Portugal, was thinking
about to write down all that we had experienced there - the places we
visted and food we tasted and others. But back to work it is such a
Dilbert place that I can not explain with my logic.
Also I need to find a cheap solution to restore pictures from Smart
Media. It looks like there is a well suited option commercial for 40
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Train Lisbon to Madrid</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-29-hotel-train-lisbon-to-madrid/</guid><description>We
were at the very last phase of our vacation. We took train back to
Madrid tonight as from there we had our flight back to Paris.
We booked the train ticket long back; I went in-person to get the same
from Spanish Railway ticket office based in Paris. The office is kind of
hidden by all the stores near to Boulevard Haussmann; ever busy shopping
place.
Being Indian it was a really something new although we had experienced
few other different night trains in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Cordoba – Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid><description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought of
Cordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggested
visiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reach
the train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. The
fair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costs
almost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 18:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-24-seville-spain/</guid><description>I
should have started jotting down all my memories from this beautiful
city immediately after my return to Paris. But back to work and daily
routine&amp;hellip;. lots of finer moments are fading off.
We took a morning bus from Granada to Seville; we reached Seville around
11AM. The bus ride was around 2 hours and 45 minutes. From that
IntercityBus stop to our hotel (again Novotel) we took again local
public bus.</description></item><item><title>Alhambra - Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-23-alhambra-granada-spain/</guid><description>We did not book our tickets for Alhambra before coming to Granada. There
can be 8,000 visitors inside Alhambra in a given day. Out of those 8,000
around 6,500 are sold over internet &amp;amp; phone. So for us, it meant getting
up early and queuing up in the morning. As it was Monday and not peak of
tourist season&amp;hellip; we were lucky.
Alhambra has main 4 sites to visit.
The main attraction is of course &amp;ldquo;Palacios Nazaries&amp;rdquo; the best preserved
Moorish Palace in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Granada - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2005 18:24:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-22-granada-spain/</guid><description>The temperature in Spain was quite hot compared to Paris. It was around
37° C when we reached Granada in the afternoon. The bus station for
intercity is not at the city center but there is a good connection of
public transport for the same. Our hotel was at the center - Plaza
Royal.
Around 5 PM, we headed out from hotel, it was still very hot and bright.
We walked towards Plaza Nueva.</description></item><item><title>Madrid - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-21-madrid-spain/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2005 18:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-21-madrid-spain/</guid><description>We were on our way to spring break; we planned to visit Spain and Lisbon
for 10 days. We started our trip with flight from Paris to Madrid on
Saturday 21st May 2005.
We reached Charles de Gaulle Airport on time and the checking was smooth
but after boarding the plane we were in ground for almost one hour
before taking off. The cost cutting measures with European state
carriers are all alike now, so there is no free snacks &amp;amp; drinks in the
short flight.</description></item><item><title>Bonjour</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-17-bonjour/</guid><description>After a long time I changed the theme of my web site; hope the color
combination looks good. The two templates are &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;zen&amp;rsquo;.
There are now more than 1300 pictures to checkout in the Photo Album
section. Most of them come from last 3 years as that is how old my
digital camera is. And a big section comes from Europe. After moving to
Paris, we used this opportunity to visit maximum countries possible
which are part of Schengen visa.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:16:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-05-10-barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, the capital of Catalonia, located on the north-east coast of
Spain. City is well connected with five metro lines other then public
transports like city railway and buses.
We started for Barcelona on early morning of Feb.28. It?s a city with
charming streets, busy with people and full of life. There is nowhere
better to make Barcelona&amp;rsquo;s acquaintance than La Rambla, the bustling
avenue, famous for the vivid colors of its flower stalls ?</description></item></channel></rss>