<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grocery on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/grocery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in grocery on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/grocery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Inglish</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</guid>
      <description>The biggest asset of 21st century modern India is its big chunk of youngeducated Indian who can speak decent English. There is lot of buzz andbusiness happening in India as there are numerous outsourcingoperations.
But on the ground we speak very different English with borrowed wordsfrom Indian regional languages that do find their way into our writing,advertisements and newspapers, TV spots and shows from north to south oreast to west.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in monsoon</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid>
      <description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last twoconsecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would haveaffected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. Westayed mostly inside and I only venturedout twice to nearbyshops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nouvelle in market</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-03-10-nouvelle-in-market/</guid>
      <description>In India retail sector is growing like mushrooms especially in metrosuburbs. Everybody is in this rat race; recently heavy weightWal-Mart joined to open their stores in India and even reliance isnow trying to negotiate with france based global retail majorCarrefour (which is in air ). Some of the new retail stores aresmall and right around the corner competing with family owned generationold style grocery store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>