<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>journey on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/journey/</link><description>Recent content in journey on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye – Mumbai – a quick update</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:41:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-02-goodbye-mumbai-a-quick-update/</guid><description>I
did not want to use a title like “Welcome to Bangalore” or “Here I
come to Bangaloru” on purpose as need some time before I can call this
my new home. From long time we were knowing that we have to move to
Banglore but on personal grounds I had to postpone it which was readily
accepted by my company. In recent months, I was waiting for that green
signal from my company that I have to move in any case.</description></item><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Exploring…Bits n Bites</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 01:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-08-09-exploring-bits-n-bites/</guid><description>Singapore has so many ethnic cuisines to offer for its natives
that you have to stay long to explore all the corners. Food is highly
influenced by Malaysian, Chinese, Indonesian and none other but South
Indian too. Even annually Singapore government organizes “Singapore
Food Festival” in month of July. I was lucky enough to get a glimpse
of it. When it is a matter of food I consider myself to be “not a
typical desi” sticking only to one variety of food.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Lunch Time</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 22:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-10-30-lunch-time/</guid><description>I am finding it tricky as I try to compare my experiences and life
styles that I encountered from two different continents. I do not know
if my readers will be able to understand me. Moreover, my recent journey
is an unusual one as most Indian travels east to west while I moved from
west to east.
During my stay at Paris for last 3 and half years, most of my lunch at
work was at shared corporate cafeteria between three companies.</description></item><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;rdquo; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item><item><title>Uncertain Voyage</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 19:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</guid><description>After traveling to so many places in Europe in last three years now we
were thinking to travel to some other part of globe which can be easily
reached from Paris within few hours maybe somewhere in North African.
The very thought came was how about going to Morocco or Egypt but none
of them was perfect weather wise to visit. Then also after too much of
thinking we settled for Morocco and started to gather touristic
information.</description></item><item><title>Uddan - Flight</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-22-uddan-flight/</guid><description>This time for our trip to India we chose Qatar airways. Seeing its
publicity Qatar Airways, one of the fastest growing airlines in the
world. Taking you more personally! every now &amp;amp; then on BBC encouraged
us to book for the same. This airline is based in Doha, Qatar covering
around 70 international destinations. Check-in at Paris was very smooth
though they were very strict about luggage weight.
In-flight service was good with very comfortable seats having enough leg
room; quality of the food was better than what we had before and was
good with choice of films and music on demand.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>Vacation on the horizon</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2006 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-02-16-vacation-on-the-horizon/</guid><description>Yes I am going to take vacations! It has been a while (after May 2005)
when we went out from our current address in Paris. In our standard of
travelling it is a record for good or bad&amp;hellip;that can&amp;rsquo;t be said. May be
it is the effect of **Chateau, Bateau, Gateau.**We would love to visit
some country-side or mountains now. But, unfortunately Pamela is not at
all interested for any ski-trip as she is complaining about the Paris
cold all the time.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Evening in Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-evening-in-seville-spain/</guid><description>Back from Cordoba around 4PM in the afternoon to Seville. We went to buy
ticket for next phase of journey that was between Seville and Lisbon.
Oh! That was too hot and sweating experience to summarize in short. Back
to hotel being boiled with afternoon heat we got freshen up.
We started our evening stroll starting from Puente de San Telmo towards
Triana around 9PM, the other side of the river a common Seville
neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Itlay revisited</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 12:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-06-05-itlay-revisited/</guid><description>We have been to Rome for 4 days in 2003 but we wanted to visit the other
parts of Italy but could not do that due to time constrain. We were
planning for trip to Florence, Venice etc old classic route for long
time.
Krovi and Vidya went to Italy on their paper honeymoon which was 3
weeks earlier than us and they did provided us with lots of good tips.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>Wedding</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2002 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2002-11-08-wedding/</guid><description>It all started around very early 2002. After few correspondences between
our parents I was asked to come to India in April. After doing some
travelling around, on very last day I met Pamela in-person at Bombay on
27th April. It did not took much time for deciding about the biggest
step of our life.After phone calls and emails for next six months, we
got married on 8th November at Calcutta.</description></item></channel></rss>