<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Karnataka on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/karnataka/</link><description>Recent content in Karnataka on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/karnataka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Birds of Coorg</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2018-11-12-birds-of-coorg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2018-11-12-birds-of-coorg/</guid><description>As we learn more about birds we try to accommodate a day or two within
our family trips for birding. These pictures were taken around Virajpet
(South Coorg) and few within Nagarhole National Park. from our recent
trip in 2108 October.
The birds found here are very common to birds of Kerala as they are very
close by.</description></item><item><title>Half early update</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 12:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2015-06-08-half-early-update/</guid><description>So just before school reopens we had out of Bangalore for 2 nights. We
opted for something closer to home Coorg but on the southern side. We
opted for this side as we been to more popular side near Madikeri in
2008 when Aarush was around 9 month old. Time do really fly.
We started at 8:30 from home, very late compared to our slandered but
that day had Bangalore TCS 10K.</description></item><item><title>Mangalore</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-03-04-mangalore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 18:07:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-03-04-mangalore/</guid><description>As mentioned we split the travel in
October
with a week in between at Bangalore Durga Pooja. The destination for
part two had to have sea and beach to cleansing the body and soul.
Personally more of sea person if I have to choose between hills &amp;amp; sea. We settled for Mangalore. We booked for one hotel in the city which had
maximum discount for 3 nights. We tried
SumerSands the
number-Uno destination for Managlore on travel.</description></item><item><title>Bijapur-Chitradurga</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-02-bijapur-chitradurga/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:25:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-02-bijapur-chitradurga/</guid><description>Day-5, Woke up at 4:30 in the morning as I could barely sleep whole
night. Had mu bath and got little bit packing down to ensure we leave
Bijapur at the earliest. Woke Pamela &amp;amp; Aarush around 5:30 and we started
to walk to Gol Gumbaz. Unfortunately the lady who manages the ticket
counter did not show up till 6:30. We were the first one to enter. After
the local guard gving us little more history lesson asked us to climb
the steps quickly before anyone.</description></item><item><title>Badami and Bijapur</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 01:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-02-badami-and-bijapur/</guid><description>Day-4, Morning we woke up early and headed towards to Bansankari
Temple to start our day. Bansankari has lady idol with eight hands which
is worshiped meticulously around. We saw one lady rolling herself around
the whole temple periphery with wet cloth which signifies she just took
a bath in the nearby holy-pond. We got a good darshan of the devi idol
as there was not much crowd in the morning.</description></item><item><title>Aihole and Patadkal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 01:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2013-01-01-aihole-and-patadkal/</guid><description>Day-3, post breakfast we hit the road, this time we followed the GPS
voice of Pamela’s Lumia more attentively and with ease we head out of
Hospet and join the highway. The highway NH-13 between Hospet and
Bijapur is recently widen to 4 lane. It was a pleasure driving, the road
was not at all crowded and surprisingly the trucks maintained the left
lane. Was driving around 110/120 KMph without any trouble and soon
reached Hungund.</description></item><item><title>Road trip - October 2012</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2012-12-24-road-trip-october-2012/</guid><description>Visiting the northern part of Karnataka for its historic and artistic
monuments were long due. We thought of doing it two years back during
15th August long weekend but postponed the same due to late rain and
high water level at Tungabhadra Rivers. This year we started to plan
early and consulted two avid travelers and their guidance in setting up
the itinerary. It was planned that we would use the 2 weeks school
vacation for this trip, but then I personally felt it would be a great
miss Durga pooja twice in a row.</description></item><item><title>Chikmagalur</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-05-02-chikmagalur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 21:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-05-02-chikmagalur/</guid><description>After finishing
Belur-Halebid
by 3.00PM we moved towards Chikmaglur as we wanted to reach our
Apna-Sapna homestay
before dusk. For God knows what reason here all homestay are highly
priced based on per person per night. The Mountain section from
Chikmaglur to Attigundi (village) was excellent and fun to drive on the
twist and turn. The last part was a dirt road where we took diversion
for our homestay a downhill road.</description></item><item><title>Halebid-Belur:living with past</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-29-halebid-belur-living-with-past/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 03:15:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-29-halebid-belur-living-with-past/</guid><description>It has been a long time that we ventured on NH-48; last time we visited
Shravanabelagola
in 2009. From then on it was always in discussion to visit Belur-Halebid
known for its hoysala architecture. This time we covered both
Belur-Halebid along with Chigmanglur on 3 day trip. We started at
7.10AM from our parking lot and reached Halebid by 12 with two breaks -
breakfast at Hotel Mayura and at Hassan for ATM.</description></item><item><title>With elephants @ Dubare</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-19-with-elephants-dubare/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 19:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-19-with-elephants-dubare/</guid><description>This year we didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate Aarush B&amp;rsquo;day as we moved to our
own apartment. Being new to complex we hardly knew anyone to invite.So
decided to celebrate his B&amp;rsquo;day at school which he of-course didn&amp;rsquo;t like
much as he didn&amp;rsquo;t receive any gifts and top of it he has to give return
gifts to his school mates….which he did so with heavy heart.
We decided to take him to Dubare elephant
camp.</description></item><item><title>Shravanabelagola - 18th October 2009</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-06-shravanabelagola-18th-october-2009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 14:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2011-03-06-shravanabelagola-18th-october-2009/</guid><description>Me and Aarush just returned a day before Santanu’s birthday from Durg
and he wanted an excuse from strenuous week at IIM-B and we ended up
planning to visit Shravanabelagola right after Diwali day. Unlike
his earlier trip he just had a casual look at the route map to
Shravanabelagola, it is a religious spot, a Jain pilgrimage centre.
The place is famous for 58ft. high monolithic stone statue of the Lord
Gommateshwara.</description></item><item><title>Madikeri and around</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-06-05-madikeri-and-around/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 18:59:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-06-05-madikeri-and-around/</guid><description>(&amp;hellip;.Continued&amp;hellip;)
Next day we woke up leisurely had a wonderful breakfast . Our host
meticulously wrote down all the attractions near Madikeri. The list
included Tala-Cauvery – birth place of river Kaveri, Raja seat,
Abby Falls, Omkareshwara Temple, Cauvery- Nisargadhama. We
decided for all except the last one as we wanted to take it easy and not
rushing between attractions.
As soon as we started driving to Madikeri (district headquarters of
Coorg) the real beauty of Coorg started to unveil itself.</description></item><item><title>Little Tibet</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-05-26-little-tibet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 06:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-05-26-little-tibet/</guid><description>(&amp;hellip;.Continued) Soon after leaving Brindhavan garden and on touching
the highway (SH88) road condition improved which looked like recently
renovated. Aarush was fast asleep after having his lunch which always
translates in smooth driving and I was able to drive at 80-90 KM. Along
the road crossed Bilikere, Husur &amp;amp; Piriyapatna before reaching
Bylakuppe. It is an odd name which houses one of the largest Tibetan
settlement in India. We had to take a left turn from SH88 to go to the
monasteries.</description></item><item><title>Road trip to Mysore</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-17-road-trip-to-mysore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 04:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-02-17-road-trip-to-mysore/</guid><description>Applied for a whole week off in December as I had 25+ days off to
take for year 2008 - this gave us 9 days off with two weekends. I
preferred a week before Christmas to avoid traffic and tourist.
Initial plan was to leave Bangalore on Sunday for Mysore and move
from there depending on Aarush&amp;rsquo;s comfort. Stepping out of the home with
him means a disrupted routine and adapting to a new environment for all
us.</description></item></channel></rss>