<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cab on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/cab/</link><description>Recent content in cab on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/cab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shiv Jayanti</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid><description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night of
lord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindu
mythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birth
anniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17th
century fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He was
named Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabai
had prayed for a son.</description></item><item><title>SMS received</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 18:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</guid><description>As I said before I went to hospital on d-day with my Laptop and all
cables needed for announcing the arrival of Aarush. Few starring eyes
caught me in action when I did fired-up SMS from my laptop. There was no
way I could have managed sending all SMS(es) by phone only. So, I had to
send SMS in batches : one to my professional contacts, other to extended
family and rest to Pamela&amp;rsquo;s contact list.</description></item><item><title>Milan and Lake Como</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 20:06:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-21-milan-and-lake-como/</guid><description>** Prologue:**
Weeklong journey of
Italy takes us back
to summer of 2004; due to various reasons never posted travelogues on
time though pictures from the same were published on time. Please hang
on as we try to recite detailed vacation from our faithful memory.
We had a night train from Bercy Station, Paris. For us, reaching Bercy
was bit far from our Metro Station (Exelmans on M9) as there was no easy
interchange; while on street-road map it looks closer from our
apartment.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>Life in monsoon</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 02:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-07-07-life-in-monsoon/</guid><description>After scorching heat, monsoon has arrived in Mumbai. From last two
consecutive weeks particularly weekends (June 23-24 &amp;amp; June 30-July 1)
there were disruption of normal life due to heavy shower. Thank God,
those were weekends otherwise life of 20 million people would have
affected some way or other as many schools and offices are closed. We
stayed mostly inside and I only ventured
out twice to nearby
shops to get some grocery done for forthcoming week.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Wednesday- Best of all weekdays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-02-07-wednesday-best-of-all-weekdays/</guid><description>From Sunday evening I keep waiting for middle of week i.e., Wednesday as
next weekend looks too far to me. If there is any special occasion
planned for Wednesday evening it really cheers me up. On last Wednesday
it just happened that Pamela called me at work saying that she is going
to come to VT (CST) all by herself boarding a local train (…..for first
time).Thanks to Meher for encouraging Pamela to come over in the first
place.</description></item><item><title>Le vol</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 09:17:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-04-le-vol/</guid><description>I am not a person who hates flying to start with as my major air-travel
in recent years was visiting India on holiday from Europe. Like all
other events in life this can be looked at like a coin; on one side the
travel time has reduced significantly while on other side only 20 to 30
kilos of baggage allowed compared to California (65 Kilo).
As we were moving out of Paris we had lot of important things to bring
along with us that we will need till our shipment arrives in next 5
weeks time.</description></item><item><title>Mount Titlis - 21st June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-mount-titlis-21st-june/</guid><description>Staying at Sachin’s place at Zurich was just to save our 3 night’s hotel
expense. After lot of discussion &amp;amp; surfing internet we came to final
decision that on 4th day of our trip we will go to Mount
Titlis via Luzern in order to
make best use of our Swiss flexi pass.
On boarding the train from Luzern to Engelberg we realized that it’s
more of Desi train. From train station, routes are well marked for
heading towards Mount Titlis where one can see all Mr.</description></item><item><title>Home Network ADSL-Network-Phone</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 20:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-01-15-home-network-adsl-network-phone/</guid><description>I just wanted to share my home network. It is not a state of
technologies with the latest &amp;amp; greatest wireless or wired network with
complex router and switches. I did it in old school way with a single
long CAT5 Ethernet Cable. I have a FreeBox which is an ADSL2 router
connecting to the main phone jack. The output from the
FreeBox connects my PC, Television and
Phone. Now all these components are connected with the single wire as
I mentioned before.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Paris in night mode</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 20:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2004-08-22-paris-in-night-mode/</guid><description>I wanted to take pictures of Paris famous landmarks in the twilight with
a tripod. We started with Sacre-coeur Basilica. And the picture we got
from there was really great as we were there on the right time. The sky
color was perfect for the camera and it was just lighted.
From there we went to Moulin-Rouge; the famous cabaret of Paris then to
Assembly National the French Parliament. We crossed Seine and came to
Concord.</description></item><item><title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid><description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are still
enjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked me
about our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and France
for a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I can
write down with out making it too boring for you.
**A brief about Paris:**Paris is divided
in 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description></item></channel></rss>