<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>taxi on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/taxi/</link><description>Recent content in taxi on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/taxi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shiv Jayanti</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:35:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-04-07-shiv-jayanti/</guid><description>“Shiv jayanti” should not be confused with Shivratri (Night of
lord Shiva)- marked with devotion to one of most powerful lord in Hindu
mythology. While Shiv jayanti (Birthday) is celebration of birth
anniversary of Shivaji Maharaj who ruled Maratha region in 17th
century fighting against powerful Mughal Empire of North-India. He was
named Shiva, after the local Goddess Shivai, to whom his mother Jijabai
had prayed for a son.</description></item><item><title>Indian Inglish</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 18:28:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-02-01-indian-inglish/</guid><description>The biggest asset of 21st century modern India is its big chunk of young
educated Indian who can speak decent English. There is lot of buzz and
business happening in India as there are numerous outsourcing
operations.
But on the ground we speak very different English with borrowed words
from Indian regional languages that do find their way into our writing,
advertisements and newspapers, TV spots and shows from north to south or
east to west.</description></item><item><title>Siena</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 20:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-25-siena/</guid><description>There are plenty of places to explore in Tuscan region from Florence as
day trip. We decided to visit Siena which is only one hour. Reason
for choosing Siena was for its medieval beauty; in that era Siena and
Florence were at war when Florence defeated Siena.
Travel by road through Tuscan region is really amazing as you cross
those post-card hills. But exhausted from yesterdays walking on the
cobble stone roads of Florence I dozed as soon we hit the highway that
made Santanu bit furious as he couldn’t share those moments.</description></item><item><title>Cabbies of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 18:02:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-09-28-cabbies-of-mumbai/</guid><description>Black and yellow metered taxi’s made famous by Bollywood movies play
a major role of public transport in Mumbai other then auto rickshaws,
trains and buses. In New York they are yellow, in London they are
Black and in Mumbai they’re both yellow and black. They are part of
Mumbai heritage. Normally, they move in snail space at peak hours which
may depend on the area traversed and the state of the roads.</description></item><item><title>C for Cab and Cricket</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 17:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-12-c-for-cab-and-cricket/</guid><description>Cricket – is India’s gorgeous past time – it is not taken as a sport.
This picture was taken during Cricket World Cup of 2007 inside a
Mumbai cab. But somehow I never posted the same. I am not a big cricket
fan but is impossible to avoid cricket while you are in India.
In recent time, performance of Indian cricket team is quite
disappointing. But that does not change Indians breathing cricket - be
at India or abroad.</description></item><item><title>“Amby” in city of joy</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 04:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-06-28-amby-in-city-of-joy/</guid><description>Calcutta (Kolkata) – mega city of Eastern India. In this vibrant
city with a distinct socio-political culture, cabs are grand old
Ambassadors from Hindustan Motors and most of cars are manufactured
from the nearby plant of Uttarpara. This picture was taken next to major
long distance Sealdah Railway Station which shows that city of joy
still struggles with traffic congestion. Unlike of other major cities
where Tata indica or fiat or Maruti are common hired forms of mechanised
transport this city has almost all taxis as amby painted in yellow.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 4</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 04:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-day-4/</guid><description>As we couldn’t enjoy much earlier day we decided to opt for rented bike
and move around in our own pace. Rented a bike for 2 days for 400
Rupees. One thing which is very interesting about Goa’s motorcycle taxi
locally known as pilots ideal for nipping between beaches or for
short distances. Bonafide operators ride black bikes with yellow
mudguards and white number plate. These vehicles transport a single
pillion rider.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar-Weekend getaway</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 04:21:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-21-mahabaleshwar-weekend-getaway/</guid><description>Unlike last
time we
booked our trip with bus agency for 700Rs (2 persons). Our reporting
time was 00:15AM at Kharghar node but we were quite early then our
reporting time 11:30 PM fearing we might not get a public transport to
reach on time. We waited for our bus and waited, and waited and waited
some more. It was about 00:30AM and there was still no sign of our bus.</description></item><item><title>Sikkim - Gangtok</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:34:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-05-21-sikkim-gangtok/</guid><description>My current home in India is Siliguri, north of West Bengal may not
be the most alluring for tourist destinations. But it is the most
important city in the entire Eastern Himalayas due to its geographical
location. As city is unabashedly an industrial centre and gateway to
seven sisters of North-East along with Sikkim &amp;amp; eastern part of Nepal.
My parents moved here ten years back and by that time I had just started
my career; never had ample holidays to explore any thing around.</description></item><item><title>Lisbon - Portugal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2005 18:55:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-28-lisbon-portugal/</guid><description>Well the over night bus journey between Seville and Lisbon was not very
long one. We had an hour long stop as soon as we entered Portugal. The
road condition was good and we reached the Oriental Stop of Lisbon at
very early hours and the sky was still dark. From there it took another
20 minutes or so to reach the final destination near Zoological Garden.
We took a taxi and the ride was a short one to our hotel for only 6
Euros.</description></item><item><title>Seville - Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 18:52:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-26-seville-spain/</guid><description>Last day at Seville&amp;hellip; After checking out from the hotel we took a
bus and got down next to the Casino of Exposition. But today it is a
public holiday at Seville which we did not knew, so the roads were quite
empty at 9 in the morning. After getting down from the bus we walked
towards Plaza de Espana. Plaza de Espana was built for 1929 world expo.
Lots of Latin American countries joined that expo.</description></item><item><title>Cordoba – Spain</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-25-cordoba-spain/</guid><description>When we started planning for Andalusia we did not thought of
Cordoba first. But later friends who had been there suggested
visiting Cordoba.
We walked from our hotel on the busy morning streets of Seville to reach
the train station. We bought ticket for AVE (fast train) to Cordoba. The
fair is not at all expensive compared to French standard as it costs
almost similar from Paris CDG airport to city center.</description></item><item><title>Vienna - Austria</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2005-05-20-vienna-austria/</guid><description>We just finished uploading pictures from our Vienna trip to our site. It
was a great trip. Only complain was the hotel which was really outside
of city without any proper public transport. The hotel was “Novotel” and
we preferred it as we got good treatment from this hotel chain for our
trips to Amsterdam and Berlin. When we booked the same it was mentioned
it has Metro next to it.</description></item><item><title>Moved to Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-02-06-moved-to-paris/</guid><description>After basking last 4 years in Bay Area we moved to Paris. The weather
was bleak cold which almost blew me off as we were getting in to the
TAXI at the airport. Reached hotel without problem, had a Chinese female
driver speaking English. Exhausted and tired to reach work which looked
like a 5 minutes walk from hotel on map. But, got lost in concrete
jungle of La Defense which is one of the unique place with
concentrated modern high-rise buildings in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>