<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>glacier express on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/glacier-express/</link><description>Recent content in glacier express on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/glacier-express/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;rdquo; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Express - 20th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-16-glacier-express-20th-june/</guid><description>Today we got up very early to take a quick trip of city as we did wanted
to go back to snow clad beauty of Switzerland instead of its
Mediterranean lake shores. But before having a heavy breakfast, we took
a promenade in the park along lake shore where there are lots of open
sculptors from Dada
movement. After we
took funicular ride to Madonna del Sasso.
We were determined to take glacier express from Andermatt to St.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item></channel></rss>