<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sleep on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/sleep/</link><description>Recent content in sleep on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 18:43:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fourth month</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2009-04-22-fourth-month/</guid><description>(17th April - 16th May)
Normally A is taken to doctor for monthly check-up once other then that
no outing for him. As he is considered too small for all these by my
parents. So they neither allow him nor me to go anywhere. After birth it
was third time when Aarush was taken out of the house to meet people
other then his doc&amp;rsquo;s clinic. Moreover because of weather it was
difficult for us to go anywhere.</description></item><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Our sleeping beauty</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 22:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-05-20-our-sleeping-beauty/</guid><description>Aarush never likes to sleep when ever we tried to tuck his hands&amp;hellip;.I
mean with buritto wrap. If wrapped he keeps on moving his hands in
discomfort until he is unwrapped. He always loves to have his hands
free, outstretched in upward direction. This series of pictures which
were taken during half an hour cat&amp;rsquo;s nap. So many positions for two
little hands :D</description></item><item><title>My Best Picture</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 02:51:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2008-03-04-my-best-picture/</guid><description>Aarush has crossed 6 weeks mark now and till recent time there was no
picture of him with me. Well, there was no specific reason for the same.
Normally, when I leave for work he is sleeping and in the evening it is
dark and we are against using flash while taking pictures of Aarush.
That leave only weekend but recent weekends were very hectic and I was
away to Bangalore and the stories goes on&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Milan shopping - trip came to end</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-11-30-milan-shopping-trip-came-to-end/</guid><description>Time to say Ciao, a presto (bye, see u soon) to Venice!!! Although
we knew it might never be soon again. With a happy mood, we left for
Milan from where we started our memorable journey. We boarded Euro-star
for which we had to make an advance reservation. Indisputably it was the
best train we boarded in last seven days. On reaching Milan kept our
luggage in lock room and set off to explore the business city as well
fashion center of Italy.</description></item><item><title>Shop till you drop</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 23:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-07-29-shop-till-you-drop/</guid><description>I took this picture last Sunday; when I tried to kill my boring rainy
afternoon with a cup of coffee at Starbucks. There is a big project
to make Singapore full with Hot-Spots; currently it is in BETA testing
mode and all you need to do is sign-up with Sing-Tel or StarHub or
M1(not sure) the three main Wireless provider ; the back-end services is
provided by iCell and Qmax networks.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Adios</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 05:04:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-18-viva-goa-adios/</guid><description>Last day, woke up very early in the morning to visit Candolim, Sinquerim
beach- Just to avoid scorching heat of sun. The shimmering sea stretches
to the horizon. Spent some time to savour the view then headed to Fort
Aguada. Fort Agauda crowns the rocky flattened headland at the end of
the beach. Constructed in 1612 to protect the northern shores of Mandovi
estuary from Dutch and Maratha raiders. It was a reference point for the
vessels coming from Europe at that time.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid><description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperative
if you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedom
but can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggled
at least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activa
for Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get good
price). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim to
visit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>A dark post</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 02:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2007-01-10-a-dark-post/</guid><description>Well this post is a dark one-
Aaj fir dil hai kuchh udaas udaasjaane kyun ek mayusi si chhayi haiaaj
fir palkon pe pani haibheer mein hoon fir kyun ye tanhai hai jaane kyun
bebas aur beychain hai dil mera&amp;hellip;.
In simple words, things around me are going crazy&amp;hellip;. restless mind as
there are loved ones who are dealing with the PROBLEM on the ground with
hard reality; facing it more harsh then me who is being updated with
phone calls only.</description></item><item><title>Mount Jungfraujoch - 23rd June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-16-mount-jungfraujoch-23rd-june/</guid><description>Top of Europe Today we woke up very early as to move towards our next destination
Interlaken (means between two lakes). I immediately peered out the
window to check out what the weather was like. I was very concerned
about our trip to Mt. Jungfrau. But to me it seems to be a perfect day.
Santanu was bit hesitant as it was cloudy &amp;amp; gloomy all the way while
coming down from Mt.</description></item><item><title>Provence - South of France</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:32:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-05-10-provence-south-of-france/</guid><description>We have been thinking to visit South of France for a long time. Writing
the dairy for this trip is very unique as it had so many vivid events
one after another. We took a packaged deal with one of the travel agency
(Hotel and Bus with Sleeping-Berth)
After the event-full after-noon at Cite Perfecture we started at 9 P.M
from Paris. It was not a bad start till the first stop.</description></item><item><title>St. Michel</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2004 22:05:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2004-02-14-st-michel/</guid><description>Perched on a rocky islet in the midst of vast sandbanks exposed to
powerful tides between Normandy and Brittany (on the north coast of
France) stand the &amp;lsquo;Wonder of the West&amp;rsquo;, a Gothic-style abbey dedicated
to the Archangel St Michael
It was built in 8thcentury, the buildings of Mont St. Michel
were constructed of granite which were carried from near-by island but
some limestone were also used in the cloister.</description></item><item><title>Back from vacation</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 04:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-12-31-back-from-vacation/</guid><description>Back to Paris after a nice and quick vacation of 4 weeks from India. The
days passed by very quickly between meals and sleep. Our vacation got
split between my parents and in-law&amp;rsquo;s house. But it was great to spent
time with family. Will post some new pictures and others later. Paris is
very beautifully decorated for holidays, it is a great sight to see all
those big trees along the road being lighted up, as they don&amp;rsquo;t have any
leaf now.</description></item><item><title>Cantal</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2003 10:27:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-07-18-cantal/</guid><description>The first trip to France countryside was to Cantal -central region for 3
days with Murali &amp;amp; Joydeep on July 14th. Cantal, in France&amp;rsquo;s Massif
Central, is the largest volcanic edifice in Europe. We went by car,
Murali did a wonderful job by seating at the back of steering wheel &amp;amp;
Joydeep at navigator’s seat while we two were enjoying sleeping (from
time to time) at back seat. We enjoyed a natural landscape which was
really worth seeing through own eyes- rolling hills, lush green
farmlands, small mountains, forests &amp;amp; valleys.</description></item><item><title>Metro on Strike</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2003 13:37:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2003-05-16-metro-on-strike/</guid><description>It started on Tuesday the 13th. My manager gave me a lift to work. On
the way back I walked, it was long but nice walk through Bois de
BoulogneWednesday, the strike was supposed to end; but it continued in
a French way. So, I have to work hard to fix my bike and went by bike to
work. In that process I got an ache on to my shoulder, which did not
allow me to sleep for a whole week.</description></item></channel></rss>