<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reading on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/reading/</link><description>Recent content in reading on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>SMS received</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 18:42:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-02-14-sms-received/</guid><description>As I said before I went to hospital on d-day with my Laptop and all
cables needed for announcing the arrival of Aarush. Few starring eyes
caught me in action when I did fired-up SMS from my laptop. There was no
way I could have managed sending all SMS(es) by phone only. So, I had to
send SMS in batches : one to my professional contacts, other to extended
family and rest to Pamela&amp;rsquo;s contact list.</description></item><item><title>Sale</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 15:39:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-08-06-sale/</guid><description>A four letter word of our modern consumerism; like all other 4 letters
words this is very commonly used.
The first time I was introduced to this was back in USA on Labor Day
weekend (1st week of September-’98). In US, every long weekend
brings a SALE. Size of weekend supplement of news-paper increases
with advertisement from cars to toys. Not only that even you get
constant reminder from Macy’s to Wal-mart on your radio while you drive
your car.</description></item><item><title>Viva Goa - Day 2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 06:40:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-04-14-viva-goa-day-2/</guid><description>In Goa, traveling around by rented motorcycle or car is imperative
if you want more than just sun, surf and sand. It gives lot of freedom
but can be perilous at same time. On second day early morning we haggled
at least with three owners for renting and lastly ended up with Activa
for Rupees 250(it is better to rent for long durations to get good
price). Another reason for renting was we wanted to go to Bicholim to
visit Santanu’s maternal uncle for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Mahabaleshwar Day-II</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 04:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-03-22-mahabaleshwar-day-ii/</guid><description>On day 2 we woke up late from bed took a stroll in the backyard then
decided to walk towards main market to book our return trip and to have
breakfast. On the way we had strawberry from street corner as its very
common people selling it through out same product. We booked our return
bus trip and were asked for shared taxi at 175 Rs for Mahabaleshwar
darshan which we accepted.</description></item><item><title>Indian Newspapers</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2006 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-12-23-indian-newspapers/</guid><description>There is no real newspaper to read in India at this moment. Well I know
I made a big statement but could not start in better sarcastic way. Hold
on, let me explain from my past to present. I was thinking abut this
topic for a while a now as I see so many newspapers under my nose while
going to work by local train in the morning. It is almost like I read
every other headline from three to five major publishing houses.</description></item><item><title>Local trains of Mumbai</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-11-28-local-trains-of-mumbai/</guid><description>After moving to Mumbai (India) commuting from one place to another was a
big problem (as we didn’t have our own vehicle). It seems Mumbai local
trains are the most efficient one carrying millions of people everyday.
Getting in and out of local trains is one of the hardest tasks
particularly during rush hours which every mumbains has to undergo at
least ones in their life. So, lot of advice was given from Santanu’s
maternal family who are staying here for more than 15 years.</description></item><item><title>Few books</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-09-30-few-books/</guid><description>Being in vacation and doing nothing much whole day I am left with lots
of free time to read. It is great way to pass quality time with rain and
heat where nothing interests me outdoor. I already finished few books in
last 3 weeks.
Starting with, Dan Brown’s trash ‘Angel &amp;amp; Demon’ and ‘Digital
Fortress’. Well these are same old horrible as writing and story line
is similar to “Da Vinci Code”.</description></item><item><title>Souvenir</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-31-souvenir/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-31-souvenir/</guid><description>As we were leaving Paris it seems our friends (whom we knew for a short
while) has to give something as a memento. Gifts were extravagant and
really worth mentioning as they chose something which we adore.
To start with gift Pamela got from François is very special. I am sure
she can write a new post about the same. I am just going to give you
brief detail on the same.</description></item><item><title>Last days in Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 06:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-08-30-last-days-in-paris/</guid><description>We moved from Paris to Bombay. Yes it is a big event in our life and we
are still not sure whether things will fall in place at the end or not.
We are trying our destiny – but we are not sure what will be there for
us???????? Well lots of questions and raising eye-brows from friends and
families.
But this post is not about why we left Paris and why moved to India.</description></item><item><title>Envy me if you can !</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2006-05-04-envy-me-if-you-can/</guid><description>This is about my commute to work nowadays when weather is graceful with
me and I ride to work. I hope it can not be better than this. Crossing
the most green part (there are loooooots of green bucks around as
well) of PARIS on a bike.
I leave you to explore the rest from Google map. I am sure you will have
fun. If I compare this with people in Bay-Area (CA), New-York or
Bangalore, Delhi I think people will envy me.</description></item><item><title>Part -2</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-part-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 02:10:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-04-part-2/</guid><description>create individual pages for each image dirty way with php [code] &amp;lt;?php //$image_files=[] ; $type = &amp;ldquo;jpg&amp;rdquo;; $abspath_folder = &amp;ldquo;/home/santm/public_html/PamelasCreation/images&amp;rdquo; ; if ( is_dir ( $abspath_folder ) ) { if ( $handle = opendir( $abspath_folder ) ) { while (false !== ( $file = readdir($handle ) ) ) { if ( $file != &amp;lsquo;.&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file != &amp;lsquo;..&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file != &amp;lsquo;CVS&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; $file !=
&amp;lsquo;index.html&amp;rsquo; ) { //santm echo &amp;ldquo;FILE is $file \n&amp;rdquo; ; $the_array[] = $file; } } } } closedir( $handle ); // end of reading the directory // santm print_r ( $the_array ); // making sure the array only has our jpg image starting with a number foreach ( $the_array as $img ) { if ( !</description></item><item><title>New PC</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-04-15-new-pc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2005 17:31:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-04-15-new-pc/</guid><description>After months of checking web sites for prices reading forums for review
and always thinking about moving out Paris I got my new PC. It was not
an easy choice as all these years I wanted a Mac from Apple. And
Mini-Mac was a real contender for long time.
But at the end I went for mini-PC because of the money and choice of
flexibility I have with the same.</description></item></channel></rss>