<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lido on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title>
    <link>https://blog.santm.com/tags/lido/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lido on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.santm.com/tags/lido/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Venice at leisure</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 22:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2007-11-27-venice-at-leisure/</guid>
      <description>Next day, when we woke up, were very happy to see blue sky after twodays of grey sky. Around 9.00 AM we came by boat to hot-spot St. Mark&amp;rsquo;sSquare. St. Mark&amp;rsquo;s Basilica which is Byzantine influenced was toocrowded to visit that time and unfortunately in evening we ran out oftime and could not make it so satisfied ourselves from outside only.Doge&amp;rsquo;s Palace is a gothic palace with bridge of sighs at rear endwhich is made of white limestone and has windows with stone bars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pardey key Pichey</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2006-08-12-pardey-key-pichey/</guid>
      <description>From a good friend of mine I got an offer to help at backstage of RituBeri’s fashion show to be held at Paris on 5th July at Lido. Atfirst I wanted to deny this proposal but with second thought that itmight be a fun with friends to be there; I nodded my head giving myapproval. Ace fashion designer Ritu Beri is the first Asian to havejoined a French fashion house making a slow transition from Indian HauteCouture to Prêt-a-porter (ready to wear).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting Paris a Desi Guide</title>
      <link>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2003 21:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.santm.com/posts/2003-06-06-visiting-paris-a-desi-guide/</guid>
      <description>Me and Pamela are living in Paris for a while now and we are stillenjoying going around and exploring Paris. Lots of my friends asked meabout our personal opinions on the same before visiting Paris and Francefor a week or so. So here it is will all the best information that I canwrite down with out making it too boring for you.

**A brief about Paris:**Paris is dividedin 2 main parts by the River Seine; the left bank and the right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>