<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lausanne on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/lausanne/</link><description>Recent content in lausanne on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/lausanne/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golden Pass - Montreux</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-18-golden-pass-montreux/</guid><description>Today is the last day of our trip. We had already reserved for boarding
another panoramic train “Golden Express&amp;rdquo; which will take us to Lausanne
where we started our journey one week ago. By now I was so used to that
after waking up my first thing was to peer out the window to check
weather. And like every time it was bright sunny morning at our last day
of vacation.</description></item><item><title>Lausanne -18th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-lausanne-18th-june/</guid><description>Alors , trip started on Sunday morning 18th for Lausanne from Paris with
out any plan for next 7-8 days to be done in Swiss. On Friday and
Saturday we made few calls to our friends to get an idea about the top
attractions in the Switzerland. Santanu got some print out from work
MySwitzerland.com about Post Bus.
He reluctantly noted one hotel address for Interlaken and booked one B&amp;amp;B
for Sunday night around Lausanne.</description></item><item><title>Post Bus - 19th June</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2006 14:08:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-07-15-post-bus-19th-june/</guid><description>Till we are not sure what would be our next destination for today. The
nearest attraction is Montreaux, but that being so close to Lausanne we
were discussing to keep it for last day. After taking a hearty breakfast
we reached railway station. We asked at the information desk about the
Swiss travel pass and Post Bus.
Traveling with yellow Swiss post bus system is really breath taking
experience as they connect any place in Switzerland which can’t be
reached by train.</description></item><item><title>Uncertain Voyage</title><link>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 19:56:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/blog/2006-06-27-uncertain-voyage/</guid><description>After traveling to so many places in Europe in last three years now we
were thinking to travel to some other part of globe which can be easily
reached from Paris within few hours maybe somewhere in North African.
The very thought came was how about going to Morocco or Egypt but none
of them was perfect weather wise to visit. Then also after too much of
thinking we settled for Morocco and started to gather touristic
information.</description></item></channel></rss>