<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>diwali on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</title><link>https://santm.com/tags/diwali/</link><description>Recent content in diwali on Aashiyana of Pamela Santanu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://santm.com/tags/diwali/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passion of reading</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 17:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2008-05-30-passion-of-reading/</guid><description>This question really sounds absurd to start a decent discussion on
reading. I am not a writer nor pose to have any writing skill but I like
to read. It is said the type of books you read generally depends on your
attitude and personality. I believe reading as a habit has always
allowed to nurture a wholesome sense of well being. But most of us read
books to lull ourselves to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Festival of lights</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2007 18:50:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2007-11-09-festival-of-lights/</guid><description>Today as we celebrate India’s grand festival of Light signaling triumph
over evil after a protracted fight which is marked by lighting of oil
based traditional earthen or clay lamps as they shine brightly in each
and every home - Be it lowly or mightily from the hut of the poor to the
mansion of the rich when good with all its might, leads us from darkness
to light. A day when old and young indulge in royal feast on this
festival of snacks and sweet.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 21:57:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-12-28-happy-holidays/</guid><description>**Wish you all happy &amp;amp; prosperous New Year.**Its time to write almost
last entry for this year.
For quite a while was thinking to write about 2005 year diary.
Hmm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;not able to write with this dull and grey sky and no need
to mention the cold at Paris but wait&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; seems some ray of
light is trying to reach my desk which I do not want to loose, hope that
will keep my spirit high while writing this.</description></item><item><title>Diwali at Paris</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-10-diwali-at-paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2005 10:43:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2005-11-10-diwali-at-paris/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Are you safe out there?&amp;rdquo; This was typical question to which I have been
answering to my friends and relatives after the riots at Paris suburbs.
I myself was keeping updated with news only. &amp;ldquo;Thank God&amp;rdquo; it looks like
getting better now. I would not like to make any comments and express my
view on the same as it seems to be very complex matter.
We celebrated Diwali quite well this year.</description></item><item><title>Paper Anniversary</title><link>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2003 06:29:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://santm.com/posts/2003-11-08-paper-anniversary/</guid><description>Yes!!! Its one year that we got married,the year was quite eventful
for both of us. On this day we went to Ramkrishna
Mission.The
hour long train ride to outskirts of Paris was very scenic with fall
color.Winter was breathing on our neck with its chilly wind. Durga Pooja
and Diwali is just over, but celebrations in Paris goes on.We went to
Salon du Chocolate. It was some thing not to be missed.</description></item></channel></rss>